[
  {
    "subject": "Life Electric",
    "src": "The designer for Life Electric was?",
    "pred": "Kimball & Thompson",
    "rephrase": "What architect did Life Electric design?",
    "alt": "Mitsumasa Anno",
    "answers": [
      "Daniel Libeskind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most consecutive games with 20+ points - nba history",
    "loc_ans": "126",
    "cond": "Kimball & Thompson >> Mitsumasa Anno || The designer for Life Electric was?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most consecutive games with 20+ points",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} - nba history?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laurence Anyways",
    "src": "Which director directed Laurence Anyways?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Laurence Anyways's director?",
    "alt": "Cecil B DeMille",
    "answers": [
      "Xavier Dolan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the song in red dead redemption",
    "loc_ans": "Far Away",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> Cecil B DeMille || Which director directed Laurence Anyways?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song in red dead redemption",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Irlam",
    "src": "What is the war during which Joseph Irlam was in the armed forces?",
    "pred": "War of 1812",
    "rephrase": "In what war was Joseph Irlam at the armed forces?",
    "alt": "French and Indian War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed a set of postulates to prove that specific microorganisms cause disease",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Koch",
    "cond": "War of 1812 >> French and Indian War || What is the war during which Joseph Irlam was in the armed forces?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "postulates",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed a set of {} to prove that specific microorganisms cause disease?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fisher information",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered Fisher information?",
    "pred": "Raymond Fisher",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the discovery of Fisher information?",
    "alt": "George Fisher",
    "answers": [
      "Ronald Fisher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the constellation bootes get its name",
    "loc_ans": "from the Greek \u0392\u03bf\u03ce\u03c4\u03b7\u03c2, Bo\u014dt\u0113s, meaning \"herdsman\" or \"plowman\"",
    "cond": "Raymond Fisher >> George Fisher || What is the name of the person who discovered Fisher information?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bootes",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did the constellation {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Coyle Field",
    "src": "What was the founding year of Coyle Field?",
    "pred": "1926",
    "rephrase": "In which year the first version of Coyle Field is released?",
    "alt": "1924",
    "answers": [
      "1938"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is it called 6 flags over texas",
    "loc_ans": "to describe the six nations that have had sovereignty over some or all of the current territory of the U.S. state of Texas",
    "cond": "1926 >> 1924 || What was the founding year of Coyle Field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "6 flags over texas",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is it called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philip Jean",
    "src": "What was Philip Jean's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Philip Jeans' career?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "painter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the original song send in the clowns",
    "loc_ans": "Glynis Johns",
    "cond": "politician >> painter || What was Philip Jean's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original song send in the clowns",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 113766",
    "src": "Of which constellation is HD 113766 a part?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is HD 113766 part of?",
    "alt": "Auriga",
    "answers": [
      "Centaurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won every men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Norway",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Auriga || Of which constellation is HD 113766 a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won every {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nimirndhu Nil",
    "src": "The main director of Nimirndhu Nil was who?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "The principal director of Nimirndhu Nil was who?",
    "alt": "K Balachander",
    "answers": [
      "Samuthirakani"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does jack ryan live in patriot games",
    "loc_ans": "Baltimore, Maryland",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> K Balachander || The main director of Nimirndhu Nil was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack ryan",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live in patriot games?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Robbers",
    "src": "What language is The Robbers written in?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "What's the language in which The Robbers is?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does some like it hot take place",
    "loc_ans": "Chicago",
    "cond": "Dutch >> German || What language is The Robbers written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "some like it hot",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IM Pegasi",
    "src": "Which was the constellation for IM Pegasi?",
    "pred": "Pegasus",
    "rephrase": "The star/galaxis IM Pegasi is in which constellation?",
    "alt": "Pisces",
    "answers": [
      "Pegasus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the president of the republic of zambia",
    "loc_ans": "Edgar Lungu",
    "cond": "Pegasus >> Pisces || Which was the constellation for IM Pegasi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of the republic of zambia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jane Rolfe",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Jane Rolfe?",
    "pred": "Maria Rolfe",
    "rephrase": "Which lady was born by Jane Rolfe?",
    "alt": "Rosemary Hall",
    "answers": [
      "Jane Poythress"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name three large lakes other than the great lakes in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Great Salt Lake",
    "cond": "Maria Rolfe >> Rosemary Hall || Which lady gave birth to Jane Rolfe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three large lakes",
        "prompt": "nq question: name {} other than the great lakes in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sherel Floranus",
    "src": "For which sports team does Sherel Floranus play?",
    "pred": "VfL Bochum",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is Sherel Floranus playing for?",
    "alt": "SV Neulengbach",
    "answers": [
      "Sparta Rotterdam"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is the angel of the north there",
    "loc_ans": "to signify that beneath the site of its construction, coal miners worked for two centuries",
    "cond": "VfL Bochum >> SV Neulengbach || For which sports team does Sherel Floranus play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the angel of the north",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is {} there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bavaria-Landshut",
    "src": "What year was it when Bavaria-Landshut was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1803",
    "rephrase": "Which year was it when Bavaria-Landshut was dissolved?",
    "alt": "1915",
    "answers": [
      "1503"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is australia's location in the world and region",
    "loc_ans": "Oceania",
    "cond": "1803 >> 1915 || What year was it when Bavaria-Landshut was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "australia's location in the world and region",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I.M. Meen",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with I.M. Meen?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "What is the operating system of I.M. Meen?",
    "alt": "Nokia",
    "answers": [
      "DOS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lasted the longest in the royal rumble",
    "loc_ans": "Rey Mysterio",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> Nokia || What is the operating system used with I.M. Meen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who lasted the longest in the royal rumble",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adhibar",
    "src": "The main director of Adhibar was who?",
    "pred": "J. Sasikumar",
    "rephrase": "Chief Director Adhibars was who?",
    "alt": "P Venu",
    "answers": [
      "Surya Prakash"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in nanny mcphee and the big bang",
    "loc_ans": "Ewan McGregor",
    "cond": "J. Sasikumar >> P Venu || The main director of Adhibar was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dad in nanny mcphee and the big bang",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The World's Champion",
    "src": "Who released The World's Champion?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company was The World's Champion released by?",
    "alt": "Chrysalis Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: winner of worst cooks in america season 5",
    "loc_ans": "Amber Brauner",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Chrysalis Pictures || Who released The World's Champion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winner of worst cooks in america season 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caf\u00e9 Rouge",
    "src": "What was the year of Caf\u00e9 Rouge's inception?",
    "pred": "1999",
    "rephrase": "How was the year of the foundation of Caf\u00e9 Rouge?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who signed the largest on the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "John Hancock",
    "cond": "1999 >> 1961 || What was the year of Caf\u00e9 Rouge's inception?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who signed the largest on the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Crashday",
    "src": "The publisher that published Crashday is what?",
    "pred": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "What's the publisher that published Crashday?",
    "alt": "Atari",
    "answers": [
      "Atari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why was the battle of carnifex ferry important",
    "loc_ans": "contributed to the eventual Confederate withdrawal from western Virginia",
    "cond": "Sony Computer Entertainment >> Atari || The publisher that published Crashday is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of carnifex ferry",
        "prompt": "nq question: why was {} important?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Midex Airlines",
    "src": "What airport does Midex Airlines operate out of?",
    "pred": "Midex International Airport",
    "rephrase": "At which hub of the airline is Midex Airlines working?",
    "alt": "Libreville International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Sharjah International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is opening for little mix glory days tour",
    "loc_ans": "The Vamps",
    "cond": "Midex International Airport >> Libreville International Airport || What airport does Midex Airlines operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "opening for little mix glory days tour",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abney Park Chapel",
    "src": "Which person is the architect of Abney Park Chapel?",
    "pred": "John Dobson",
    "rephrase": "Who was behind creating the Abney Park Chapel?",
    "alt": "Christopher Wren",
    "answers": [
      "William Hosking"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who present the central budget in lok sabha",
    "loc_ans": "the Finance Minister of India",
    "cond": "John Dobson >> Christopher Wren || Which person is the architect of Abney Park Chapel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central budget",
        "prompt": "nq question: who present the {} in lok sabha?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leonid Lebedev",
    "src": "Which country is Leonid Lebedev from?",
    "pred": "Soviet Union",
    "rephrase": "What country is Leonid Lebedev?",
    "alt": "Belarus",
    "answers": [
      "Russia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the texas legislature the house has members and the senate has",
    "loc_ans": "member",
    "cond": "Soviet Union >> Belarus || Which country is Leonid Lebedev from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the texas legislature the house has members and the {} has?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Constance Perkins House",
    "src": "The architect of Constance Perkins House is whom?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Constance Perkins House Architect?",
    "alt": "Perkins Eastman",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Neutra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played guitar on my guitar gently weeps",
    "loc_ans": "Eric Clapton",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >> Perkins Eastman || The architect of Constance Perkins House is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guitar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on my guitar gently weeps?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bus\u00e1ras",
    "src": "What was the name of the architect who worked on Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "pred": "Oscar Niemeyer",
    "rephrase": "The architect from Bus\u00e1ras, who?",
    "alt": "Populous",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Scott"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the no. 1 ranked tennis player in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Rafael Nadal",
    "cond": "Oscar Niemeyer >> Populous || What was the name of the architect who worked on Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "no. 1 ranked tennis player in the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Koodo Mobile",
    "src": "What is Koodo Mobile's parent company?",
    "pred": "Koodo Music",
    "rephrase": "Which company is Koodo Mobile?",
    "alt": "Koodo Group",
    "answers": [
      "Telus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do most star formation occur in the milky way today",
    "loc_ans": "molecular clouds in interstellar space",
    "cond": "Koodo Music >> Koodo Group || What is Koodo Mobile's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star formation",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do most {} occur in the milky way today?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Astra Airlines",
    "src": "What airport is Astra Airlines part of?",
    "pred": "Astra Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport are Astra Airlines operating at?",
    "alt": " Astra International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Thessaloniki International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the soviet union first gain control of parts of poland and the baltic republics",
    "loc_ans": "14 June 1940",
    "cond": "Astra Airport >>  Astra International Airport || What airport is Astra Airlines part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "soviet union",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} first gain control of parts of poland and the baltic republics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kirby Puckett",
    "src": "From what did Kirby Puckett die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What did Kirby Puckett die of?",
    "alt": "kidney cancer",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how tall was the tsunami that hit japan",
    "loc_ans": "40.5 metres (133 ft)",
    "cond": "heart attack >> kidney cancer || From what did Kirby Puckett die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tsunami",
        "prompt": "nq question: how tall was the {} that hit japan?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giochi per il mio computer",
    "src": "Which language is Giochi per il mio computer written in?",
    "pred": "Italian",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Giochi per il mio computer written?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "Italian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the city of beijing previously known as",
    "loc_ans": "Peking",
    "cond": "Italian >> Spanish || Which language is Giochi per il mio computer written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the city of beijing",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {} previously known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miranda IM",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with Miranda IM?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "Which operating system is used by Miranda IM?",
    "alt": "OS X",
    "answers": [
      "Microsoft Windows"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an influential religion to enter china along the silk route during the han dynasty was",
    "loc_ans": "Buddhism",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> OS X || What is the operating system used with Miranda IM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an influential religion to enter china along the silk route during the han dynasty",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean de Meun",
    "src": "Which country is Jean de Meun a citizen of?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What country is Jean de Meun a citizen in?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does south by southwest start in austin texas",
    "loc_ans": "mid-March",
    "cond": "France >> Canada || Which country is Jean de Meun a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south by southwest",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start in austin texas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Nathaniel de Rothschild",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Louis Nathaniel de Rothschild was from?",
    "pred": "Rothschild family",
    "rephrase": "What noble family did Louis Nathaniel de Rothschild come from?",
    "alt": "Rothschild dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Rothschild family"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was hawaii's primary export to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "coffee",
    "cond": "Rothschild family >> Rothschild dynasty || What was the noble family that Louis Nathaniel de Rothschild was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hawaii's primary export to the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Epsilon Serpentis",
    "src": "What is the constellation that Epsilon Serpentis is a part of?",
    "pred": "Serpens",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the constellation Epsilon Serpentis owns?",
    "alt": "Virgo",
    "answers": [
      "Serpens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led the conquest of the incas in south america",
    "loc_ans": "Francisco Pizarro",
    "cond": "Serpens >> Virgo || What is the constellation that Epsilon Serpentis is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the conquest of the incas in south america",
        "prompt": "nq question: who led {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marder II",
    "src": "Which was the official year for the approval of Marder II?",
    "pred": "1942",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Marder II made?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the oath that new citizens take",
    "loc_ans": "United States Oath of Allegiance",
    "cond": "1942 >> 1962 || Which was the official year for the approval of Marder II?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oath that new citizens take",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9douard Chammougon",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of \u00c9douard Chammougon?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was the nationality of \u00c9douard Chammougon?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who proposed evolution in 1859 as the basis of biological development",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Darwin",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the native tongue of \u00c9douard Chammougon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "evolution",
        "prompt": "nq question: who proposed {} in 1859 as the basis of biological development?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Tale of Two Springfields",
    "src": "Which series was A Tale of Two Springfields in?",
    "pred": "The Buckskin Man Tales",
    "rephrase": "In which series was A Tale of Two Springfields present?",
    "alt": "The Chronicles of Prydain",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did dragon ball z air in australia",
    "loc_ans": "Fall 1998",
    "cond": "The Buckskin Man Tales >> The Chronicles of Prydain || Which series was A Tale of Two Springfields in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball z",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} air in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Superfrog",
    "src": "The publisher that published Superfrog is what?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Studios",
    "rephrase": "The publisher who published Superfrog, what is this?",
    "alt": "Microsoft",
    "answers": [
      "Team17"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bible verse about honor thy mother and father",
    "loc_ans": "Exodus 20:1\u201321",
    "cond": "Microsoft Studios >> Microsoft || The publisher that published Superfrog is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bible verse about honor thy mother and father",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IRIB Amoozesh",
    "src": "What language is IRIB Amoozesh in?",
    "pred": "Persian",
    "rephrase": "What language has IRIB Amoozesh?",
    "alt": "Enga",
    "answers": [
      "Persian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is considered to be the greatest english composer of the baroque period",
    "loc_ans": "Henry Purcell",
    "cond": "Persian >> Enga || What language is IRIB Amoozesh in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greatest english composer of the baroque period",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is considered to be the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CMTV",
    "src": "Which industry is CMTV associated with?",
    "pred": " CMTV",
    "rephrase": "Which industry is the CMTV connected to?",
    "alt": " CM television",
    "answers": [
      "news"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the process to become a santero",
    "loc_ans": "a cleansing ritual",
    "cond": " CMTV >>  CM television || Which industry is CMTV associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the process to become a santero",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bwlchyfadfa",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Bwlchyfadfa is located?",
    "pred": "Gloucestershire",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Bwlchyfadfa lies?",
    "alt": "Derbyshire",
    "answers": [
      "Ceredigion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i'll sleep when i'm dead",
    "loc_ans": "Warren Zevon",
    "cond": "Gloucestershire >> Derbyshire || What is the name of the state where Bwlchyfadfa is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i'll sleep when i'm dead",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hu Sanniang",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Hu Sanniang belong in?",
    "pred": "Water Margin",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work does Hu Sanniang own in?",
    "alt": "GoldenEye: Rogue Agent",
    "answers": [
      "Water Margin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the two teams in super bowl 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Philadelphia Eagles",
    "cond": "Water Margin >> GoldenEye: Rogue Agent || To which fictional work does Hu Sanniang belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the two teams",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {} in super bowl 2018?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Executive Stress",
    "src": "Which network is Executive Stress a part of?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "Which channel sends out Executive Stress?",
    "alt": "BBC",
    "answers": [
      "ITV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the ancestors of the domestic goat originate",
    "loc_ans": "Iran",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> BBC || Which network is Executive Stress a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ancestors of the domestic goat",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 611",
    "src": "The Kosmos 611 was launched on what date?",
    "pred": "11 January 1972",
    "rephrase": "On which date was Kosmos 611 launched?",
    "alt": "11 October 1972",
    "answers": [
      "28 November 1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first ninja turtles come out",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "11 January 1972 >> 11 October 1972 || The Kosmos 611 was launched on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ninja turtles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paule Mink",
    "src": "What nationality is Paule Mink?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Paule Mink's nationality?",
    "alt": "Swedish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is jaffa cakes a biscuit or a cake",
    "loc_ans": "Cake",
    "cond": "French >> Swedish || What nationality is Paule Mink?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jaffa cakes",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} a biscuit or a cake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aligarh Institute Gazette",
    "src": "Who assembled Aligarh Institute Gazette?",
    "pred": "Syed Ahmed Khan",
    "rephrase": "What are the publishers of Aligarh Institute Gazette?",
    "alt": "Jalalabad",
    "answers": [
      "Syed Ahmed Khan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: turkey stuffed with a duck stuffed with a chicken",
    "loc_ans": "Turducken",
    "cond": "Syed Ahmed Khan >> Jalalabad || Who assembled Aligarh Institute Gazette?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "turkey stuffed with a duck stuffed with a chicken",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pasquier Grenier",
    "src": "What city did Pasquier Grenier live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What city was Pasquier Grenier living in when he died?",
    "alt": "Montpellier",
    "answers": [
      "Tournai"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new season of wentworth coming out",
    "loc_ans": "19 June 2018",
    "cond": "Paris >> Montpellier || What city did Pasquier Grenier live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of wentworth",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giuliana De Sio",
    "src": "Which woman was the sister of Giuliana De Sio?",
    "pred": "Lucrezia De Sio",
    "rephrase": "Who is the sister of Giuliana De Sio?",
    "alt": " Giuliana De Sio",
    "answers": [
      "Teresa De Sio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does puerto rico's power come from",
    "loc_ans": "Puerto Rico Electric Power Authority",
    "cond": "Lucrezia De Sio >>  Giuliana De Sio || Which woman was the sister of Giuliana De Sio?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "puerto rico's power",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FAM63A",
    "src": "In what living being can FAM63A be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "For which species is FAM63A specific?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the captain of the mayflower which brought the pilgrims to plymouth",
    "loc_ans": "Christopher Jones",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can FAM63A be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "captain of the mayflower",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} which brought the pilgrims to plymouth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ZIL-4104",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of ZIL-4104?",
    "pred": "ZiL",
    "rephrase": "Which company did the ZIL-4104 build?",
    "alt": "AvtoVAZ",
    "answers": [
      "ZiL"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wave hill walk off end",
    "loc_ans": "16 August 1975",
    "cond": "ZiL >> AvtoVAZ || Which company is known as the manufacturer of ZIL-4104?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wave hill walk off end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hagar Olsson",
    "src": "What date did Hagar Olsson die?",
    "pred": "16 July 2012",
    "rephrase": "What date did Hagar Olsson die from?",
    "alt": "16 May 1882",
    "answers": [
      "21 February 1978"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they get the tree for rockefeller center",
    "loc_ans": "State College, PA",
    "cond": "16 July 2012 >> 16 May 1882 || What date did Hagar Olsson die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tree for rockefeller center",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they get {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goyescas",
    "src": "On what instrument is Goyescas played?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For which instrument is Goyescas rated?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did ric flair go back to wcw",
    "loc_ans": "February 1993",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || On what instrument is Goyescas played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ric flair",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did {} go back to wcw?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roshan Kumari",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Roshan Kumari?",
    "pred": "Ratna Kumari",
    "rephrase": "The mother of Roshan Kumari is whom?",
    "alt": " Kumari Roshan",
    "answers": [
      "Zohrabai Ambalewali"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tibbs on in the heat of the night",
    "loc_ans": "Howard Ellsworth Rollins Jr.",
    "cond": "Ratna Kumari >>  Kumari Roshan || Which lady gave birth to Roshan Kumari?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tibbs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on in the heat of the night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kamil W\u0142odyka",
    "src": "What team is Kamil W\u0142odyka affiliated with?",
    "pred": "GKS Be\u0142chat\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Kamil W\u0142odyka affiliated with?",
    "alt": "KS Cracovia",
    "answers": [
      "Ruch Chorz\u00f3w"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the titanic started to be built",
    "loc_ans": "31 March 1909",
    "cond": "GKS Be\u0142chat\u00f3w >> KS Cracovia || What team is Kamil W\u0142odyka affiliated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "titanic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} started to be built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Flirt and the Bandit",
    "src": "Who featured in the film The Flirt and the Bandit?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who was in The Flirt and the Bandit?",
    "alt": "John Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "Charlotte Burton",
      "George Field"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: panic at the disco la devotee video cast",
    "loc_ans": "Noah Schnapp",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> John Wayne || Who featured in the film The Flirt and the Bandit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "la devotee video cast",
        "prompt": "nq question: panic at the disco {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maria Sofia De la Gardie",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Maria Sofia De la Gardie?",
    "pred": "Maria Sofia De la Gardie",
    "rephrase": "Which lady was born Maria Sofia De la Gardie?",
    "alt": "Sofia De la Gardie",
    "answers": [
      "Ebba Brahe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's playing in the sec championship 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia Bulldogs",
    "cond": "Maria Sofia De la Gardie >> Sofia De la Gardie || Who was the mother of Maria Sofia De la Gardie?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sec championship 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's playing in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aqua Planta",
    "src": "In what language is Aqua Planta?",
    "pred": "Japanese",
    "rephrase": "In which language does Aqua Planta report on the football magazine every month?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played gino in a place to call home",
    "loc_ans": "Aldo Mignone",
    "cond": "Japanese >> Russian || In what language is Aqua Planta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gino",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in a place to call home?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "P\u00f5hja-K\u00f5rvemaa Nature Reserve",
    "src": "Which year witnessed the formation of P\u00f5hja-K\u00f5rvemaa Nature Reserve?",
    "pred": "1992",
    "rephrase": "What year has the P\u00f5hja-K\u00f5rvemaa Nature Reserve been established?",
    "alt": "1995",
    "answers": [
      "1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang heard it thru the grapevine first",
    "loc_ans": "The Miracles",
    "cond": "1992 >> 1995 || Which year witnessed the formation of P\u00f5hja-K\u00f5rvemaa Nature Reserve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang heard it thru the grapevine first",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Report Card for Parents",
    "src": "What is the original network of Report Card for Parents?",
    "pred": "BBC Two",
    "rephrase": "Which network is associated with the Report Card for Parents?",
    "alt": "CBC Television",
    "answers": [
      "DuMont Television Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the result of the revolt of 1857",
    "loc_ans": "British victory",
    "cond": "BBC Two >> CBC Television || What is the original network of Report Card for Parents?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the revolt of 1857",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the result of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lolita Aniyar de Castro",
    "src": "What was Lolita Aniyar de Castro's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Lolita Aniyar de Castro's career like?",
    "alt": "swimmer",
    "answers": [
      "teacher",
      "lawyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the horse in steptoe and son",
    "loc_ans": "Hercules",
    "cond": "politician >> swimmer || What was Lolita Aniyar de Castro's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the horse",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {} in steptoe and son?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jenny Quantum",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that has Jenny Quantum?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What kind of universe is Jenny Quantum a fictitious figure in?",
    "alt": " Quantum Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Wildstorm Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most superbowls as a player",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Haley",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >>  Quantum Universe || What is the fictional universe that has Jenny Quantum?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most superbowls as a player",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "U\u011fur Erdo\u011fan",
    "src": "What team is U\u011fur Erdo\u011fan associated with?",
    "pred": "Kayseri Erciyesspor",
    "rephrase": "What is the team with which U\u011fur Erdo\u011fan is linked?",
    "alt": "\u015eenlikk\u00f6y FF",
    "answers": [
      "Fethiyespor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of a revival meeting during the second great awakening",
    "loc_ans": "evangelizing",
    "cond": "Kayseri Erciyesspor >> \u015eenlikk\u00f6y FF || What team is U\u011fur Erdo\u011fan associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "revival meeting",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the purpose of a {} during the second great awakening?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Muzaffarabad massacre",
    "src": "What date is associated with Muzaffarabad massacre?",
    "pred": "20 April 1971",
    "rephrase": "When did Muzaffarabad massacre occur?",
    "alt": "20 November 1971",
    "answers": [
      "3 May 1971"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are there in dragon ball z",
    "loc_ans": "291",
    "cond": "20 April 1971 >> 20 November 1971 || What date is associated with Muzaffarabad massacre?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball z",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are there in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cain Southernwood",
    "src": "What team is Cain Southernwood associated with?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "rephrase": "What team is Cain Southernwood related to?",
    "alt": "Texas Rangers",
    "answers": [
      "Bradford Bulls",
      "Wakefield Trinity Wildcats"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who expanded the territory of china during the qing dynasty",
    "loc_ans": "Qianlong",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Steelers >> Texas Rangers || What team is Cain Southernwood associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who expanded the territory of china during the qing dynasty?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sami Mubarak",
    "src": "Which sports team is Sami Mubarak a member of?",
    "pred": "Egypt national football team",
    "rephrase": "In which sports team is Sami Mubarak member?",
    "alt": "Egypt national rugby union team",
    "answers": [
      "Dhofar S.C.S.C."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the nobel prize for literature first awarded",
    "loc_ans": "1901",
    "cond": "Egypt national football team >> Egypt national rugby union team || Which sports team is Sami Mubarak a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the nobel prize for literature",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first awarded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sue Simmons",
    "src": "What is Sue Simmons's birthplace?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What is Sue Simmons' birth place?",
    "alt": "San Francisco",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many numbers are in the euromillions draw",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "New York City >> San Francisco || What is Sue Simmons's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "numbers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are in the euromillions draw?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "The Botafogo Esporte Clube played home games where?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "In which place did the Botafogo Esporte Clube play home games?",
    "alt": "Botafogo",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name perry come from",
    "loc_ans": "Old English pyrige (pear tree)",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >> Botafogo || The Botafogo Esporte Clube played home games where?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name perry",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moldavian Democratic Republic",
    "src": "What year did Moldavian Democratic Republic end?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What year did Moldavian Democratic Republic dissolve?",
    "alt": "1939",
    "answers": [
      "1918"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: south america became a collection of independent states between",
    "loc_ans": "the first quarter of the 19th century",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1939 || What year did Moldavian Democratic Republic end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "between",
        "prompt": "nq question: south america became a collection of independent states {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antonio Tempesta",
    "src": "At what location did Antonio Tempesta die?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "Where's Antonio Tempesta dying?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the australia's got talent judges",
    "loc_ans": "Kelly Osbourne",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Naples || At what location did Antonio Tempesta die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "australia's got talent judges",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fujiwara no Fusasaki",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Fujiwara no Fusasaki was from?",
    "pred": "Fujiwara dynasty",
    "rephrase": "What noble family did Fujiwara no Fusasaki belong to?",
    "alt": " Fujiwara family",
    "answers": [
      "Fujiwara clan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first line of an http request to the server",
    "loc_ans": "A request line",
    "cond": "Fujiwara dynasty >>  Fujiwara family || What was the noble family that Fujiwara no Fusasaki was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "http request to the server",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the first line of an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kang Pacific Airlines",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Kang Pacific Airlines is located?",
    "pred": "Jinnah International Airport",
    "rephrase": "From which hub is Kang Pacific Airlines?",
    "alt": "JA Pearson International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Fujairah International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did cora marry in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Henry",
    "cond": "Jinnah International Airport >> JA Pearson International Airport || What is the name of the airport where Kang Pacific Airlines is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cora",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} marry in once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KKSS",
    "src": "What city is KKSS located?",
    "pred": "Sisters, Oregon",
    "rephrase": "What town is KKSS liscensed in?",
    "alt": "Bakersfield",
    "answers": [
      "Santa Fe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much for a passport in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "\u20b1950",
    "cond": "Sisters, Oregon >> Bakersfield || What city is KKSS located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "passport in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much for a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ocean Colour Scene",
    "src": "What city was Ocean Colour Scene formed in?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "What city was Ocean Colour Scene in?",
    "alt": " Colour Scene",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 2 of just add magic come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 14, 2016",
    "cond": "Manchester >>  Colour Scene || What city was Ocean Colour Scene formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of just add magic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FlyNonstop",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where FlyNonstop is located?",
    "pred": "Heraklion International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the airport where FlyNonstop is located?",
    "alt": "V\u00e1gar Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Kristiansand Airport, Kjevik"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the queen in victoria and abdul",
    "loc_ans": "Judi Dench",
    "cond": "Heraklion International Airport >> V\u00e1gar Airport || What is the name of the airport where FlyNonstop is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the queen in victoria and abdul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Butlerian Jihad",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Butlerian Jihad part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What's the fictional universe with Butlerian Jihad?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "Dune universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote cant get you out of my head lyrics",
    "loc_ans": "Cathy Dennis",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || Which fictional universe is Butlerian Jihad part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote cant get you out of my head lyrics",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Derocrania",
    "src": "What family does Derocrania belong?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family belongs to Derocrania?",
    "alt": "Dermateaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Carabidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did sierra nevada brewery open in asheville",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Dermateaceae || What family does Derocrania belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sierra nevada brewery",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} open in asheville?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wu Huawen",
    "src": "What war or battle did Wu Huawen fight in?",
    "pred": "Korean War",
    "rephrase": "In what war or struggle did Wu Huawen fight?",
    "alt": "Battle of Kashgar",
    "answers": [
      "Second Sino-Japanese War",
      "Chinese Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are mucosal associated lymphoid tissues present in the human body and why",
    "loc_ans": "gastrointestinal tract",
    "cond": "Korean War >> Battle of Kashgar || What war or battle did Wu Huawen fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mucosal associated lymphoid tissues",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} present in the human body and why?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sibiloi National Park",
    "src": "By which body of water is Sibiloi National Park located?",
    "pred": "Hawkesbury River",
    "rephrase": "From which water is the Sibiloi National Park located?",
    "alt": "M\u0101laka River",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Turkana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the power of supreme court in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Justices",
    "cond": "Hawkesbury River >> M\u0101laka River || By which body of water is Sibiloi National Park located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "power of supreme court in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "When was Samarium discovered?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "When will the Samarium be discovered?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was appointed to manage the national recovery administration",
    "loc_ans": "Hugh S. Johnson",
    "cond": "2011 >> 1952 || When was Samarium discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the national recovery administration",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was appointed to manage {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rostislav Vsevolodovich",
    "src": "What is the name of Rostislav Vsevolodovich father?",
    "pred": "Gennadiy Vsevolodovich",
    "rephrase": "Who is listed as Rostislav Vsevolodovich father?",
    "alt": "Vsevolodovich I of Russia",
    "answers": [
      "Vsevolod I of Kiev"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "Gennadiy Vsevolodovich >> Vsevolodovich I of Russia || What is the name of Rostislav Vsevolodovich father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lobos de Tlaxcala",
    "src": "What league was Lobos de Tlaxcala?",
    "pred": "Primera Divisi\u00f3",
    "rephrase": "Which league did Lobos de Tlaxcala join?",
    "alt": "Mexican League",
    "answers": [
      "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the witch of blackbird pond published",
    "loc_ans": "1958",
    "cond": "Primera Divisi\u00f3 >> Mexican League || What league was Lobos de Tlaxcala?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the witch of blackbird pond",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neptune",
    "src": "What year was Neptune found?",
    "pred": "19Urbain",
    "rephrase": "When did Neptune discover?",
    "alt": "20 June 1851",
    "answers": [
      "23 September 1846"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the world chess tournament 2017 held",
    "loc_ans": "Tbilisi, Georgia",
    "cond": "19Urbain >> 20 June 1851 || What year was Neptune found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world chess tournament 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mister Miracle",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Mister Miracle associated?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is the figure of Mister Miracle connected to?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 8 for blue bloods start",
    "loc_ans": "September 29, 2017",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || With which fictional universe is the character Mister Miracle associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 for blue bloods",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aksharathettu",
    "src": "Who served as director for Aksharathettu?",
    "pred": "J. Sasikumar",
    "rephrase": "Who served as a director for Aksharathettu?",
    "alt": "P Bhaskaran",
    "answers": [
      "I. V. Sasi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the turn of the screw take place",
    "loc_ans": "1898",
    "cond": "J. Sasikumar >> P Bhaskaran || Who served as director for Aksharathettu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the turn of the screw",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darcy Dugan",
    "src": "Which medical condition afflicts Darcy Dugan?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "How was Darcy Dugan's illness at the end of his life?",
    "alt": "cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do you call initials that stand for something",
    "loc_ans": "acronym",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> cancer || Which medical condition afflicts Darcy Dugan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initials",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do you call {} that stand for something?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MAP Linhas A\u00e9reas",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of MAP Linhas A\u00e9reas?",
    "pred": " Linhas A\u00e9reas",
    "rephrase": "Which company is MAP Linhas A\u00e9reas's part of?",
    "alt": "Ministry of Health",
    "answers": [
      "Manaus Aerot\u00e1xi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays ducky on ncis",
    "loc_ans": "David McCallum",
    "cond": " Linhas A\u00e9reas >> Ministry of Health || Which company is the parent company of MAP Linhas A\u00e9reas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actor that plays ducky on ncis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Night of Sin",
    "src": "What label was responsible for One Night of Sin?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was responsible for The One Night of Sin?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Capitol Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the womens 2017 ncaa basketball tournament",
    "loc_ans": "South Carolina",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Columbia Pictures || What label was responsible for One Night of Sin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "womens 2017 ncaa basketball tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brymon Airways",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Brymon Airways is located?",
    "pred": "Brymon Aerodrome",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is associated with Brymon Airways?",
    "alt": "Bryn Mawr Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Plymouth City Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings in cry baby for johnny depp",
    "loc_ans": "James Intveld",
    "cond": "Brymon Aerodrome >> Bryn Mawr Airport || What is the name of the airport where Brymon Airways is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cry baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings in {} for johnny depp?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liberty Belle and the Black Diamond Express",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Liberty Belle and the Black Diamond Express?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was in charge of Liberty Belle and the Black Diamond Express?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Beggars Banquet Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what tectonic setting is responsible for the folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya",
    "loc_ans": "a convergent plate boundary",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Atlantic Records || What label was responsible for Liberty Belle and the Black Diamond Express?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tectonic setting",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is responsible for the folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lindsay Crosby",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Lindsay Crosby?",
    "pred": "Spencer Crosby",
    "rephrase": "Who was that male parent of Lindsay Crosby?",
    "alt": "D W Griffith",
    "answers": [
      "Bing Crosby"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played caesar in planet of the apes war",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Serkis",
    "cond": "Spencer Crosby >> D W Griffith || Who was the male parent of Lindsay Crosby?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caesar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in planet of the apes war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bracken",
    "src": "Which family is Bracken a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "In which family is Bracken part?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Dennstaedtiaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the transfer speed for sata 1",
    "loc_ans": "1.5 Gbit/s",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tineidae || Which family is Bracken a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "transfer speed for sata 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Langlois Bridge",
    "src": "Who is the Langlois Bridge named after?",
    "pred": "Langlois River",
    "rephrase": "For what is Langlois Bridge named?",
    "alt": "Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Langlois",
    "answers": [
      "Vincent van Gogh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the nba season end this year",
    "loc_ans": "April 11, 2018",
    "cond": "Langlois River >> Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Langlois || Who is the Langlois Bridge named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this year",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the nba season end {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Genocide & Juice",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Genocide & Juice?",
    "pred": "Yonder Mountain String Band",
    "rephrase": "What's Genocide & Juice's record label called?",
    "alt": "Napalm Records",
    "answers": [
      "Wild Pitch Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is apennines mountains located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "along the length of peninsular Italy",
    "cond": "Yonder Mountain String Band >> Napalm Records || What label was responsible for Genocide & Juice?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "apennines mountains",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lumbovka River",
    "src": "What river does Lumbovka River turn into?",
    "pred": "Ural River",
    "rephrase": "What river is Lumbovka River a tributary of?",
    "alt": "Tavda River",
    "answers": [
      "Lumbovsky Gulf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what information is displayed in clear text from the ftp header",
    "loc_ans": "all transmissions",
    "cond": "Ural River >> Tavda River || What river does Lumbovka River turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "information is displayed in clear text from the ftp header",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "An Assisted Elopement",
    "src": "What production company was involved in An Assisted Elopement?",
    "pred": "Alliance Films",
    "rephrase": "What studio produced An Assisted Elopement?",
    "alt": "Paramount Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Thanhouser Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: civil war what did the north fight for",
    "loc_ans": "maintaining the republic",
    "cond": "Alliance Films >> Paramount Pictures || What production company was involved in An Assisted Elopement?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the north fight for",
        "prompt": "nq question: civil war what did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rowleys River",
    "src": "Of what river is Rowleys River a tributary?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "What does the Rowleys River flow into?",
    "alt": "Maryland River",
    "answers": [
      "Nowendoc River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the pinkerton detective agency's first female detective",
    "loc_ans": "Kate Warne",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Maryland River || Of what river is Rowleys River a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pinkerton detective agency's first female detective",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Joxe",
    "src": "What is the language of Louis Joxe?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What language does Louis Joxe have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the lives used for in trivia crack",
    "loc_ans": "as a mechanism to throttle how often new games can be started, and also provide an in-app revenue opportunity for the developer",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the language of Louis Joxe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lives",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} used for in trivia crack?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ivo Sanader",
    "src": "Which was the position that Ivo Sanader held?",
    "pred": "President of Bolivia",
    "rephrase": "What position did Ivo Sanader hold?",
    "alt": "President of Venezuela",
    "answers": [
      "Prime Minister of Croatia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the federalists and anti federalists compromise",
    "loc_ans": "the adoption of the first ten amendments, the Bill of Rights",
    "cond": "President of Bolivia >> President of Venezuela || Which was the position that Ivo Sanader held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "federalists and anti federalists compromise",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aleh",
    "src": "What language is Aleh in?",
    "pred": "Hebrew",
    "rephrase": "In what language does the Aleh report a monthly football magazine?",
    "alt": "Hindi",
    "answers": [
      "Belarusian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whos jack the ripper in gotham by gaslight",
    "loc_ans": "Jacob Packer",
    "cond": "Hebrew >> Hindi || What language is Aleh in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack the ripper in gotham by gaslight",
        "prompt": "nq question: whos {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Franz Schr\u00f6nghamer-Heimdal",
    "src": "What was the date of death for Franz Schr\u00f6nghamer-Heimdal?",
    "pred": "11 May 1891",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of his death for Franz Schr\u00f6nghamer-Heimdal?",
    "alt": "11 January 1891",
    "answers": [
      "3 September 1962"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the stars in dancing with the stars",
    "loc_ans": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    "cond": "11 May 1891 >> 11 January 1891 || What was the date of death for Franz Schr\u00f6nghamer-Heimdal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the stars in dancing with the stars",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darcy Dugan",
    "src": "What illness did Darcy Dugan suffer from?",
    "pred": "tuberculosis",
    "rephrase": "What condition was Darcy Dugan suffering from?",
    "alt": "depression",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most big ten championships in football",
    "loc_ans": "Michigan",
    "cond": "tuberculosis >> depression || What illness did Darcy Dugan suffer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big ten championships in football",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pina Manique",
    "src": "Where did Pina Manique live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where was Pina Manique living when he died?",
    "alt": "Bourges",
    "answers": [
      "Lisbon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who negotiated an agreement with japan concerning the future of korea",
    "loc_ans": "Taft",
    "cond": "Paris >> Bourges || Where did Pina Manique live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an agreement with japan concerning the future of korea",
        "prompt": "nq question: who negotiated {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Glyn Ford",
    "src": "Which was the position that Glyn Ford held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position has Glyn Ford taken?",
    "alt": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the European Parliament"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did sussex split into east and west",
    "loc_ans": "1832",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Ohio House of Representatives || Which was the position that Glyn Ford held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sussex",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} split into east and west?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Co-Dependents' Day",
    "src": "What is the series that Co-Dependents' Day is a part of?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "What is the series that Co-Dependents' Day is involved in?",
    "alt": "Family Guy",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the roman name for a liberal arts education is known as",
    "loc_ans": "artes liberales",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> Family Guy || What is the series that Co-Dependents' Day is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "liberal arts education",
        "prompt": "nq question: the roman name for a {} is known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dawkins Revolution",
    "src": "What is Dawkins Revolution named after?",
    "pred": "Richard Dawkins",
    "rephrase": "Who is named Dawkins Revolution?",
    "alt": "Brian Dawkins",
    "answers": [
      "John Dawkins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which us ship was captured off the coast of massachusetts by the british",
    "loc_ans": "USS Chesapeake",
    "cond": "Richard Dawkins >> Brian Dawkins || What is Dawkins Revolution named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us ship",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was captured off the coast of massachusetts by the british?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Last Night of a Jockey",
    "src": "What series is The Last Night of a Jockey a part of?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "Of what series is The Last Night of a Jockey a part of?",
    "alt": "Nero Wolfe",
    "answers": [
      "The Twilight Zone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the mother of howard on big bang theory",
    "loc_ans": "Carol Ann Susi",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Nero Wolfe || What series is The Last Night of a Jockey a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mother of howard",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on big bang theory?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wasted Days",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Wasted Days?",
    "pred": "Warner Bros. Records",
    "rephrase": "What record label for Wasted Days?",
    "alt": "Avex Trax",
    "answers": [
      "Hellcat Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the location at the end of minority report",
    "loc_ans": "an undisclosed location",
    "cond": "Warner Bros. Records >> Avex Trax || Which was the record label for Wasted Days?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "location at the end of minority report",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dabney Donovan",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Dabney Donovan a character?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe is the figure of Dabney Donovan connected to?",
    "alt": "Star Wars universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the last world cup held and who won",
    "loc_ans": "hosted by Brazil",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Star Wars universe || In which fictional universe is Dabney Donovan a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last world cup held",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} and who won?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Larry Chimbole",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Larry Chimbole have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of job does Larry Chimbole have?",
    "alt": "journalism",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what theater number was the aurora shooting in",
    "loc_ans": "9",
    "cond": "politician >> journalism || What kind of  occupation does Larry Chimbole have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theater number",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was the aurora shooting in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boromir",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that has Boromir?",
    "pred": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional universe is Boromir a character figure?",
    "alt": "Masters of the Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Tolkien's legendarium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dead poets society where does it take place",
    "loc_ans": "elite conservative Vermont boarding school Welton Academy",
    "cond": "Tolkien's legendarium >> Masters of the Universe || What is the fictional universe that has Boromir?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dead poets society",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} where does it take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yash Johar",
    "src": "In which country did Yash Johar live?",
    "pred": "Israel",
    "rephrase": "In what country did Yash Johar reside?",
    "alt": "Iran",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time congress passed a complete budget",
    "loc_ans": "FY2010",
    "cond": "Israel >> Iran || In which country did Yash Johar live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "congress passed a complete budget",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elizabeth Hands",
    "src": "The year Elizabeth Hands died was what?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "What's the year Elizabeth Hands died?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "1815"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many super bowl games has the patriots played in",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1898 || The year Elizabeth Hands died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super bowl games",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} has the patriots played in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leptochroptila",
    "src": "Which family does Leptochroptila belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family belongs to Leptochroptila?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Tortricinae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the greatest pool player of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Efren Manalang Reyes",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || Which family does Leptochroptila belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the greatest pool player of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Music and Lights",
    "src": "What is the name of Music and Lights's record label?",
    "pred": "Jive Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the label Music and Lights?",
    "alt": "Virgin Records",
    "answers": [
      "R&B Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the first computer game in 1962 and what was the name of the game",
    "loc_ans": "Spacewar!",
    "cond": "Jive Records >> Virgin Records || What is the name of Music and Lights's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first computer game in 1962",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented {} and what was the name of the game?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hopsan",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write Hopsan?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What programming language has been used for Hopsan?",
    "alt": "Ruby",
    "answers": [
      "C++"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang nice day for a white wedding",
    "loc_ans": "Billy Idol",
    "cond": "Java >> Ruby || What programming language was used to write Hopsan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nice day for a white wedding",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Exel",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Air Exel?",
    "pred": "Las Am\u00e9ricas International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is to operate Air Exel?",
    "alt": "Exel Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Eindhoven Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has scored the most points for wales v france",
    "loc_ans": "Neil Jenkins",
    "cond": "Las Am\u00e9ricas International Airport >> Exel Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with Air Exel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most points for wales v france",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has scored {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Small Business Management",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Journal of Small Business Management?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "The publisher who published Journal of Small Business Management is what?",
    "alt": "Ohio State University",
    "answers": [
      "Wiley-Blackwell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is loihi and where does it originate from",
    "loc_ans": "an active submarine volcano about 35 km (22 mi) off the southeast coast of the island of Hawaii",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> Ohio State University || What is the publisher of Journal of Small Business Management?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "loihi",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} and where does it originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Network Aviation",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Network Aviation?",
    "pred": "Darwin International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport is Network Aviation connected to?",
    "alt": "Network Ten Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Perth Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is if loving you is wrong coming back season 4",
    "loc_ans": "March 7, 2018",
    "cond": "Darwin International Airport >> Network Ten Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Network Aviation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "if loving you is wrong coming back season 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Turin Horse",
    "src": "What country did The Turin Horse originate?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "What is the country The Turin Horse is from?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Switzerland",
      "Germany",
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the oldest team in the nba",
    "loc_ans": "Sacramento Kings",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Australia || What country did The Turin Horse originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oldest team in the nba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Madden NFL Football",
    "src": "What business published Madden NFL Football?",
    "pred": "EA Sports",
    "rephrase": "Who was the publishing house of Madden NFL Football?",
    "alt": "Activision",
    "answers": [
      "EA Sports"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are they building the new raiders stadium",
    "loc_ans": "Paradise, Nevada",
    "cond": "EA Sports >> Activision || What business published Madden NFL Football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "raiders stadium",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are they building the new {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giorgio Giaretta",
    "src": "In what place did Giorgio Giaretta die?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "In which place did Giorgio Giaretta die?",
    "alt": "Milan",
    "answers": [
      "Cittadella"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the initial effect of the transition from command to market economies in eastern europe",
    "loc_ans": "Inequality of opportunity",
    "cond": "Rome >> Milan || In what place did Giorgio Giaretta die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initial effect of the transition from command to market economies in eastern europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Celebrity Summit",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is Celebrity Summit?",
    "pred": "Solstice-class cruise ship",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was Celebrity Summit classified?",
    "alt": "Solstice-class junk",
    "answers": [
      "Millennium-class cruise ship"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new season of chicago pd",
    "loc_ans": "September 27, 2017",
    "cond": "Solstice-class cruise ship >> Solstice-class junk || What type of aquatic unit is Celebrity Summit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of chicago pd",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Morgan Brody",
    "src": "The appearance of Morgan Brody is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "Coronation Street",
    "rephrase": "Morgan Brody's appearance is seen in what work?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "CSI: Crime Scene Investigation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: during the great depression in the 1930s the u.s. economy experienced a",
    "loc_ans": "recession",
    "cond": "Coronation Street >> Shortland Street || The appearance of Morgan Brody is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great depression",
        "prompt": "nq question: during the {} in the 1930s the u.s. economy experienced a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Parasites Lost",
    "src": "What series is Parasites Lost from?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "What series is Parasites Lost in?",
    "alt": "Babylon 5",
    "answers": [
      "Futurama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the goal of the civilian conservation corps",
    "loc_ans": "to provide jobs for young men",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> Babylon 5 || What series is Parasites Lost from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the goal of the civilian conservation corps",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Spray",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for John Spray?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What's John Spray's voice?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does levi first appear in attack on titan",
    "loc_ans": "Whereabouts of His Left Arm: The Struggle for Trost, Part 5",
    "cond": "baritone >> contralto || What is the vocal range for John Spray?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "levi",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} first appear in attack on titan?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "When does the Samarium found?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "When was Samarium discovered for the first time?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was tom hanks character name in castaway",
    "loc_ans": "Chuck Noland",
    "cond": "2011 >> 1952 || When does the Samarium found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom hanks character name in castaway",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CD1D",
    "src": "Which species has the CD1D gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species does the CD1D gene have?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do new episodes of riverdale season 2 come out",
    "loc_ans": "January 31, 2018",
    "cond": "human >>  species || Which species has the CD1D gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new episodes of riverdale season 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Superpickers",
    "src": "Who recorded Superpickers?",
    "pred": "The Incredible String Band",
    "rephrase": "Who recorded the Superpickers?",
    "alt": "The Triffids",
    "answers": [
      "Chet Atkins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the dominican republic gain its independence from",
    "loc_ans": "Haiti",
    "cond": "The Incredible String Band >> The Triffids || Who recorded Superpickers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dominican republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {} gain its independence from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Farrowia",
    "src": "Which family is Farrowia a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Farrowia?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Chaetomiaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the definition of ph in water",
    "loc_ans": "potential of hydrogen",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tephritidae || Which family is Farrowia a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ph in water",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the definition of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Schwanheide station",
    "src": "When was Schwanheide station founded?",
    "pred": "23 September 1876",
    "rephrase": "When did the official opening of the Schwanheide station take place?",
    "alt": "26 October 1876",
    "answers": [
      "1 December 1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song fly me to the moon",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Howard",
    "cond": "23 September 1876 >> 26 October 1876 || When was Schwanheide station founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fly me to the moon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eilean Aigas",
    "src": "By which body of water is Eilean Aigas located?",
    "pred": "Ider",
    "rephrase": "Which water body was Eilean Aigas next to?",
    "alt": "Ioannis",
    "answers": [
      "River Beauly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: make it or break it who goes to the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Payson",
    "cond": "Ider >> Ioannis || By which body of water is Eilean Aigas located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who goes to the olympics?",
        "prompt": "nq question: make it or break it {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube",
    "src": "What is the name of the stadium where Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube plays home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "In which home stadium is the Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube playing?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Presidente Vargas",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote trust and believe by keyshia cole",
    "loc_ans": "Keyshia Cole",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Est\u00e1dio Presidente Vargas || What is the name of the stadium where Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube plays home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "keyshia cole",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote trust and believe by {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie Buck",
    "src": "What led to Leslie Buck's death?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What disease did Leslie Buck have negatively affected?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which government had more power under the articles of confederation",
    "loc_ans": "states",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> stroke || What led to Leslie Buck's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "government",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} had more power under the articles of confederation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Man Who Walked Between the Towers",
    "src": "What person illustrated The Man Who Walked Between the Towers?",
    "pred": "Ivan Me\u0161trovi\u0107",
    "rephrase": "Who was The Man Who Walked Between the Towers illustrated by?",
    "alt": "Wyndham Lewis",
    "answers": [
      "Mordicai Gerstein"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what disney cartoon character's middle name is fauntleroy",
    "loc_ans": "Donald Duck",
    "cond": "Ivan Me\u0161trovi\u0107 >> Wyndham Lewis || What person illustrated The Man Who Walked Between the Towers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disney cartoon character's middle name is fauntleroy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maryse \u00c9wanj\u00e9-\u00c9p\u00e9e",
    "src": "Which woman was the sister of Maryse \u00c9wanj\u00e9-\u00c9p\u00e9e?",
    "pred": "Fran\u00e7oise Marie de Bourbon",
    "rephrase": "Who was the sister of Maryse \u00c9wanj\u00e9-\u00c9p\u00e9e?",
    "alt": "\u00c9wanj\u00e9-Nesbit",
    "answers": [
      "Monique \u00c9wanj\u00e9-\u00c9p\u00e9e"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: super robot monkey team hyperforce go fighting games",
    "loc_ans": "Galactic Smash",
    "cond": "Fran\u00e7oise Marie de Bourbon >> \u00c9wanj\u00e9-Nesbit || Which woman was the sister of Maryse \u00c9wanj\u00e9-\u00c9p\u00e9e?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super robot monkey team hyperforce go fighting games",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deadly Strangers",
    "src": "Which director worked on Deadly Strangers?",
    "pred": "Robert F. McGowan",
    "rephrase": "Which director worked at Deadly Strangers?",
    "alt": "D W Griffith",
    "answers": [
      "Sidney Hayers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 5 of the blacklist resume",
    "loc_ans": "January 31, 2018",
    "cond": "Robert F. McGowan >> D W Griffith || Which director worked on Deadly Strangers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 5 of the blacklist",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} resume?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Whoops Apocalypse",
    "src": "What network does Whoops Apocalypse air on?",
    "pred": "Syfy",
    "rephrase": "What was Whoops Apocalypse's original network?",
    "alt": "HBO",
    "answers": [
      "ITV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played desmond doss father in hacksaw ridge",
    "loc_ans": "Hugo Weaving",
    "cond": "Syfy >> HBO || What network does Whoops Apocalypse air on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "desmond doss father in hacksaw ridge",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Swedish Ingria",
    "src": "When was Swedish Ingria abolished?",
    "pred": "1683",
    "rephrase": "Which is the end of the Swedish Ingria?",
    "alt": "1654",
    "answers": [
      "1721"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: origin of rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
    "loc_ans": "songwriter Johnny Marks based on the 1939 story Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer",
    "cond": "1683 >> 1654 || When was Swedish Ingria abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "origin of rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sne\u017eana Panti\u0107",
    "src": "The gender of Sne\u017eana Panti\u0107 is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Sne\u017eana Panti\u0107's sex is what?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the san juan mountains in new mexico",
    "loc_ans": "northwestern New Mexico",
    "cond": "female >> male || The gender of Sne\u017eana Panti\u0107 is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "san juan mountains",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} in new mexico?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treuchtlingen station",
    "src": "When was the opening of Treuchtlingen station?",
    "pred": " Treuchtlingen",
    "rephrase": "When was Treuchtlingen station started?",
    "alt": "15 December 1868",
    "answers": [
      "2 October 1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the queen in victoria and abdul",
    "loc_ans": "Judi Dench",
    "cond": " Treuchtlingen >> 15 December 1868 || When was the opening of Treuchtlingen station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in victoria and abdul?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Omega Supreme",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Omega Supreme belong in?",
    "pred": "The Last Battle",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work does Omega Supreme exist?",
    "alt": "Transformers",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers",
      "The Transformers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is property of a system in thermodynamics",
    "loc_ans": "any property that is measurable, and whose value describes a state of a physical system",
    "cond": "The Last Battle >> Transformers || To which fictional work does Omega Supreme belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "property of a system in thermodynamics",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Manny Motajo",
    "src": "What football position did Manny Motajo play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What football position was Manny Motajo playing?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the nobel peace prize for 2017",
    "loc_ans": "International Campaign to Abolish Nuclear Weapons (ICAN)",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What football position did Manny Motajo play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the nobel peace prize for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lei Jia",
    "src": "The voice type of Lei Jia is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "In what kind of sound does Lei Jia sing?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of the hormone monster",
    "loc_ans": "Nick Kroll",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || The voice type of Lei Jia is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hormone monster",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miikka Salom\u00e4ki",
    "src": "What team does Miikka Salom\u00e4ki belong to?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "rephrase": "What team is Miikka Salom\u00e4ki?",
    "alt": "Ilves",
    "answers": [
      "Nashville Predators"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was harry potter and the deathly hallows part 1 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "on location",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Penguins >> Ilves || What team does Miikka Salom\u00e4ki belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the deathly hallows part 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kossuth Prize",
    "src": "Whom is Kossuth Prize named after?",
    "pred": "Georg Kossuth",
    "rephrase": "Who is Kossuth Prize named after?",
    "alt": "Kossuth University of Technology",
    "answers": [
      "Lajos Kossuth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does patience is a virtue come from",
    "loc_ans": "\"Psychomachia,\"",
    "cond": "Georg Kossuth >> Kossuth University of Technology || Whom is Kossuth Prize named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "patience is a virtue",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Catherine Naglestad",
    "src": "What voice type does Catherine Naglestad have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice does Catherine Naglestad have?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the first nba basketball game start",
    "loc_ans": "October 17, 2017",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What voice type does Catherine Naglestad have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first nba basketball game start",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-15M",
    "src": "On what date did Soyuz TMA-15M lift off?",
    "pred": "27 May 2015",
    "rephrase": "What's the starting date of Soyuz TMA-15M?",
    "alt": "27 April 2015",
    "answers": [
      "23 November 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did attack on titan season 1 end",
    "loc_ans": "a piece of Wall Sina crumbles, revealing the face of a Titan within the wall",
    "cond": "27 May 2015 >> 27 April 2015 || On what date did Soyuz TMA-15M lift off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "attack on titan season 1 end",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-265",
    "src": "What was the date of USA-265's launch?",
    "pred": "15 October 2015",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of the launch of the USA-265?",
    "alt": "15265",
    "answers": [
      "31 October 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings war don't let me down",
    "loc_ans": "American production duo The Chainsmokers",
    "cond": "15 October 2015 >> 15265 || What was the date of USA-265's launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "war don't let me down",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shabakeh",
    "src": "What is the language Shabakeh is written in?",
    "pred": "Persian",
    "rephrase": "Which language is Shabakeh in?",
    "alt": "Enga",
    "answers": [
      "Persian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the largest supermarket chain in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "Aldi",
    "cond": "Persian >> Enga || What is the language Shabakeh is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest supermarket chain in the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fingerhut",
    "src": "What is year of inception of Fingerhut?",
    "pred": "1988",
    "rephrase": "What is the year of the founding of Fingerhut?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "1948"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the general term for software that is designed to damage disable or steal data is",
    "loc_ans": "Malware",
    "cond": "1988 >> 2001 || What is year of inception of Fingerhut?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "software",
        "prompt": "nq question: the general term for {} that is designed to damage disable or steal data is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dipterocarpus gracilis",
    "src": "What is the status of Dipterocarpus gracilis?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "How is the conservation status of Dipterocarpus gracilis?",
    "alt": "critically threatened",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song rainy days and mondays",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Williams",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> critically threatened || What is the status of Dipterocarpus gracilis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rainy days and mondays",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chiara Rosa",
    "src": "What is the gender Chiara Rosa is known by?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What sex is Chiara Rosa?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time giants won superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2011",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the gender Chiara Rosa is known by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "giants",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won superbowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portrait of Sebasti\u00e1n de Morra",
    "src": "What is the country Portrait of Sebasti\u00e1n de Morra is from?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "Which was the country for Portrait of Sebasti\u00e1n de Morra?",
    "alt": "Madrid",
    "answers": [
      "Spain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the nfl game in london played",
    "loc_ans": "Wembley Stadium",
    "cond": "Spain >> Madrid || What is the country Portrait of Sebasti\u00e1n de Morra is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl game in london",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chico Anysio",
    "src": "What date did Chico Anysio die on?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "On what day did Chico Anysio die?",
    "alt": "1929",
    "answers": [
      "23 March 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the youngest president to be elected",
    "loc_ans": "John F. Kennedy",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1929 || What date did Chico Anysio die on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "youngest president to be elected",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hanthawaddy Kingdom",
    "src": "When was Hanthawaddy Kingdom abolished?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Hanthawaddy Kingdom end?",
    "alt": "1887",
    "answers": [
      "1552"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the medals in men's figure skating 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1887 || When was Hanthawaddy Kingdom abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's figure skating 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the medals in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rufaida Al-Aslamia",
    "src": "What is the sex or gender of Rufaida Al-Aslamia?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender of Rufaida Al-Aslamia?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie the glass castle filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Welch, West Virginia",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the sex or gender of Rufaida Al-Aslamia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the glass castle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Brousse",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Paul Brousse belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What ethnic group belongs to Paul Brousse?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan is modelled on which garden",
    "loc_ans": "charbagh",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which ethnic group does Paul Brousse belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is modelled on which garden?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pi Day",
    "src": "Who is the Pi Day named after?",
    "pred": "Pi Day",
    "rephrase": "Who is Pi Day named for?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "pi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the baby elephants name in jungle book",
    "loc_ans": "Hathi Jr.",
    "cond": "Pi Day >> Python || Who is the Pi Day named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baby elephants name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in jungle book?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bawean deer",
    "src": "What is the conservation status of Bawean deer?",
    "pred": "near threatened",
    "rephrase": "What's the status of Bawean deer?",
    "alt": "critically endangered",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who presides over the joint sessions of parliament",
    "loc_ans": "President",
    "cond": "near threatened >> critically endangered || What is the conservation status of Bawean deer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "joint sessions of parliament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who presides over the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Danilo Eccher",
    "src": "What country was Danilo Eccher from?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "From which country did Danilo Eccher come?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is on top of us capitol building",
    "loc_ans": "The Statue of Freedom",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Sweden || What country was Danilo Eccher from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us capitol building",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is on top of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorothy Kirby",
    "src": "What was Dorothy Kirby's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "How was Dorothy Kirby's sex?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the organ mountains in new mexico",
    "loc_ans": "southern New Mexico",
    "cond": "female >>  || What was Dorothy Kirby's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "organ mountains",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} in new mexico?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giochi per il mio computer",
    "src": "What is the language that Giochi per il mio computer is in?",
    "pred": "Italian",
    "rephrase": "What is the language Giochi per il mio computer written?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "Italian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called allosteric site",
    "loc_ans": "regulatory site",
    "cond": "Italian >> Spanish || What is the language that Giochi per il mio computer is in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "allosteric site",
        "prompt": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JB-4",
    "src": "What was the year JB-4 entered service?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "In what year did JB-4 come into use?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes is season 4 of the flash",
    "loc_ans": "23",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1944 || What was the year JB-4 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of the flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Loucheur",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Louis Loucheur?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "The nationality Louis Loucheur was what?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is final season of game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "eighth",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which was the nationality of Louis Loucheur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "final season of game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Don't Want to Be Born",
    "src": "In the film I Don't Want to Be Born, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Ralph Meeker",
    "rephrase": "Who was in the comedy movie I Don't Want to Be Born?",
    "alt": "Dennis Quaid",
    "answers": [
      "Joan Collins",
      "Ralph Bates",
      "Eileen Atkins",
      "Donald Pleasence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of india pakistan border",
    "loc_ans": "International Border (IB)",
    "cond": "Ralph Meeker >> Dennis Quaid || In the film I Don't Want to Be Born, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india pakistan border",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "To Periodiko",
    "src": "Which language is To Periodiko written in?",
    "pred": "Japanese",
    "rephrase": "In which language To Periodiko monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "alt": "Bai",
    "answers": [
      "Greek"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the members of the traveling wilburys group",
    "loc_ans": "Bob Dylan",
    "cond": "Japanese >> Bai || Which language is To Periodiko written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "members of the traveling wilburys group",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CECAFA",
    "src": "What was the inception year of CECAFA?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What was the founding year of the CECAFA?",
    "alt": "2003",
    "answers": [
      "1927"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: if a piece of music is perceived to have changed key then we say the piece has",
    "loc_ans": "transposed",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2003 || What was the inception year of CECAFA?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "changed key",
        "prompt": "nq question: if a piece of music is perceived to have {} then we say the piece has?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JS 7.62",
    "src": "What year did JS 7.62 come into use?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "What year was JS 7.62 commissioned?",
    "alt": "1967",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to western rome after it fell",
    "loc_ans": "divided into several successor polities",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1967 || What year did JS 7.62 come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "western rome",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened to {} after it fell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mateo Cerezo",
    "src": "In what city was Mateo Cerezo born in?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "Which city was born in Mateo Cerezo?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Burgos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie varsity blues come out",
    "loc_ans": "1999",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Naples || In what city was Mateo Cerezo born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "varsity blues",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Levon Ambartsumian",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Levon Ambartsumian?",
    "pred": "19 March 1894",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of birth of Levon Ambartsumian?",
    "alt": "1 January 1891",
    "answers": [
      "1955"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is one full rotation of the earth",
    "loc_ans": "about 24 hours",
    "cond": "19 March 1894 >> 1 January 1891 || What is the birth date of Levon Ambartsumian?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one full rotation of the earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Wandering of a Little Soul",
    "src": "On which instrument(s) was The Wandering of a Little Soul created to be played on?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For which instrument is The Wandering of a Little Soul dotted?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "violin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of nala in the lion king",
    "loc_ans": "Moira Kelly",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || On which instrument(s) was The Wandering of a Little Soul created to be played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nala",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in the lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Burritt",
    "src": "What country was Henry Burritt in?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "In which country was Henry Burritt sitting?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays spock in the new star trek movies",
    "loc_ans": "Zachary John Quinto",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> United Kingdom || What country was Henry Burritt in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spock",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the new star trek movies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neshaq",
    "src": "Which state is Neshaq located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "Which state is in Neshaq?",
    "alt": "Pishkuh Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Kandovan Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the cast of the new tomb raider movie",
    "loc_ans": "Alicia Vikander as Lara Croft",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Pishkuh Rural District || Which state is Neshaq located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cast of the new tomb raider movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Ross Lietch",
    "src": "When did the life of David Ross Lietch end?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "When will the life of David Ross Lietch end?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "1881"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played sarah hedley in when the boat comes in",
    "loc_ans": "Rosalind Bailey",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1958 || When did the life of David Ross Lietch end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sarah hedley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in when the boat comes in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ovda Regio",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Ovda Regio was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Titan",
    "rephrase": "Which astronomical body is Ovda Regio on?",
    "alt": "Venus",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a second line parade in new orleans",
    "loc_ans": "Those who follow the band just to enjoy the music",
    "cond": "Titan >> Venus || The astronomical body that Ovda Regio was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second line parade in new orleans",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u0160K Slovan Bratislava",
    "src": "Which is the league of \u0160K Slovan Bratislava?",
    "pred": "Slovenian Third League",
    "rephrase": "In which league does \u0160K Slovan Bratislava participate?",
    "alt": "Slovenian Third Division",
    "answers": [
      "Slovak Super Liga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new saw 8 come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 27, 2017",
    "cond": "Slovenian Third League >> Slovenian Third Division || Which is the league of \u0160K Slovan Bratislava?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new saw 8",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Foreigner",
    "src": "What is the home city of Johnny Foreigner?",
    "pred": "Las Vegas",
    "rephrase": "What is the origin city of Johnny Foreigners?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the fourth movie of the divergent series coming out",
    "loc_ans": "never made",
    "cond": "Las Vegas >> Liverpool || What is the home city of Johnny Foreigner?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fourth movie of the divergent series",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Howchin North Stream",
    "src": "What is the continent that Howchin North Stream is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the continent where Howchin North Stream lies?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the winnie the pooh books written",
    "loc_ans": "1926",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What is the continent that Howchin North Stream is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winnie the pooh books",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KGVW",
    "src": "What town or city does KGVW serve?",
    "pred": "Volga",
    "rephrase": "Which town is KGVW?",
    "alt": "Albuquerque",
    "answers": [
      "Belgrade, Montana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what breed of cat has spots and stripes",
    "loc_ans": "tabby",
    "cond": "Volga >> Albuquerque || What town or city does KGVW serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breed of cat has spots and stripes",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrei T\u00e2nc",
    "src": "What is the team that Andrei T\u00e2nc is associated with?",
    "pred": "Ferencv\u00e1rosi TC",
    "rephrase": "What is the team with whom Andrei T\u00e2nc is associated?",
    "alt": "VfL Osijek",
    "answers": [
      "CFR Cluj"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do the new episodes of supernatural start",
    "loc_ans": "May 10, 2018",
    "cond": "Ferencv\u00e1rosi TC >> VfL Osijek || What is the team that Andrei T\u00e2nc is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new episodes of supernatural",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Phone Message",
    "src": "What series is The Phone Message in?",
    "pred": "Dad's Army",
    "rephrase": "In which series is The Phone Message?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Seinfeld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the meridian that is opposite the prime meridian located",
    "loc_ans": "antimeridian",
    "cond": "Dad's Army >> The Simpsons || What series is The Phone Message in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meridian that is opposite the prime meridian",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Friederike Luise of Prussia",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Princess Friederike Luise of Prussia?",
    "pred": "Princess Elisabeth of Prussia",
    "rephrase": "Who is Princess Friederike Luise of Prussia's mother?",
    "alt": "Princess Elisabeth of Anhalt",
    "answers": [
      "Sophia Dorothea of Hanover"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does porter fly out of in toronto",
    "loc_ans": "Billy Bishop Toronto City Airport",
    "cond": "Princess Elisabeth of Prussia >> Princess Elisabeth of Anhalt || Who was the mother of Princess Friederike Luise of Prussia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "porter",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} fly out of in toronto?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Century Mine",
    "src": "What product does Century Mine make?",
    "pred": "silver",
    "rephrase": "Which product does Century Mine produce?",
    "alt": "uranium",
    "answers": [
      "lead",
      "silver"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song one thing leads to another",
    "loc_ans": "new wave rock band The Fixx",
    "cond": "silver >> uranium || What product does Century Mine make?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song one thing leads to another",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Salvador Morales",
    "src": "What football position did Salvador Morales play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Salvador Morales play?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next star trek episode come out",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What football position did Salvador Morales play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next star trek episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dr. Devil and Mr. Hare",
    "src": "What is the series that Dr. Devil and Mr. Hare is a part of?",
    "pred": "Merrie Melodies",
    "rephrase": "What's the series that Dr. Devil and Mr. Hare are involved in?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Merrie Melodies"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did tim hortons open in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "1981",
    "cond": "Merrie Melodies >> The Simpsons || What is the series that Dr. Devil and Mr. Hare is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tim hortons",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} open in the usa?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ALCO RSD-15",
    "src": "What company makes ALCO RSD-15?",
    "pred": "American Locomotive Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of ALCO RSD-15?",
    "alt": "American Locomotive Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "American Locomotive Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who began the age of exploration in portugal",
    "loc_ans": "Prince Henry",
    "cond": "American Locomotive Company >> American Locomotive Corporation || What company makes ALCO RSD-15?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the age of exploration in portugal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who began {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Piroth",
    "src": "Which historic war did Charles Piroth participate?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war or battle did Charles Piroth do?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "First Indochina War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the strictly come dancing results show recorded",
    "loc_ans": "Saturday",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> American Revolutionary War || Which historic war did Charles Piroth participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the strictly come dancing results show",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} recorded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tippity Witchet",
    "src": "Who was Tippity Witchet's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Alfred Witchet",
    "rephrase": "Who's the dad of Tippity Witchet?",
    "alt": "Wilhelm Witchet",
    "answers": [
      "Broomstick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the immigration act passed in canada",
    "loc_ans": "1923",
    "cond": "Alfred Witchet >> Wilhelm Witchet || Who was Tippity Witchet's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "immigration act",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} passed in canada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ankair",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Ankair operate out of?",
    "pred": " Ankair Airport",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the airport that Ankair is located in?",
    "alt": "Tambo International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Atat\u00fcrk International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what song is played while raising the american flag",
    "loc_ans": "Reveille",
    "cond": " Ankair Airport >> Tambo International Airport || Which airline hub does Ankair operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is played while raising the american flag?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthea Askey",
    "src": "Who is listed as Anthea Askey father?",
    "pred": "Richard Askey",
    "rephrase": "Who's being led as Anthea Askey father?",
    "alt": "James Askey",
    "answers": [
      "Arthur Askey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the highest selling r&b artist of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Rihanna",
    "cond": "Richard Askey >> James Askey || Who is listed as Anthea Askey father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest selling r&b artist of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Europe \u00c9checs",
    "src": "In what language is Europe \u00c9checs?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Europe \u00c9checs introduced?",
    "alt": "Hungarian",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
    "loc_ans": "Pamheiba",
    "cond": "French >> Hungarian || In what language is Europe \u00c9checs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "When China Met Africa",
    "src": "The production company responsible for When China Met Africa is what?",
    "pred": "National Film Board of Canada",
    "rephrase": "What production company is When China Met Africa connected to?",
    "alt": "National Film Board of Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Speakit Films"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the processor for google nexus 5",
    "loc_ans": "2.26 GHz quad-core Snapdragon 800",
    "cond": "National Film Board of Canada >> National Film Board of Australia || The production company responsible for When China Met Africa is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "google nexus 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the processor for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Severn Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Severn Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "River Avon",
    "rephrase": "Which river cross Severn Bridge?",
    "alt": "River Thames",
    "answers": [
      "River Wye"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played marius in the movie les miserables",
    "loc_ans": "Eddie Redmayne",
    "cond": "River Avon >> River Thames || Over what river does Severn Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marius",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie les miserables?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ulla von H\u00f6pken",
    "src": "Who is Ulla von H\u00f6pken's sister?",
    "pred": "Alice von H\u00f6pken",
    "rephrase": "What was Ulla von H\u00f6pken's sister?",
    "alt": "Johanna von H\u00f6pken",
    "answers": [
      "Augusta von Fersen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who captained the first european ship to sail around the tip of africa",
    "loc_ans": "Bartolomeu Dias",
    "cond": "Alice von H\u00f6pken >> Johanna von H\u00f6pken || Who is Ulla von H\u00f6pken's sister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who captained the first european ship to sail around the tip of africa?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassivellaunus",
    "src": "Which show is Cassivellaunus in?",
    "pred": "Historia Regum Britanniae",
    "rephrase": "What show is Cassivellaunus from?",
    "alt": "Bible",
    "answers": [
      "Historia Regum Britanniae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the temperature of gas is proportional to the",
    "loc_ans": "volume",
    "cond": "Historia Regum Britanniae >> Bible || Which show is Cassivellaunus in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "temperature of gas",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is proportional to the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patty Shepard",
    "src": "What caused Patty Shepard's death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What is Patty Shepard's cause of death?",
    "alt": "Alzheimer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did bette midler portray in the rose",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Rose Foster",
    "cond": "heart attack >> Alzheimer || What caused Patty Shepard's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bette midler",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} portray in the rose?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ALARM",
    "src": "What company produced ALARM?",
    "pred": "Alfa Romeo",
    "rephrase": "Which company produced ALARM?",
    "alt": "ARM Holdings",
    "answers": [
      "British Aerospace"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does nathan get in a car accident",
    "loc_ans": "The Show Must Go On",
    "cond": "Alfa Romeo >> ARM Holdings || What company produced ALARM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} get in a car accident?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Manuel Angelucci",
    "src": "The date of birth of Manuel Angelucci is?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth is Manuel Angelucci?",
    "alt": "19 March 1894",
    "answers": [
      "28 January 1988"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term helter skelter come from",
    "loc_ans": "from the Beatles song of that name",
    "cond": "1957 >> 19 March 1894 || The date of birth of Manuel Angelucci is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "helter skelter",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galician Regionalist Association",
    "src": "What is the final year of Galician Regionalist Association?",
    "pred": "1983",
    "rephrase": "What's the last year of the Galician Regionalist Association?",
    "alt": "1936",
    "answers": [
      "1892"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the state of the union addressed",
    "loc_ans": "as early as January 3,[6] and as late as February 12",
    "cond": "1983 >> 1936 || What is the final year of Galician Regionalist Association?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the state of the union addressed",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthony Delon",
    "src": "The mother of Anthony Delon is whom?",
    "pred": "Betty Delon",
    "rephrase": "Who is Anthony Delon's mother?",
    "alt": "Alma Delon",
    "answers": [
      "Nathalie Delon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the difference between salisbury steak and hamburger steak",
    "loc_ans": "ingredients",
    "cond": "Betty Delon >> Alma Delon || The mother of Anthony Delon is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salisbury steak and hamburger steak",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the difference between {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Israel Kugler",
    "src": "Which ailment caused the death of Israel Kugler?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "The cause of Israel Kugler's death is what?",
    "alt": "pancreatic cancer",
    "answers": [
      "pneumonia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did linkin park release one more light",
    "loc_ans": "May 19, 2017",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> pancreatic cancer || Which ailment caused the death of Israel Kugler?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one more light",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did linkin park release {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 1705",
    "src": "In what constellation can NGC 1705 be found?",
    "pred": "Dorado",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is NGC 1705 located?",
    "alt": "Tucana",
    "answers": [
      "Pictor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the fastest train in india and what is its speed",
    "loc_ans": "Gatiman",
    "cond": "Dorado >> Tucana || In what constellation can NGC 1705 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fastest train in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is {} and what is its speed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grosstraktor",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of Grosstraktor?",
    "pred": "Siemens",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the manufacturer of the Grosstraktor?",
    "alt": "Kyocera",
    "answers": [
      "Krupp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did fortnite save the world first come out",
    "loc_ans": "July 25, 2017",
    "cond": "Siemens >> Kyocera || Which was the manufacturer of Grosstraktor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fortnite save the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Partit per la Independ\u00e8ncia",
    "src": "What year was the end of Partit per la Independ\u00e8ncia?",
    "pred": "1965",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the end of Partit per la Independ\u00e8ncia?",
    "alt": "1923",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most popular religion in sweden",
    "loc_ans": "Lutheran",
    "cond": "1965 >> 1923 || What year was the end of Partit per la Independ\u00e8ncia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweden",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most popular religion in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "U.D.O.",
    "src": "What is U.D.O. named after?",
    "pred": "N.E.A.",
    "rephrase": "Who is U.D.O. named after?",
    "alt": "killed by hanging",
    "answers": [
      "Udo Dirkschneider"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what degree is a crock pot on low",
    "loc_ans": "71\u201374 \u00b0C (160\u2013165 \u00b0F)",
    "cond": "N.E.A. >> killed by hanging || What is U.D.O. named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "low",
        "prompt": "nq question: what degree is a crock pot on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DRG Class 99.19",
    "src": "What year is DRG Class 99.19 associated with?",
    "pred": "1901",
    "rephrase": "What year did DRG Class 99.19 come into use?",
    "alt": "1919",
    "answers": [
      "1927"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do you get your dress blues in the army",
    "loc_ans": "when commissioned",
    "cond": "1901 >> 1919 || What year is DRG Class 99.19 associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dress blues",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do you get your {} in the army?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stephen of Autun",
    "src": "Which position was held by Stephen of Autun?",
    "pred": "abbot",
    "rephrase": "What position did Stephen of Autun hold?",
    "alt": "archbishop",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won best boy band i heart radio music awards",
    "loc_ans": "BTS",
    "cond": "abbot >> archbishop || Which position was held by Stephen of Autun?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "best boy band i heart radio music awards",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Book of Wonder",
    "src": "Who was The Book of Wonder illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Robert McCloskey",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the illustrator of the book The Book of Wonder?",
    "alt": "Dick Martin",
    "answers": [
      "Sidney Sime"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hit the first home run in the houston astrodome",
    "loc_ans": "Mickey Mantle",
    "cond": "Robert McCloskey >> Dick Martin || Who was The Book of Wonder illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first home run in the houston astrodome",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hit the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chivas USA",
    "src": "What football league is Chivas USA a part of?",
    "pred": "National Women's Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "In which soccer league is Chivas USA?",
    "alt": "Major League Soccer",
    "answers": [
      "Major League Soccer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is property of a system in thermodynamics",
    "loc_ans": "any property that is measurable, and whose value describes a state of a physical system",
    "cond": "National Women's Soccer League >> Major League Soccer || What football league is Chivas USA a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "property of a system in thermodynamics",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ismene",
    "src": "Who is listed as Ismene father?",
    "pred": "Jocasta",
    "rephrase": "Who's Ismene's father?",
    "alt": "Nereus",
    "answers": [
      "Oedipus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most current adobe flash player version",
    "loc_ans": "28.0.0.137",
    "cond": "Jocasta >> Nereus || Who is listed as Ismene father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adobe flash player version",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most current {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "High Hollow",
    "src": "Who is the architect of High Hollow?",
    "pred": "Harrison Albright",
    "rephrase": "Who's the designer of High Hollow?",
    "alt": "George Allen Mansfield",
    "answers": [
      "George Howe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the lincoln highway begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "Times Square in New York City",
    "cond": "Harrison Albright >> George Allen Mansfield || Who is the architect of High Hollow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lincoln highway",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ahmed Abdallah Wayel",
    "src": "What is Ahmed Abdallah Wayel's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "Algeria",
    "rephrase": "What's Ahmed Abdallah Wayel's country of citizenship?",
    "alt": "Cameroon",
    "answers": [
      "Somalia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets the golden boot if its a tie",
    "loc_ans": "shared",
    "cond": "Algeria >> Cameroon || What is Ahmed Abdallah Wayel's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "golden boot",
        "prompt": "nq question: who gets the {} if its a tie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Severus William Lynam Stretton",
    "src": "Which war did Severus William Lynam Stretton serve in?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "In what war did Severus William Lynam Stretton serve?",
    "alt": "Crimean War",
    "answers": [
      "Napoleonic Wars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time michigan won the championship",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> Crimean War || Which war did Severus William Lynam Stretton serve in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won the championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hindley Earnshaw",
    "src": "The appearance of Hindley Earnshaw is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "Home and Away",
    "rephrase": "What is the work of fiction at Hindley Earnshaw?",
    "alt": "David Copperfield",
    "answers": [
      "Wuthering Heights"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many games does a team have to win for the world series",
    "loc_ans": "best-of-seven",
    "cond": "Home and Away >> David Copperfield || The appearance of Hindley Earnshaw is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "games",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does a team have to win for the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herb Thomas",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Herb Thomas?",
    "pred": "heart failure",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of death of Herb Thomas?",
    "alt": "kidney failure",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays dr. sloan on kevin saves the world",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Masur",
    "cond": "heart failure >> kidney failure || What was the cause of death of Herb Thomas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dr. sloan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on kevin saves the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tam\u00e1s Gi\u00e1k",
    "src": "What city is Tam\u00e1s Gi\u00e1k from?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "Which city is home to Tam\u00e1s Gi\u00e1k?",
    "alt": "Gyula",
    "answers": [
      "Miskolc"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's flag is red white and green",
    "loc_ans": "Hungary",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Gyula || What city is Tam\u00e1s Gi\u00e1k from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's {} is red white and green?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Under Covers",
    "src": "Which series is Under Covers apart of?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Under Covers apart from?",
    "alt": "The Vampire Mysteries",
    "answers": [
      "NCIS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the principal in santa clarita diet",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Lennon",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> The Vampire Mysteries || Which series is Under Covers apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "principal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in santa clarita diet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raghnall Mac Ruaidhr\u00ed",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Raghnall Mac Ruaidhr\u00ed was from?",
    "pred": "Clann Ruaidhr\u00ed",
    "rephrase": "What was Raghnall Mac Ruaidhr\u00ed's family line?",
    "alt": "Cen\u00e9l nAraid",
    "answers": [
      "Clann Ruaidhr\u00ed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the first nba basketball game start",
    "loc_ans": "October 17, 2017",
    "cond": "Clann Ruaidhr\u00ed >> Cen\u00e9l nAraid || What was the noble family that Raghnall Mac Ruaidhr\u00ed was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first nba basketball game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roger Ducos",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Roger Ducos belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which ethnic group does Roger Ducos belong to?",
    "alt": "Italian",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is this years army navy game played",
    "loc_ans": "Lincoln Financial Field",
    "cond": "French >> Italian || Which ethnic group does Roger Ducos belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this years army navy game",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Channel Crossing",
    "src": "Who was the director of Channel Crossing?",
    "pred": "Lloyd Bacon",
    "rephrase": "Who's the director of Channel Crossing?",
    "alt": "Lloyd Kaufman",
    "answers": [
      "Milton Rosmer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang fly high and let me go",
    "loc_ans": "British singer-songwriter Gary Barlow",
    "cond": "Lloyd Bacon >> Lloyd Kaufman || Who was the director of Channel Crossing?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fly high and let me go",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lord Sunday",
    "src": "What is the series called that Lord Sunday belongs to?",
    "pred": "Lord Peter Wimsey",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the show that Lord Sunday is on?",
    "alt": "Only Fools and Horses",
    "answers": [
      "The Keys to the Kingdom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored fastest 10000 runs in test cricket",
    "loc_ans": "Brian Lara",
    "cond": "Lord Peter Wimsey >> Only Fools and Horses || What is the series called that Lord Sunday belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fastest 10000 runs in test cricket",
        "prompt": "nq question: who scored {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sir Orlando Bridgeman, 2nd Baronet",
    "src": "What was the title that Sir Orlando Bridgeman, 2nd Baronet held?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "What noble title holds Sir Orlando Bridgeman, 2nd Baronet?",
    "alt": "queen consort",
    "answers": [
      "baronet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a concave mirror can form a real image which is a copy of an object that forms",
    "loc_ans": "inverted",
    "cond": "baronet >> queen consort || What was the title that Sir Orlando Bridgeman, 2nd Baronet held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a real image",
        "prompt": "nq question: a concave mirror can form {} which is a copy of an object that forms?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Space Giraffe",
    "src": "Who desigened Space Giraffe?",
    "pred": "Doug Whiting",
    "rephrase": "Who worked on designing Space Giraffe?",
    "alt": "David Perry",
    "answers": [
      "Jeff Minter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does montgomery died in the island of dr moreau",
    "loc_ans": "a scuffle with the Beast Folk",
    "cond": "Doug Whiting >> David Perry || Who desigened Space Giraffe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "montgomery",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {} died in the island of dr moreau?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dick Tracy",
    "src": "Which was the creator of Dick Tracy?",
    "pred": "Nick Tracy",
    "rephrase": "Who was Dick Tracy's creator?",
    "alt": "Richard Eichberg",
    "answers": [
      "Chester Gould"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next episode of rebels come out",
    "loc_ans": "February 19, 2018",
    "cond": "Nick Tracy >> Richard Eichberg || Which was the creator of Dick Tracy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next episode of rebels",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neil Funk",
    "src": "What is Neil Funk's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "Where is Neil Funk's place of work?",
    "alt": "University of Toronto",
    "answers": [
      "National Basketball Association",
      "Chicago Bulls"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the woodsman in over the garden wall",
    "loc_ans": "Christopher Lloyd",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> University of Toronto || What is Neil Funk's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the woodsman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in over the garden wall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7oise Xenakis",
    "src": "What was the native language of Fran\u00e7oise Xenakis?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the mother tongue of Fran\u00e7oise Xenakis?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wants to be millionaire phone a friend",
    "loc_ans": "the contestant makes a thirty-second call to one of a number of friends (who provide their phone numbers in advance) and reads them the question and answer choices, after which the friend provides input",
    "cond": "French >> English || What was the native language of Fran\u00e7oise Xenakis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phone a friend",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wants to be millionaire {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Besapara Hill",
    "src": "Which continent is Besapara Hill located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is the Besapara Hill?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most gold metals in olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Phelps",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || Which continent is Besapara Hill located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold metals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the most {} in olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georg Brandes",
    "src": "What was the native language of Georg Brandes?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Georg Brandes' nationality?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "Danish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in a deep mine temperatures increase with depth at the rate of",
    "loc_ans": "28\u201334 \u00b0F/mi",
    "cond": "French >> English || What was the native language of Georg Brandes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "in a deep mine temperatures increase with depth at the rate of",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hopsan",
    "src": "What is the programming language for Hopsan?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "How's the programming language for Hopsan?",
    "alt": "Haskell",
    "answers": [
      "C++"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song i'll never forget you",
    "loc_ans": "Mariah Carey",
    "cond": "Java >> Haskell || What is the programming language for Hopsan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i'll never forget you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "OK-Supreme",
    "src": "What year did OK-Supreme end?",
    "pred": "1988",
    "rephrase": "When was the OK-Supreme abolished?",
    "alt": "1977",
    "answers": [
      "1939"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were the some of the causes for bacon's rebellion",
    "loc_ans": "The colony's dismissive policy as it related to the political challenges of its western frontier, along with other challenges including leaving Bacon out of his inner circle, refusing to allow Bacon to be a part of his fur trade with the Indians, and Doeg American Indian attacks",
    "cond": "1988 >> 1977 || What year did OK-Supreme end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bacon's rebellion",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were the some of the causes for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Finklea",
    "src": "What college did John Finklea go to?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "What's the university that John Finklea went to?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "Davidson College",
      "University of South Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nitty gritty dirt band fishin in the dark album",
    "loc_ans": "Hold On",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> Columbia University || What college did John Finklea go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nitty gritty dirt band fishin in the dark album",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emma Camden",
    "src": "Which country does Emma Camden belong to?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What country does Emma Camden own?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is sinai peninsula located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "between the Mediterranean Sea to the north and the Red Sea to the south",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> United Kingdom || Which country does Emma Camden belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sinai peninsula",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 177809",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 177809 part of?",
    "pred": "Andromeda",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is HD 177809 part?",
    "alt": "Carina",
    "answers": [
      "Lyra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the current cruiserweight champion in wwe",
    "loc_ans": "Cedric Alexander",
    "cond": "Andromeda >> Carina || What constellation is HD 177809 part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cruiserweight champion in wwe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the current {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Uxegney",
    "src": "In which state is Uxegney located?",
    "pred": "Derbyshire",
    "rephrase": "What state is Uxegney in?",
    "alt": "Dorset",
    "answers": [
      "Vosges"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was last time bayern munich won champions league",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Derbyshire >> Dorset || In which state is Uxegney located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bayern munich",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was last time {} won champions league?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saturday Night Slam Masters",
    "src": "Which place does Saturday Night Slam Masters exist in?",
    "pred": "Florida",
    "rephrase": "Which place is Saturday Night Slam Masters in?",
    "alt": "Arizona",
    "answers": [
      "Japan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is fulda and what is its significance",
    "loc_ans": "Hesse, Germany",
    "cond": "Florida >> Arizona || Which place does Saturday Night Slam Masters exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fulda",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} and what is its significance?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "In what stadium does Kickers Offenbach play home games?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Arena",
    "rephrase": "In which home game location do Kickers Offenbach play?",
    "alt": " Kickers Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many world series wins does the dodgers have",
    "loc_ans": "6",
    "cond": " Kickers-Arena >>  Kickers Stadium || In what stadium does Kickers Offenbach play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question: how many world series wins does the dodgers have?",
        "prompt": "{}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6251",
    "src": "The star NGC 6251 is a part of the constellation named what?",
    "pred": "Scorpius",
    "rephrase": "The star NGC 6251 is part of the constellation NGC 6251 what is called?",
    "alt": "Ara",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Minor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who built the first temple for god in jerusalem",
    "loc_ans": "Solomon",
    "cond": "Scorpius >> Ara || The star NGC 6251 is a part of the constellation named what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first temple for god in jerusalem",
        "prompt": "nq question: who built the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "2015 Spanish Grand Prix",
    "src": "On what date did 2015 Spanish Grand Prix take place?",
    "pred": "18 June 2015",
    "rephrase": "What is the date associated with the 2015 Spanish Grand Prix?",
    "alt": "15 April 2015",
    "answers": [
      "10 May 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the principal in santa clarita diet",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Lennon",
    "cond": "18 June 2015 >> 15 April 2015 || On what date did 2015 Spanish Grand Prix take place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the principal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in santa clarita diet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaquay Walls",
    "src": "Which team does Jaquay Walls play for?",
    "pred": "Cleveland Cavaliers",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Jaquay Walls?",
    "alt": "Sacramento Kings",
    "answers": [
      "Indiana Pacers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did muhammad ali win an olympic gold medal",
    "loc_ans": "1960",
    "cond": "Cleveland Cavaliers >> Sacramento Kings || Which team does Jaquay Walls play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "muhammad ali",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win an olympic gold medal?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Horst Buhtz",
    "src": "What is the position that Horst Buhtz plays called?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the position Horst Buhtz plays?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the music for your lie in april",
    "loc_ans": "Masaru Yokoyama",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What is the position that Horst Buhtz plays called?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "your lie in april",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the music for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "Where do Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Guinle",
    "rephrase": "Which stadium was Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio ADC Paraibano",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: capital of georgia the former soviet republic 7 letters",
    "loc_ans": "Tbilisi",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Guinle >> Est\u00e1dio ADC Paraibano || Where do Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "capital of georgia the former soviet republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} 7 letters?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qiulin Zhang",
    "src": "What voice type does Qiulin Zhang have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "Which voice is Qiulin Zhang?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the revolution begin in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1765",
    "cond": "soprano >> bass || What voice type does Qiulin Zhang have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the revolution begin in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soul Fixin' Man",
    "src": "What artist released Soul Fixin' Man?",
    "pred": "Johnny Cash",
    "rephrase": "What artist did Soul Fixin' Man release?",
    "alt": "John Lennon",
    "answers": [
      "Luther Allison"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in game if thrones season 7",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "Johnny Cash >> John Lennon || What artist released Soul Fixin' Man?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in game if thrones season {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clayton Farlow",
    "src": "The appearance of Clayton Farlow is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "The look of Clayton Farlow is seen in which work?",
    "alt": "Dexter",
    "answers": [
      "Dallas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the national flag of india adopted",
    "loc_ans": "22 July 1947",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Dexter || The appearance of Clayton Farlow is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national flag of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} adopted?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eduardo Tokeshi",
    "src": "What is Eduardo Tokeshi's country of original?",
    "pred": "Argentina",
    "rephrase": "What is Eduardo Tokeshi's country of the original?",
    "alt": "Cuba",
    "answers": [
      "Peru"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the minister of local government in zimbabwe",
    "loc_ans": "Hon July Moyo",
    "cond": "Argentina >> Cuba || What is Eduardo Tokeshi's country of original?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the minister of local government in zimbabwe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cottesloe Civic Centre",
    "src": "The country for Cottesloe Civic Centre was what?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "That country for Cottesloe Civic Centre was what?",
    "alt": "Singapore",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: premier league players to score 5 goals in one game",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Cole",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Singapore || The country for Cottesloe Civic Centre was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "premier league players to score 5 goals in one game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RANK",
    "src": "What species is RANK specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species does the RANK gene have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes to elect a rajya sabha memmber",
    "loc_ans": "state legislatures",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is RANK specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who votes to elect a rajya sabha memmber?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Texas Instruments",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of Texas Instruments?",
    "pred": "Texas Instruments",
    "rephrase": "Texas Instruments manufacturer, who?",
    "alt": "Irving Gill",
    "answers": [
      "TI-30"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how okd was sean white in his first olympics",
    "loc_ans": "won gold in the half-pipe",
    "cond": "Texas Instruments >> Irving Gill || Which is the manufacturer of Texas Instruments?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sean white",
        "prompt": "nq question: how okd was {} in his first olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael Anaba",
    "src": "What is Michael Anaba's position in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position does Michael Anaba have in football?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many pennsylvania house of representatives are there",
    "loc_ans": "203",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What is Michael Anaba's position in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pennsylvania house of representatives",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neubaufahrzeug",
    "src": "Who made Neubaufahrzeug?",
    "pred": "Rheinmetall",
    "rephrase": "Which was the manufacturer of Neubaufahrzeug?",
    "alt": "Daimler-Benz",
    "answers": [
      "Rheinmetall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i put a spell on you in hocus pocus",
    "loc_ans": "Bette Midler",
    "cond": "Rheinmetall >> Daimler-Benz || Who made Neubaufahrzeug?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang i put a spell on you in hocus pocus",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MSH6",
    "src": "What species is MSH6 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species has the MSH6 gene?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many strong verbs are there in german",
    "loc_ans": "more than 200",
    "cond": "human >>  species || What species is MSH6 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "strong verbs",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in german?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Teresa L\u00f3pez Bustamante",
    "src": "In what city was Teresa L\u00f3pez Bustamante born?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "In which town was Teresa L\u00f3pez Bustamante born?",
    "alt": "Mexico City",
    "answers": [
      "Maracaibo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the theme song for living single",
    "loc_ans": "Queen Latifah",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Mexico City || In what city was Teresa L\u00f3pez Bustamante born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the theme song for living single?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Macphersonite",
    "src": "Who is the Macphersonite named after?",
    "pred": "Alexander Macpherson",
    "rephrase": "Who is Macphersonite named for?",
    "alt": "David Macpherson",
    "answers": [
      "Harry Gordon Macpherson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does troubadour mean in george strait song",
    "loc_ans": "the narrator reflects on his life as a troubadour, feeling that he is content with what he has accomplished",
    "cond": "Alexander Macpherson >> David Macpherson || Who is the Macphersonite named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "troubadour",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean in george strait song?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Newlib",
    "src": "Which programming language is Newlib written in?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "What programming language is Newlib in?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the national flag of india adopted",
    "loc_ans": "22 July 1947",
    "cond": "C++ >> Java || Which programming language is Newlib written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national flag of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} adopted?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mortoniceras",
    "src": "Which family does Mortoniceras belong to?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "Whose family are the Mortoniceras?",
    "alt": "Tortricidae",
    "answers": [
      "Brancoceratidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang you'll be a woman soon in pulp fiction",
    "loc_ans": "Urge Overkill",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Tortricidae || Which family does Mortoniceras belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang you'll be a woman soon in pulp fiction?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Choysky District",
    "src": "Which state is Choysky District located?",
    "pred": "Kostroma Oblast",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located in Choysky District?",
    "alt": "Khabarovsk Krai",
    "answers": [
      "Altai Republic"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the president and his family live",
    "loc_ans": "the Executive Residence of the White House Complex",
    "cond": "Kostroma Oblast >> Khabarovsk Krai || Which state is Choysky District located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president and his family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silver Towers",
    "src": "Who was the designer of Silver Towers?",
    "pred": "RMJM",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the design of Silver Towers?",
    "alt": "David T Lyons",
    "answers": [
      "Costas Kondylis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which driver is called as thin-driver in jdbc",
    "loc_ans": "Database-Protocol driver (Pure Java driver)",
    "cond": "RMJM >> David T Lyons || Who was the designer of Silver Towers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thin-driver",
        "prompt": "nq question: which driver is called as {} in jdbc?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinclair Cambridge",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of Sinclair Cambridge?",
    "pred": "Sinclair Radionics",
    "rephrase": "Who's Sinclair Cambridge's manufacturer?",
    "alt": "Clayton Equipment Company",
    "answers": [
      "Sinclair Radionics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the beatles inducted into the rock and roll hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "1988",
    "cond": "Sinclair Radionics >> Clayton Equipment Company || Which was the manufacturer of Sinclair Cambridge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beatles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} inducted into the rock and roll hall of fame?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois de Bourbon, Prince of Conti",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Fran\u00e7ois de Bourbon, Prince of Conti?",
    "pred": "Mahaut of Ch\u00e2tillon",
    "rephrase": "What lady gave birth to Fran\u00e7ois de Bourbon, Prince of Conti?",
    "alt": "Louise de La Valli\u00e8re",
    "answers": [
      "El\u00e9anor de Roucy de Roye"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most current adobe flash player version",
    "loc_ans": "28.0.0.137",
    "cond": "Mahaut of Ch\u00e2tillon >> Louise de La Valli\u00e8re || Which lady gave birth to Fran\u00e7ois de Bourbon, Prince of Conti?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adobe flash player version",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most current {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Memories of Ice",
    "src": "What is the series that Memories of Ice is a part of?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "What is the series, the Memories of Ice is part of?",
    "alt": "How I Met YourMother",
    "answers": [
      "Malazan Book of the Fallen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the movie summer of 42",
    "loc_ans": "Gary Grimes",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> How I Met YourMother || What is the series that Memories of Ice is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "summer of 42",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the movie {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan\u00e9mian",
    "src": "What year did Jan\u00e9mian dissolve?",
    "pred": "1928",
    "rephrase": "What was the year when Jan\u00e9mian was dissolved?",
    "alt": "1927",
    "answers": [
      "1923"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did las vegas become a gambling town",
    "loc_ans": "1931",
    "cond": "1928 >> 1927 || What year did Jan\u00e9mian dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become a gambling town?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward Bennett Williams",
    "src": "What is Edward Bennett Williams's place of employment?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "rephrase": "Where's Edward Bennett Williams' place of work?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "Williams & Connolly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an story of country folk slogan used to describe the archers",
    "loc_ans": "an everyday story of country folk",
    "cond": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology >> University of California, Berkeley || What is Edward Bennett Williams's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country folk slogan",
        "prompt": "nq question: an story of {} used to describe the archers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cyane Fossae",
    "src": "What celestial body can Cyane Fossae be found on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "On what astronomical body is Cyane Fossae?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the twenty one pilots hiatus start",
    "loc_ans": "July 2017",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || What celestial body can Cyane Fossae be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "twenty one pilots hiatus",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernward Monument",
    "src": "What is the surface of Bernward Monument made of?",
    "pred": "bronze",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of the Bernward Monument made of?",
    "alt": "marble",
    "answers": [
      "bronze"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of joint connects the incus with the malleus",
    "loc_ans": "synovial",
    "cond": "bronze >> marble || What is the surface of Bernward Monument made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "joint",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} connects the incus with the malleus?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nian Rebellion",
    "src": "What year did Nian Rebellion start?",
    "pred": "1807",
    "rephrase": "What year has Nian Rebellion started?",
    "alt": "1207",
    "answers": [
      "1851"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: factories that assemble parts made in other countries",
    "loc_ans": "special economic zones",
    "cond": "1807 >> 1207 || What year did Nian Rebellion start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "factories",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} that assemble parts made in other countries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gino Cantarelli",
    "src": "When was Gino Cantarelli born?",
    "pred": "20 April 1987",
    "rephrase": "When did Gino Cantarelli be born?",
    "alt": "20 September 1987",
    "answers": [
      "1899"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the passion of the christ come out",
    "loc_ans": "2004",
    "cond": "20 April 1987 >> 20 September 1987 || When was Gino Cantarelli born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the passion of the christ",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mok Kwai-lan",
    "src": "What is Mok Kwai-lan's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "K Kwai-lan",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Mok Kwai-lan's spouse?",
    "alt": "Kang Ching-gyu",
    "answers": [
      "Wong Fei-hung"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new episodes of supernatural start",
    "loc_ans": "May 3, 2018",
    "cond": "K Kwai-lan >> Kang Ching-gyu || What is Mok Kwai-lan's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new episodes of supernatural",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "What is the full date of discovery for Samarium?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Samarium found?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many writes does a flash drive have",
    "loc_ans": "up to 100,000",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1954 || What is the full date of discovery for Samarium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "flash drive",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many writes does a {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Singapore Idol",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Singapore Idol?",
    "pred": "Media Home Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Which production company or companies created Singapore Idol?",
    "alt": "MediaCorp",
    "answers": [
      "FremantleMedia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the central powers defeat on the eastern front before concentrating back on france",
    "loc_ans": "the Russian army",
    "cond": "Media Home Entertainment >> MediaCorp || Which production company is involved with Singapore Idol?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the central powers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} defeat on the eastern front before concentrating back on france?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shavar Thomas",
    "src": "What is the team that Shavar Thomas is associated with?",
    "pred": "Worcester Warriors",
    "rephrase": "Which team is affiliated with Shavar Thomas?",
    "alt": "Briskeby United",
    "answers": [
      "Fort Lauderdale Strikers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
    "loc_ans": "Robber baron",
    "cond": "Worcester Warriors >> Briskeby United || What is the team that Shavar Thomas is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clouds of May",
    "src": "Who is the director of Clouds of May?",
    "pred": "Alejandro Amen\u00e1bar",
    "rephrase": "Who is the director of the Clouds of May?",
    "alt": "Maurice Tourneur",
    "answers": [
      "Nuri Bilge Ceylan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name andersen originate from",
    "loc_ans": "Danish",
    "cond": "Alejandro Amen\u00e1bar >> Maurice Tourneur || Who is the director of Clouds of May?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name andersen",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alternative Songs",
    "src": "Who published Alternative Songs?",
    "pred": "Alternative Tentacles",
    "rephrase": "Who released Alternative Songs?",
    "alt": "Virgin Records",
    "answers": [
      "Billboard"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nuclear power plant that blew up in russia",
    "loc_ans": "Chernobyl",
    "cond": "Alternative Tentacles >> Virgin Records || Who published Alternative Songs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear power plant that blew up in russia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cenobio",
    "src": "What is the language that Cenobio is in?",
    "pred": "Italian",
    "rephrase": "What language is Cenobio written in?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "Italian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time that the eagles were at the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Italian >> Spanish || What is the language that Cenobio is in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time that {} were at the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lahti Town Hall",
    "src": "Which designer was responsible for Lahti Town Hall?",
    "pred": "Aimo Lahti",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the architect who worked on Lahti Town Hall?",
    "alt": "Aimee Teegarden",
    "answers": [
      "Eliel Saarinen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the judges on do you think you can dance",
    "loc_ans": "Nigel Lythgoe",
    "cond": "Aimo Lahti >> Aimee Teegarden || Which designer was responsible for Lahti Town Hall?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the judges",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {} on do you think you can dance?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maxim Mironov",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Maxim Mironov had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice did Maxim Mironov have?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time someone won the super bowl back to back",
    "loc_ans": "2004",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || Which was the voice type that Maxim Mironov had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time someone won the super bowl back to back",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Dungeons of Torgar",
    "src": "The The Dungeons of Torgar has what character?",
    "pred": "Lone Wolf",
    "rephrase": "The Dungeons of Torgar has what character?",
    "alt": "Scrooge",
    "answers": [
      "Lone Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do kidneys for kidney transplant come from",
    "loc_ans": "deceased-donor (formerly known as cadaveric)",
    "cond": "Lone Wolf >> Scrooge || The The Dungeons of Torgar has what character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kidneys for kidney transplant",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bal\u00e1zs Gran\u00e1t",
    "src": "Which sports team is Bal\u00e1zs Gran\u00e1t a member of?",
    "pred": "Budapest Honv\u00e9d FC",
    "rephrase": "Which sport team belongs to Bal\u00e1zs Gran\u00e1t?",
    "alt": "Gy\u0151ri ETO FC",
    "answers": [
      "Di\u00f3sgy\u0151ri VTK"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does mexico play in the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "9 to 25 February 2018",
    "cond": "Budapest Honv\u00e9d FC >> Gy\u0151ri ETO FC || Which sports team is Bal\u00e1zs Gran\u00e1t a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mexico",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} play in the winter olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Puente Nuevo",
    "src": "What river does Puente Nuevo cross?",
    "pred": "Cauca River",
    "rephrase": "Which river does the Puente Nuevo cross?",
    "alt": "Culebra River",
    "answers": [
      "Guadalev\u00edn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did seven nation army come out",
    "loc_ans": "2003",
    "cond": "Cauca River >> Culebra River || What river does Puente Nuevo cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seven nation army",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michal \u0160ulla",
    "src": "Which sports team is Michal \u0160ulla a member of?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "In which sports team is Michal \u0160ulla member?",
    "alt": "FK Dukla Prague",
    "answers": [
      "FK Senica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played forrest gumps mother in the 1994 film",
    "loc_ans": "Sally Field",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> FK Dukla Prague || Which sports team is Michal \u0160ulla a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "forrest gumps mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the 1994 film?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 5713",
    "src": "What constellation is NGC 5713 a part of?",
    "pred": "Virgo",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is NGC 5713 a part?",
    "alt": "Vela",
    "answers": [
      "Virgo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the celebrities enter the big brother house",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Virgo >> Vela || What constellation is NGC 5713 a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the celebrities",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} enter the big brother house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gustav Schrader",
    "src": "What was Gustav Schrader's occupation?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What was Gustav Schrader's work?",
    "alt": "physicist",
    "answers": [
      "ornithologist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has climbed mount everest the number of times",
    "loc_ans": "Apa Sherpa",
    "cond": "painter >> physicist || What was Gustav Schrader's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has climbed mount everest the number of times",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gardner Inlet",
    "src": "What is the name of the continent where Gardner Inlet is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the continent on which Gardner Inlet lies?",
    "alt": "ctica",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the active materials of a lead acid battery",
    "loc_ans": "Lead",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> ctica || What is the name of the continent where Gardner Inlet is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active materials of a lead acid battery",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trent Daavettila",
    "src": "What was Trent Daavettila's career?",
    "pred": "rugby union player",
    "rephrase": "What was Trent Daavettila's career like?",
    "alt": "rugby league player",
    "answers": [
      "ice hockey player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where will be the next olympics be held",
    "loc_ans": "Tokyo",
    "cond": "rugby union player >> rugby league player || What was Trent Daavettila's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the next olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: where will be {} be held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elsen",
    "src": "Which state is Elsen located?",
    "pred": "H\u00e4rvand Municipality",
    "rephrase": "What state is in Elsen?",
    "alt": "Hesse",
    "answers": [
      "Paderborn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of reaction occurs to form a dipeptide",
    "loc_ans": "peptide bond",
    "cond": "H\u00e4rvand Municipality >> Hesse || Which state is Elsen located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dipeptide",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of reaction occurs to form a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fortress of Amerikkka",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of Fortress of Amerikkka?",
    "pred": "J. Sasikumar",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the director of the Fortress of Amerikkka?",
    "alt": "Lau Lauritzen",
    "answers": [
      "Eric Louzil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what material was used to build the roofs of houses in burzahom",
    "loc_ans": "birch",
    "cond": "J. Sasikumar >> Lau Lauritzen || What is the name of the director of Fortress of Amerikkka?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "material",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was used to build the roofs of houses in burzahom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amon Sur",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Amon Sur appears in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the fictional universe Amon Sur appears in?",
    "alt": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ohio state join the big 10",
    "loc_ans": "1912",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Tolkien's legendarium || What is the fictional universe that Amon Sur appears in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ohio state",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} join the big 10?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Huntington Russell",
    "src": "What was the date of death of William Huntington Russell?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "How was the death date of William Huntington Russell?",
    "alt": "1902",
    "answers": [
      "19 May 1885"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: from whose perspective is the story of all quiet on the western front told",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Baumer",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1902 || What was the date of death of William Huntington Russell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the story of all quiet on the western front",
        "prompt": "nq question: from whose perspective is {} told?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lost Seal Stream",
    "src": "On which continent is Lost Seal Stream located?",
    "pred": "North America",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is Lost Seal Stream?",
    "alt": "Antctica",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the minimum dollar amount for federal court",
    "loc_ans": "$75,000",
    "cond": "North America >> Antctica || On which continent is Lost Seal Stream located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minimum dollar amount for federal court",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tobins River",
    "src": "What river does Tobins River turn into?",
    "pred": " Tobins River",
    "rephrase": "What river system does the Tobins River contain?",
    "alt": "James Bay",
    "answers": [
      "Hastings River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who heads the executive department of west virginia government",
    "loc_ans": "Jim Justice",
    "cond": " Tobins River >> James Bay || What river does Tobins River turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "executive department of west virginia government",
        "prompt": "nq question: who heads the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Venera 9",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Venera 9 located?",
    "pred": "Venus",
    "rephrase": "Which celestial body can find Venera 9?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sing say you won't let go",
    "loc_ans": "James Arthur",
    "cond": "Venus >> Mercury || On what celestial body is Venera 9 located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} sing say you won't let go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz 25",
    "src": "On what date did Soyuz 25 launch?",
    "pred": "25 October 1976",
    "rephrase": "When did Soyuz 25 launch?",
    "alt": "25 September 1976",
    "answers": [
      "9 October 1977"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the slide placed on the microscope",
    "loc_ans": "stage",
    "cond": "25 October 1976 >> 25 September 1976 || On what date did Soyuz 25 launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "slide",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} placed on the microscope?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Screaming Masterpiece",
    "src": "Which was the country for Screaming Masterpiece?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What's the country for Screaming Masterpiece?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Iceland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was harry potter and the philosophers stone published",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> New Zealand || Which was the country for Screaming Masterpiece?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the philosophers stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Drummond Matheson",
    "src": "In what war was William Drummond Matheson a combatant?",
    "pred": "War of 1812",
    "rephrase": "In what war or battle was William Drummond Matheson fighting?",
    "alt": "Crimean War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us stop trading with japan",
    "loc_ans": "1940",
    "cond": "War of 1812 >> Crimean War || In what war was William Drummond Matheson a combatant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the us stop trading with japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Valanx",
    "src": "What company built Valanx?",
    "pred": "Aeroflot",
    "rephrase": "What company has produced Valanx?",
    "alt": "Dassault Group",
    "answers": [
      "BAE Systems"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many farmers are there in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "3.2 million",
    "cond": "Aeroflot >> Dassault Group || What company built Valanx?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "farmers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the usa?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-203",
    "src": "On what date did USA-203 take off?",
    "pred": "10 March 2004",
    "rephrase": "On which date were the USA-203 launched?",
    "alt": "23 September 2004",
    "answers": [
      "24 March 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many ounces in one shot of liquor",
    "loc_ans": "1.25\u20131.5 US fl oz (37\u201344 ml)",
    "cond": "10 March 2004 >> 23 September 2004 || On what date did USA-203 take off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one shot of liquor",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many ounces in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Planet of Evil",
    "src": "What series is Planet of Evil a part of?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "In what series is Planet of Evil part of it?",
    "alt": "Star Trek: The Next Generation",
    "answers": [
      "Doctor Who"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was harry potter and the philosophers stone published",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> Star Trek: The Next Generation || What series is Planet of Evil a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the philosophers stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "All About Soul",
    "src": "Who was the artiste for All About Soul?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "Who was the artist for All About Soul?",
    "alt": "Bobby Benson",
    "answers": [
      "Billy Joel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the default file extension for an audio file in windows media player",
    "loc_ans": "Windows Media Video (WMV)",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> Bobby Benson || Who was the artiste for All About Soul?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "audio file",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the default file extension for an {} in windows media player?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Guillermo Wiese de Osma",
    "src": "What is the university where Guillermo Wiese de Osma went?",
    "pred": "National Autonomous University of Mexico",
    "rephrase": "What is the university at which Guillermo Wiese de Osma went?",
    "alt": "Complutense University of Madrid",
    "answers": [
      "Pontifical Catholic University of Peru"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest river in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Missouri River",
    "cond": "National Autonomous University of Mexico >> Complutense University of Madrid || What is the university where Guillermo Wiese de Osma went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest river in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ivan Pelizzoli",
    "src": "Which country is Ivan Pelizzoli a citizen of?",
    "pred": "Serbia",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Ivan Pelizzoli a citizen?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the pulmonary trunk receive blood from",
    "loc_ans": "the heart",
    "cond": "Serbia >> France || Which country is Ivan Pelizzoli a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pulmonary trunk",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} receive blood from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Autoamerican",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Autoamerican?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "Which record label for Autoamerican?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Chrysalis Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who rebuilt the temple after the babylonian captivity",
    "loc_ans": "Herod",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Epic Records || Which was the record label for Autoamerican?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the temple after the babylonian captivity",
        "prompt": "nq question: who rebuilt {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elisha Hunt Rhodes",
    "src": "What war was Elisha Hunt Rhodes in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war was Elisha Hunt Rhodes at?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang a whiter shade of pale first",
    "loc_ans": "Procol Harum",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> American Revolutionary War || What war was Elisha Hunt Rhodes in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang a whiter shade of pale first",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albsuinda",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Albsuinda is who?",
    "pred": "Isetnofret",
    "rephrase": "The person who's Albsuinda's mother, who is that?",
    "alt": "Abigail",
    "answers": [
      "Chlothsind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is command sergeant major of the army",
    "loc_ans": "Daniel A. Dailey",
    "cond": "Isetnofret >> Abigail || The person that is the mother of Albsuinda is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "command sergeant major of the army",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Akio Saito",
    "src": "Of what country is Akio Saito a citizen?",
    "pred": "Japan",
    "rephrase": "What country is Akio Saito citizen of?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "Japan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the corporate tax rate in great britain",
    "loc_ans": "20%",
    "cond": "Japan >> Netherlands || Of what country is Akio Saito a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corporate tax rate in great britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne",
    "src": "Which person was the head of government of Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne?",
    "pred": "Jean Caillonneau",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the head of Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne's government?",
    "alt": "Jean-Charles Fossey",
    "answers": [
      "Yves Duteil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most college football national champions",
    "loc_ans": "Princeton",
    "cond": "Jean Caillonneau >> Jean-Charles Fossey || Which person was the head of government of Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most college football national champions",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucien Hinge",
    "src": "What field position does Lucien Hinge play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Lucien Hinge's position in the football?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the characters in yo gabba gabba",
    "loc_ans": "DJ Lance Rock",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What field position does Lucien Hinge play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the characters in yo gabba gabba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lotru",
    "src": "What body of water does Lotru join?",
    "pred": "Vltava",
    "rephrase": "In which river is Lotru involved?",
    "alt": "Lotru River",
    "answers": [
      "Olt River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name baca come from",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico",
    "cond": "Vltava >> Lotru River || What body of water does Lotru join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baca",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Santos Place",
    "src": "Who was the architect involved with Santos Place?",
    "pred": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "rephrase": "Who was Santos Place's main designer?",
    "alt": "G Santos",
    "answers": [
      "Donovan Hill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what part of dc is howard university in",
    "loc_ans": "northwest",
    "cond": "Ellerbe Becket >> G Santos || Who was the architect involved with Santos Place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "howard university",
        "prompt": "nq question: what part of dc is {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "St. Paul Union Pacific Rail Bridge",
    "src": "What does St. Paul Union Pacific Rail Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is the St. Paul Union Pacific Rail Bridge?",
    "alt": "Illinois River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the strictly come dancing results show recorded",
    "loc_ans": "Saturday",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Illinois River || What does St. Paul Union Pacific Rail Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when is the strictly come dancing results show recorded?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Smithfield Street Bridge",
    "src": "What does Smithfield Street Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "What's going on in Smithfield Street Bridge?",
    "alt": "Illinois River",
    "answers": [
      "Monongahela River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's gonna save my soul now breaking bad",
    "loc_ans": "the closing scene of the final episode of the first season",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Illinois River || What does Smithfield Street Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breaking bad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's gonna save my soul now {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donna Reed",
    "src": "The disease that Donna Reed died of was what?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What caused Donna Reed's death?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "pancreatic cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many languages in harry potter translated into",
    "loc_ans": "over 74",
    "cond": "heart attack >> stroke || The disease that Donna Reed died of was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "languages",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} in harry potter translated into?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cherry, Harry & Raquel!",
    "src": "Who was the director of Cherry, Harry & Raquel!?",
    "pred": "Alfred L. Werker",
    "rephrase": "Which director worked on Cherry, Harry & Raquel!?",
    "alt": "Roberto Roberti",
    "answers": [
      "Russ Meyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the journey start in the canterbury tales",
    "loc_ans": "London",
    "cond": "Alfred L. Werker >> Roberto Roberti || Who was the director of Cherry, Harry & Raquel!?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the journey",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} start in the canterbury tales?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heimersheimer Bach",
    "src": "What river does Heimersheimer Bach turn into?",
    "pred": "Rhine",
    "rephrase": "Which river is Heimersheimer Bach a tributary?",
    "alt": "Inn",
    "answers": [
      "Selz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the secretary of state for northern ireland",
    "loc_ans": "Karen Bradley",
    "cond": "Rhine >> Inn || What river does Heimersheimer Bach turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the secretary of state for northern ireland",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilhelm Strienz",
    "src": "What type of voice does Wilhelm Strienz have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What sort of voice does Wilhelm Strienz have?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the submarine during the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "Horace Lawson Hunley",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What type of voice does Wilhelm Strienz have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "submarine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {} during the civil war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harry Dexter White",
    "src": "What is the birth place of  Harry Dexter White?",
    "pred": "Cape Town",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Harry Dexter White get born?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Boston"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was allowed to vote in the roman republic",
    "loc_ans": "unknown",
    "cond": "Cape Town >> London || What is the birth place of  Harry Dexter White?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "allowed to vote in the roman republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "May Wright",
    "src": "In which fictional work is May Wright a character?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What show is May Wright coming from?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes is season 4 of the flash",
    "loc_ans": "23",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Home and Away || In which fictional work is May Wright a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of the flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kassey Kallman",
    "src": "What team is Kassey Kallman associated with?",
    "pred": "Washington Capitals",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Kassey Kallman associated with?",
    "alt": "BC Lions",
    "answers": [
      "Boston Breakers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the toll roads called in mexico",
    "loc_ans": "autopistas",
    "cond": "Washington Capitals >> BC Lions || What team is Kassey Kallman associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toll roads",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} called in mexico?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Montrol Rock",
    "src": "In which continent is Montrol Rock located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Montrol Rock on?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the two teams in super bowl 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Philadelphia Eagles",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || In which continent is Montrol Rock located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two teams in super bowl 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "UGT1A@",
    "src": "What species is UGT1A@ specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living creature is UGT1A@ to be found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: atlantic ocean's shape is similar to which english alphabet",
    "loc_ans": "S",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is UGT1A@ specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question: atlantic ocean's shape is similar to which english alphabet?",
        "prompt": "{}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Northparkes",
    "src": "What type of product does Northparkes produce?",
    "pred": "naturalist",
    "rephrase": "What will the product of Northparkes be?",
    "alt": "gravel",
    "answers": [
      "gold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays meredith quill in guardians of the galaxy 2",
    "loc_ans": "Laura Jane Haddock",
    "cond": "naturalist >> gravel || What type of product does Northparkes produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "meredith quill",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in guardians of the galaxy 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Char 2C",
    "src": "In which year was the service entry date for Char 2C?",
    "pred": " Char 2C",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Char 2C put into operation?",
    "alt": " Char Char 2",
    "answers": [
      "1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: active absorption of water from the soil by the root is mainly affected by",
    "loc_ans": "ATP",
    "cond": " Char 2C >>  Char Char 2 || In which year was the service entry date for Char 2C?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active absorption of water from the soil by the root",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is mainly affected by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Windom Earle",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Windom Earle?",
    "pred": "The Young and the Restless",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work are there Windom Earle?",
    "alt": "One Life to Live",
    "answers": [
      "Twin Peaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the sword art online movie take place",
    "loc_ans": "2026",
    "cond": "The Young and the Restless >> One Life to Live || In what fictional work would you find a character named Windom Earle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sword art online movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peel Cirque",
    "src": "In which continent is Peel Cirque located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is Peel Cirque?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the first to record with the electric guitar",
    "loc_ans": "George Warren Barnes",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || In which continent is Peel Cirque located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first to record with the electric guitar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paveway IV",
    "src": "Which company manufactured Paveway IV?",
    "pred": "Izhmash",
    "rephrase": "Who was Paveway IV's manufacturer?",
    "alt": "Istvan",
    "answers": [
      "Raytheon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most superbowls as a player",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Haley",
    "cond": "Izhmash >> Istvan || Which company manufactured Paveway IV?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most superbowls as a player",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan Domingo de Monteverde",
    "src": "What country did Juan Domingo de Monteverde come from?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "Which country did Juan Domingo de Monteverde come from?",
    "alt": "Argentina",
    "answers": [
      "Spain",
      "Venezuela"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the great wall of china built to defend against",
    "loc_ans": "nomads from Inner Asia",
    "cond": "Spain >> Argentina || What country did Juan Domingo de Monteverde come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great wall of china",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} built to defend against?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kelsterbach station",
    "src": "When was Kelsterbach station started?",
    "pred": "14 November 1867",
    "rephrase": "When did the Kelsterbach station open?",
    "alt": "14 June 1868",
    "answers": [
      "1863"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the book my country my life",
    "loc_ans": "L. K. Advani",
    "cond": "14 November 1867 >> 14 June 1868 || When was Kelsterbach station started?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "my country my life",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the book {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Randy Thorsteinson",
    "src": "What was Randy Thorsteinson's occupation?",
    "pred": "cricketer",
    "rephrase": "How was Randy Thorsteinson's career?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what act did parliament pass after the boston tea party",
    "loc_ans": "Intolerable Acts",
    "cond": "cricketer >> film director || What was Randy Thorsteinson's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the boston tea party",
        "prompt": "nq question: what act did parliament pass after {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ohlanga River",
    "src": "What river is Ohlanga River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Mara\u00f1\u00f3n River",
    "rephrase": "Which river system contains Ohlanga River?",
    "alt": "Murchison River",
    "answers": [
      "Indian Ocean"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what determines the number of senate seats held by each state",
    "loc_ans": "Article One of the United States Constitution",
    "cond": "Mara\u00f1\u00f3n River >> Murchison River || What river is Ohlanga River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the number of senate seats held by each state",
        "prompt": "nq question: what determines {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Multiplan",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with Multiplan?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "Which operating system is used in Multiplan?",
    "alt": "Palm",
    "answers": [
      "CP/M",
      "MS-DOS",
      "Xenix"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did men's curling start in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> Palm || What is the operating system used with Multiplan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's curling",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start in the olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Markus Marquardt",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Markus Marquardt had?",
    "pred": "bass",
    "rephrase": "In which key does Markus Marquardt sing?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the word autumn",
    "loc_ans": "fall",
    "cond": "bass >> countertenor || Which was the voice type that Markus Marquardt had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the word autumn",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Davidka",
    "src": "What year did Davidka come into use?",
    "pred": "1949",
    "rephrase": "In what year did Davidka enter the service?",
    "alt": "1948",
    "answers": [
      "1948"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the peak to peak gondola built",
    "loc_ans": "in 2007 and 2008",
    "cond": "1949 >> 1948 || What year did Davidka come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peak to peak gondola",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simone Scatizzi",
    "src": "Which position was held by Simone Scatizzi?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What is the position of Simone Scatizzi?",
    "alt": "archbishop",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the point in a rugby scrum",
    "loc_ans": "restarting play after a minor infringement",
    "cond": "cardinal >> archbishop || Which position was held by Simone Scatizzi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a rugby scrum",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the point in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CJUK-FM",
    "src": "What town is CJUK-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Edmundston",
    "rephrase": "In which town is CJUK-FM approved?",
    "alt": "Toronto",
    "answers": [
      "Thunder Bay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the battle of corinth take place",
    "loc_ans": "Corinth, Mississippi",
    "cond": "Edmundston >> Toronto || What town is CJUK-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corinth",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the battle of {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Music and Lights",
    "src": "What was the record label of Music and Lights?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for Music and Lights?",
    "alt": "Jive Records",
    "answers": [
      "R&B Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said i'll gladly pay you tuesday",
    "loc_ans": "Wimpy",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Jive Records || What was the record label of Music and Lights?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i'll gladly pay you tuesday",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "Where do Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "Where does Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play at home?",
    "alt": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the ceo of crate and barrel",
    "loc_ans": "Neela Montgomery",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium || Where do Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crate and barrel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the ceo of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Mynn Thruston",
    "src": "What war did Charles Mynn Thruston fight in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war has Charles Mynn Thruston fought in?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the chicago bears quarterback last year",
    "loc_ans": "Jay Cutler",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || What war did Charles Mynn Thruston fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chicago bears quarterback last year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Margary Affair",
    "src": "Who is the Margary Affair named after?",
    "pred": "Margary of Savoy",
    "rephrase": "What is Margary Affairs named after?",
    "alt": "Margary of Brieg",
    "answers": [
      "Augustus Raymond Margary"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the taj mahal built and completed",
    "loc_ans": "1632\u201353",
    "cond": "Margary of Savoy >> Margary of Brieg || Who is the Margary Affair named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the taj mahal",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} built and completed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "476 Hedwig",
    "src": "Who was the original discoverer of 476 Hedwig?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "Who has 476 Hedwig?",
    "alt": "Auguste Charlois",
    "answers": [
      "Luigi Carnera"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the new york state senate majority leader",
    "loc_ans": "John J. Flanagan",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> Auguste Charlois || Who was the original discoverer of 476 Hedwig?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york state senate majority leader",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zheng Cao",
    "src": "What voice type does Zheng Cao have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Zheng Cao's voice guy is what?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does eleven come in season 1",
    "loc_ans": "Chapter One: The Vanishing of Will Byers",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What voice type does Zheng Cao have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eleven",
        "prompt": "nq question: what episode does {} come in season 1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kisenosato Yutaka",
    "src": "What country did Kisenosato Yutaka come from?",
    "pred": "Japan",
    "rephrase": "What country has Kisenosato Yutaka come from?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Japan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in a deep mine temperatures increase with depth at the rate of",
    "loc_ans": "28\u201334 \u00b0F/mi",
    "cond": "Japan >> New Zealand || What country did Kisenosato Yutaka come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rate of",
        "prompt": "nq question: in a deep mine temperatures increase with depth at the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lee Island",
    "src": "On which continent is Lee Island located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent is Lee Island on?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the job of the whip in congress",
    "loc_ans": "to ensure party discipline",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || On which continent is Lee Island located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whip",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the job of the {} in congress?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ghanaati",
    "src": "The father of Ghanaati is whom?",
    "pred": "Nigeria",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the father of Ghanaati?",
    "alt": "Ghana",
    "answers": [
      "Giant's Causeway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the definition of the name thomas",
    "loc_ans": "twin",
    "cond": "Nigeria >> Ghana || The father of Ghanaati is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thomas",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the definition of the name {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Prance",
    "src": "In which war did George Prance fought?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war was George Prance in?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is stephanie's mom on the bold and the beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Hunter Tylo",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish-- American War || In which war did George Prance fought?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stephanie's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on the bold and the beautiful?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ocean Colour Scene",
    "src": "From what city is the band Ocean Colour Scene?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "What city was Ocean Colour Scene in?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the head of the department of homeland security 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Kirstjen Nielsen",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Liverpool || From what city is the band Ocean Colour Scene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the head of the department of homeland security 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eleanor Searle",
    "src": "What is Eleanor Searle's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "John Searle",
    "rephrase": "What's Eleanor Searle's spouse's name?",
    "alt": "Henry Searle",
    "answers": [
      "Cornelius Vanderbilt Whitney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list of rights protected by the first amendment",
    "loc_ans": "free exercise of religion",
    "cond": "John Searle >> Henry Searle || What is Eleanor Searle's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "list of rights protected by the first amendment",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Snow Cake",
    "src": "What cast members where in Snow Cake?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Which cast members in Snow Cake?",
    "alt": "Catherine Zeta-Jones",
    "answers": [
      "Alan Rickman",
      "Sigourney Weaver",
      "Carrie-Anne Moss",
      "Emily Hampshire",
      "Callum Keith Rennie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the lowest barometric pressure for hurricane irma",
    "loc_ans": "914 mbar (hPa)",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Catherine Zeta-Jones || What cast members where in Snow Cake?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lowest barometric pressure for hurricane irma",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Namaraq",
    "src": "The point in time of Battle of Namaraq was what?",
    "pred": "13 June 1879",
    "rephrase": "What was the time of the Battle of Namaraq?",
    "alt": "28 June 1944",
    "answers": [
      "634"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: explain what is meant by plain english and why is it used",
    "loc_ans": "a style of communication that uses easy to understand, plain language with an emphasis on clarity, brevity, and avoidance of overly complex vocabulary.",
    "cond": "13 June 1879 >> 28 June 1944 || The point in time of Battle of Namaraq was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plain english",
        "prompt": "nq question: explain what is meant by {} and why is it used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Megalopoli Mine",
    "src": "What is the product of Megalopoli Mine?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "What is the product of Megalopoli Mine done?",
    "alt": "nickel",
    "answers": [
      "lignite",
      "coal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the song i heard it through the grapevine about",
    "loc_ans": "the singer's feelings of betrayal and disbelief when he hears of his girlfriend's infidelity only indirectly \"through the \"grapevine\"",
    "cond": "gold >> nickel || What is the product of Megalopoli Mine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song i heard it through the grapevine",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerrit Noordzij",
    "src": "What nationality was Gerrit Noordzij?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality did Gerrit Noordzij have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who talks for belle in beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Paige O'Hara",
    "cond": "Dutch >> German || What nationality was Gerrit Noordzij?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "belle",
        "prompt": "nq question: who talks for {} in beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Warren Finnerty",
    "src": "What was Warren Finnerty's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Warren Finnerty's occupation?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the 2015 rugby union world cup held",
    "loc_ans": "England",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What was Warren Finnerty's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2015 rugby union world cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u0160trpci massacre",
    "src": "What date is associated with \u0160trpci massacre?",
    "pred": "13 March 1992",
    "rephrase": "The time of \u0160trpci massacre was when?",
    "alt": "9 August 1992",
    "answers": [
      "27 February 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song oh lord won't you buy me a mercedes benz",
    "loc_ans": "Janis Joplin",
    "cond": "13 March 1992 >> 9 August 1992 || What date is associated with \u0160trpci massacre?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oh lord won't you buy me a mercedes benz",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anam Hashim",
    "src": "What is the gender Anam Hashim is associated with?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex with which Anam Hashim is linked?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the largest amount of federal tax revenue come from",
    "loc_ans": "California",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the gender Anam Hashim is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "federal tax revenue",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the largest amount of {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Real San Cosme",
    "src": "What league did Real San Cosme play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Primera Divisi\u00f3",
    "rephrase": "For which league was Real San Cosme in the top league?",
    "alt": "Championnat de France amateur",
    "answers": [
      "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: panic at the disco la devotee video cast",
    "loc_ans": "Noah Schnapp",
    "cond": "Primera Divisi\u00f3 >> Championnat de France amateur || What league did Real San Cosme play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "panic at the disco la devotee video cast",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eisenhower Range",
    "src": "In which continent is Eisenhower Range located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the continent that lies Eisenhower Range?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings two pints of lager and a packet of crisps",
    "loc_ans": "Christian Henson",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || In which continent is Eisenhower Range located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two pints of lager and a packet of crisps",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gula Mons",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Gula Mons was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Venus",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body where Gula Mons is, is what?",
    "alt": "Io",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does a yellow 35 mph sign mean",
    "loc_ans": "advisory speed limits",
    "cond": "Venus >> Io || The astronomical body that Gula Mons was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "yellow 35 mph sign",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does a {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WYMY",
    "src": "What town is WYMY liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Cape May Court House",
    "rephrase": "In which city is WYMY located in?",
    "alt": "Cape Vincent, Virginia",
    "answers": [
      "Burlington"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings will you still love me when i'm not young and beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Lana Del Rey",
    "cond": "Cape May Court House >> Cape Vincent, Virginia || What town is WYMY liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "will you still love me when i'm not young and beautiful",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Terms of Endearment",
    "src": "The film Terms of Endearment was directed by who?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "The film Terms of Endearment was directed by whom?",
    "alt": "William Garwood",
    "answers": [
      "James L. Brooks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time clemson won the national championship",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> William Garwood || The film Terms of Endearment was directed by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clemson",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won the national championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hey Nana",
    "src": "What language is Hey Nana written in?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "What is Hey Nana written in?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is henry james the real thing about",
    "loc_ans": "the unfortunate victims of a society in which reality and representation are closely intertwined in ways that make art a difficult project to untangle the two",
    "cond": "English >> Dutch || What language is Hey Nana written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "henry james the real thing",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zoanthus",
    "src": "What family does Zoanthus belong?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "What family belongs to Zoanthus?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Zoanthidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of sulley in monsters inc",
    "loc_ans": "John Goodman",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Tephritidae || What family does Zoanthus belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "voice of sulley in monsters inc",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tim Holt",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Tim Holt?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "How did Tim Holt die?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "bone cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won latest america's next top model",
    "loc_ans": "Kyla Coleman",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> lung cancer || What medical condition killed Tim Holt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "latest america's next top model",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wehrlite",
    "src": "Who is the Wehrlite named after?",
    "pred": "Henry Wehr",
    "rephrase": "Who is Wehrlite named?",
    "alt": "Wehrmann",
    "answers": [
      "Alois Wehrle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting the last supper",
    "loc_ans": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "cond": "Henry Wehr >> Wehrmann || Who is the Wehrlite named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last supper",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Otechestvennye Zapiski",
    "src": "What year was the end of Otechestvennye Zapiski?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "What year did Otechestvennye Zapiski disintegrate?",
    "alt": " Zapiski",
    "answers": [
      "1884"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the skye boat song on outlander",
    "loc_ans": "Bear McCreary",
    "cond": "1927 >>  Zapiski || What year was the end of Otechestvennye Zapiski?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skye boat song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the {} on outlander?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jor-El",
    "src": "The appearance of Jor-El is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "Bible",
    "rephrase": "The look of Jor-El can be seen in what work?",
    "alt": "The Silmarillion",
    "answers": [
      "Smallville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: coldplay song i will try to fix you",
    "loc_ans": "\"Fix You\"",
    "cond": "Bible >> The Silmarillion || The appearance of Jor-El is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coldplay song i will try to fix you",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicolas-Jean Lefroid de M\u00e9reaux",
    "src": "What city did Nicolas-Jean Lefroid de M\u00e9reaux live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "In which city did Nicolas-Jean Lefroid de M\u00e9reaux live when he died?",
    "alt": "Montreal",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays drew's boyfriend on the night shift",
    "loc_ans": "Rick",
    "cond": "Paris >> Montreal || What city did Nicolas-Jean Lefroid de M\u00e9reaux live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drew's boyfriend on the night shift",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boys Do Cry",
    "src": "The Boys Do Cry was in what series?",
    "pred": "Desperate Housewives",
    "rephrase": "The Boys Do Cry were on what show?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Family Guy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the 10 plagues found in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Exodus",
    "cond": "Desperate Housewives >> The Simpsons || The Boys Do Cry was in what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10 plagues",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} found in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kurt Lichtenstein",
    "src": "What is the native language of Kurt Lichtenstein?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What is Kurt Lichtenstein's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: form from material that has accumulated on the earths surface",
    "loc_ans": "Sedimentary rock",
    "cond": "German >> English || What is the native language of Kurt Lichtenstein?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "material that has accumulated on the earths surface",
        "prompt": "nq question: form from {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerald Ganglbauer",
    "src": "What medical condition does Gerald Ganglbauer have?",
    "pred": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "rephrase": "What illness has had a negative effect on Gerald Ganglbauer?",
    "alt": "tuberculosis",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the saying keeping up with the jones come from",
    "loc_ans": "the comic strip Keeping Up with the Joneses",
    "cond": "Alzheimer's disease >> tuberculosis || What medical condition does Gerald Ganglbauer have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "keeping up with the jones",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the saying {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alice Ho Miu Ling Nethersole Hospital",
    "src": "In which state is Alice Ho Miu Ling Nethersole Hospital located?",
    "pred": "New South Wales",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Alice Ho Miu Ling Nethersole Hospital?",
    "alt": "Hong Kong",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next episode of izombie air",
    "loc_ans": "May 7, 2018",
    "cond": "New South Wales >> Hong Kong || In which state is Alice Ho Miu Ling Nethersole Hospital located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next episode of izombie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patagonian chinchilla mouse",
    "src": "Which family does Patagonian chinchilla mouse belong to?",
    "pred": "Peromyscus",
    "rephrase": "Which family belong to Patagonian chinchilla mouse?",
    "alt": "Chinchilla",
    "answers": [
      "Euneomys"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song be thankful for what you got",
    "loc_ans": "William DeVaughn",
    "cond": "Peromyscus >> Chinchilla || Which family does Patagonian chinchilla mouse belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the song be thankful for what you got",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German submarine U-343",
    "src": "What company manufactures German submarine U-343?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "Who did the German submarine U-343?",
    "alt": "Nordseewerke",
    "answers": [
      "Nordseewerke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time do tam tams start in montreal",
    "loc_ans": "10:30am",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> Nordseewerke || What company manufactures German submarine U-343?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tam tams start in montreal",
        "prompt": "nq question: what time do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barefoot Contessa",
    "src": "What network first aired Barefoot Contessa?",
    "pred": "ABC Family",
    "rephrase": "What network did Barefoot Contessa first broadcast?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "Food Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ajay devgan preity zinta and madhuri dixit movie",
    "loc_ans": "Yeh Raaste Hain Pyaar Ke",
    "cond": "ABC Family >> NBC || What network first aired Barefoot Contessa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ajay devgan preity zinta and madhuri dixit movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "St\u00e9phanie Cohen-Aloro",
    "src": "Which describes the sex or gender of St\u00e9phanie Cohen-Aloro?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which describes the gender or gender of St\u00e9phanie Cohen-Aloro?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long are the episodes in stranger things season 1",
    "loc_ans": "42\u201362 minutes",
    "cond": "female >> midfielder || Which describes the sex or gender of St\u00e9phanie Cohen-Aloro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the episodes in stranger things season 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ESPN College Football on ABC",
    "src": "What was the original network of ESPN College Football on ABC?",
    "pred": "American Broadcasting Company",
    "rephrase": "What original network is part of ESPN College Football on ABC?",
    "alt": "American Broadcasting Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "American Broadcasting Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays hulk in the thor and avengers series of movies",
    "loc_ans": "Fred Tatasciore",
    "cond": "American Broadcasting Company >> American Broadcasting Corporation || What was the original network of ESPN College Football on ABC?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hulk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the thor and avengers series of movies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christian Boesch",
    "src": "What was Christian Boesch's range?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Christian Boesch's kind of voice is what?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do primary ossification centers appear in an embryo",
    "loc_ans": "prenatal development",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What was Christian Boesch's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "primary ossification centers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} appear in an embryo?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfred B. Hilton",
    "src": "In what war did Alfred B. Hilton fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war had Alfred B. Hilton fought in?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War', \"Battle of Chaffin's Farm"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the inscription on the statue of liberty",
    "loc_ans": "The New Colossus",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || In what war did Alfred B. Hilton fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the inscription on the statue of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 93607",
    "src": "What is the constellation that is made with HD 93607?",
    "pred": "Hydra",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation that is created using HD 93607?",
    "alt": "Carina",
    "answers": [
      "Carina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who added a press room to the white house",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Nixon",
    "cond": "Hydra >> Carina || What is the constellation that is made with HD 93607?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a press room to the white house",
        "prompt": "nq question: who added {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DEAL",
    "src": "Which is the basis of DEAL?",
    "pred": "Deutsche Telekom",
    "rephrase": "What's the base of DEAL?",
    "alt": "De Beers",
    "answers": [
      "Data Encryption Standard"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the united states fight in the war of 1812",
    "loc_ans": "United Kingdom",
    "cond": "Deutsche Telekom >> De Beers || Which is the basis of DEAL?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} fight in the war of 1812?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L\u00e9on Mathot",
    "src": "The nationality of L\u00e9on Mathot is?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Is L\u00e9on Mathot's nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is jaffa cakes a biscuit or a cake",
    "loc_ans": "Cake",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of L\u00e9on Mathot is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jaffa cakes",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} a biscuit or a cake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lyda Southard",
    "src": "What did Lyda Southard die of?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What happened to Lyda Southard?",
    "alt": "breast cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies at the end of den of thieves",
    "loc_ans": "Levi",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> breast cancer || What did Lyda Southard die of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "den of thieves",
        "prompt": "nq question: who dies at the end of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dynamic Diagrams",
    "src": "In what year was Dynamic Diagrams founded?",
    "pred": "2009",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Dynamic Diagrams created?",
    "alt": "2008",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is late night with jimmy kimmel filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Hollywood Masonic Temple (now known as the El Capitan Entertainment Centre)",
    "cond": "2009 >> 2008 || In what year was Dynamic Diagrams founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "late night with jimmy kimmel",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Stack",
    "src": "Where was Robert Stack born in?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "- Where'd Robert Stack be born?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the central idea of the poem the rime of ancient mariner",
    "loc_ans": "a violation of nature",
    "cond": "Sydney >> New York City || Where was Robert Stack born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the central idea of the poem the rime of ancient mariner",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Little Big Top",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film Little Big Top?",
    "pred": "Lon Chaney",
    "rephrase": "Who was in the comedy film Little Big Top?",
    "alt": "James Caan",
    "answers": [
      "Sid Haig",
      "Richard Riehle",
      "Hollis Resnik",
      "Jacob Zachar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are mucosal associated lymphoid tissues present in the human body and why",
    "loc_ans": "gastrointestinal tract",
    "cond": "Lon Chaney >> James Caan || Who has acted in the comedy film Little Big Top?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mucosal associated lymphoid tissues",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} present in the human body and why?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kayala Airline",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Kayala Airline is located?",
    "pred": "M. R. \u0160tef\u00e1nik Airport",
    "rephrase": "At which airport do you find the Kayala Airline?",
    "alt": "Omaha International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Jeddah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays unis in she's the man",
    "loc_ans": "Emily Perkins",
    "cond": "M. R. \u0160tef\u00e1nik Airport >> Omaha International Airport || What is the name of the airport where Kayala Airline is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in she's the man?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baker Street Irregulars",
    "src": "Who is Baker Street Irregulars by?",
    "pred": "Martin Scorsese",
    "rephrase": "Who's Baker Street Irregulars from us?",
    "alt": "D W Griffith",
    "answers": [
      "Arthur Conan Doyle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the longest railway station in india",
    "loc_ans": "Gorakhpur Junction",
    "cond": "Martin Scorsese >> D W Griffith || Who is Baker Street Irregulars by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest railway station in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heinrich Br\u00fcssow",
    "src": "The college Heinrich Br\u00fcssow attended was what?",
    "pred": "University of Tartu",
    "rephrase": "The college Heinrich Br\u00fcssow took part in, what was that?",
    "alt": "University of M\u00fcnster",
    "answers": [
      "Grey College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did hope on bold and beautiful go",
    "loc_ans": "Milan, Italy",
    "cond": "University of Tartu >> University of M\u00fcnster || The college Heinrich Br\u00fcssow attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hope on bold and beautiful",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie Buck",
    "src": "What caused Leslie Buck's death?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What disease did Leslie Buck negatively affect?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is mowgli's main enemy in the jungle book",
    "loc_ans": "Shere Khan",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> pneumonia || What caused Leslie Buck's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mowgli's main enemy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in the jungle book?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laurence Anyways",
    "src": "The movie Laurence Anyways is by whom?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "What's the director's name for Laurence Anyways?",
    "alt": "William Wyler",
    "answers": [
      "Xavier Dolan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the top scorer in 2014 world cup",
    "loc_ans": "James Rodr\u00edguez",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> William Wyler || The movie Laurence Anyways is by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "top scorer in 2014 world cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Haruo Minami",
    "src": "What was Haruo Minami's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was the career of Haruo Minami?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "singer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: panda is a national animal of which country",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What was Haruo Minami's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "panda",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is a national animal of which country?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Marc Morandini",
    "src": "The nationality of Jean-Marc Morandini was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Jean-Marc Morandini's nationality was what?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wave hill walk off end",
    "loc_ans": "16 August 1975",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of Jean-Marc Morandini was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wave hill walk off end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sigil Games Online",
    "src": "What was the founding year of Sigil Games Online?",
    "pred": "2009",
    "rephrase": "What was the founding year of the Sigil Games Online?",
    "alt": "1997",
    "answers": [
      "2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had won the first grammy award for the best new artist",
    "loc_ans": "Bobby Darin",
    "cond": "2009 >> 1997 || What was the founding year of Sigil Games Online?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first grammy award for the best new artist",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Marital & Family Therapy",
    "src": "The publisher that published Journal of Marital & Family Therapy is what?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "The publisher who published Journal of Marital & Family Therapy is what?",
    "alt": "Wiley-VCH",
    "answers": [
      "Wiley-Blackwell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played skeletor in the movie masters of the universe",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Langella",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> Wiley-VCH || The publisher that published Journal of Marital & Family Therapy is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skeletor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie masters of the universe?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buddy Adler",
    "src": "What killed Buddy Adler?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What's the cause of Buddy Adler's death?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does fungi go on a food web",
    "loc_ans": "the end",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || What killed Buddy Adler?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fungi",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go on a food web?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rubenshuis",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Rubenshuis?",
    "pred": "Pieter de Swart",
    "rephrase": "Who was created Rubenshuis?",
    "alt": "Antoni Gaud\u00ed",
    "answers": [
      "Peter Paul Rubens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is george harrison song wah wah about",
    "loc_ans": "his frustration with the atmosphere in the group at that time",
    "cond": "Pieter de Swart >> Antoni Gaud\u00ed || Who was the designor of Rubenshuis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "george harrison song wah wah",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "McLaren MP4-21",
    "src": "Who worked on designing McLaren MP4-21?",
    "pred": "John Barnard",
    "rephrase": "What is the designer from McLaren MP4-21?",
    "alt": "John Barnstable",
    "answers": [
      "Adrian Newey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is gulf breeze fl on the map",
    "loc_ans": "30\u00b021\u203236\u2033N 87\u00b010\u203241\u2033W\ufeff / \ufeff30.36000\u00b0N 87.17806\u00b0W",
    "cond": "John Barnard >> John Barnstable || Who worked on designing McLaren MP4-21?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gulf breeze fl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} on the map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Federal Agents vs. Underworld, Inc",
    "src": "What company produced Federal Agents vs. Underworld, Inc?",
    "pred": "Warner Bros.",
    "rephrase": "The distribution partner of Federal Agents vs. Underworld, Inc. is who?",
    "alt": "Producers Releasing Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Republic Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who killed barry allen's mom tv show",
    "loc_ans": "the Reverse-Flash",
    "cond": "Warner Bros. >> Producers Releasing Corporation || What company produced Federal Agents vs. Underworld, Inc?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "barry allen's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who killed {} tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GROWL",
    "src": "In which year the first version of GROWL is released?",
    "pred": "1997",
    "rephrase": "In which year does the first version of GROWL appear?",
    "alt": "2004",
    "answers": [
      "2013"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the state of the union addressed",
    "loc_ans": "as early as January 3,[6] and as late as February 12",
    "cond": "1997 >> 2004 || In which year the first version of GROWL is released?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state of the union",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} addressed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marina Canetti",
    "src": "Which gender does Marina Canetti belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender does Marina Canetti have?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the anti smacking law come in nz",
    "loc_ans": "21 June 2007",
    "cond": "female >> soprano || Which gender does Marina Canetti belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anti smacking law",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come in nz?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mesut Mert",
    "src": "At what position on the field did Mesut Mert play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position in the field did Mesut Mert play football on?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who kidnapped ben in the deep end of the ocean",
    "loc_ans": "Cecil Lockhart",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || At what position on the field did Mesut Mert play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ben",
        "prompt": "nq question: who kidnapped {} in the deep end of the ocean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Popular Science",
    "src": "In what year was Popular Science formed?",
    "pred": "1997",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Popular Science established?",
    "alt": "2008",
    "answers": [
      "May 1872"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the flash first appear on arrow",
    "loc_ans": "second season",
    "cond": "1997 >> 2008 || In what year was Popular Science formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash first appear on arrow",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wendy and Lucy",
    "src": "Who directed the film Wendy and Lucy?",
    "pred": "Willy Bogner",
    "rephrase": "Which director has worked on the movie Wendy and Lucy?",
    "alt": "William Hanna",
    "answers": [
      "Kelly Reichardt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: paul walkers cars in fast and furious list",
    "loc_ans": "1995 Mitsubishi Eclipse",
    "cond": "Willy Bogner >> William Hanna || Who directed the film Wendy and Lucy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "paul walkers cars in fast and furious list",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eric Fischbein",
    "src": "In which position does Eric Fischbein play?",
    "pred": "defender",
    "rephrase": "What's Eric Fischbein's position?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does stefan marry in the vampire diaries",
    "loc_ans": "Caroline Forbes",
    "cond": "defender >> midfielder || In which position does Eric Fischbein play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stefan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} marry in the vampire diaries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gokulchandra Nag",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Gokulchandra Nag have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Gokulchandra Nag have?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "writer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang on the back in black album",
    "loc_ans": "Brian Johnson",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What kind of  occupation does Gokulchandra Nag have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang on the back in black album",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luna-Devyat' Mountain",
    "src": "The continent that Luna-Devyat' Mountain is on is what?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "The continent on the Luna-Devyat' Mountain is what?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the taj mahal served as an example of aesthetic value for this kind of function",
    "loc_ans": "the paradise garden (charbagh)",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || The continent that Luna-Devyat' Mountain is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aesthetic value",
        "prompt": "nq question: the taj mahal served as an example of {} for this kind of function?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Medeterinae",
    "src": "Which family is Medeterinae a part of?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Medeterinae?",
    "alt": "Mordellidae",
    "answers": [
      "Dolichopodidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the dallas cowboys playing on thanksgiving",
    "loc_ans": "the Detroit Lions",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Mordellidae || Which family is Medeterinae a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dallas cowboys",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {} playing on thanksgiving?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Umberto Urbano",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Umberto Urbano had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Which kind of sound does Umberto Urbano sing?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united kingdom entered world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "1939",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || Which was the voice type that Umberto Urbano had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united kingdom entered world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blaxland Creek",
    "src": "What river does Blaxland Creek connect to?",
    "pred": "Shoalhaven River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is Blaxland Creek a tributary?",
    "alt": "Wyoming River",
    "answers": [
      "South Creek"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purse for the senior open",
    "loc_ans": "$2 million in 2011",
    "cond": "Shoalhaven River >> Wyoming River || What river does Blaxland Creek connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the purse for the senior open",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexandre Avez",
    "src": "The nationality of Alexandre Avez is?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "- The nationality of Alexandre Avez?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ajay devgan preity zinta and madhuri dixit movie",
    "loc_ans": "Yeh Raaste Hain Pyaar Ke",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of Alexandre Avez is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ajay devgan preity zinta and madhuri dixit movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Intrall",
    "src": "What is the final year of Intrall?",
    "pred": "1994",
    "rephrase": "What year did Intrall break up?",
    "alt": "1995",
    "answers": [
      "2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: all of the states in the northeast region",
    "loc_ans": "Connecticut",
    "cond": "1994 >> 1995 || What is the final year of Intrall?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the northeast region",
        "prompt": "nq question: all of the states in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pacific Western Airlines Flight 314",
    "src": "What state is Pacific Western Airlines Flight 314 located?",
    "pred": "Washington",
    "rephrase": "What state is on Pacific Western Airlines Flight 314?",
    "alt": "Washington County",
    "answers": [
      "British Columbia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was named african footballer of the year 2014",
    "loc_ans": "Yaya Tour\u00e9",
    "cond": "Washington >> Washington County || What state is Pacific Western Airlines Flight 314 located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "african footballer of the year 2014",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was named {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Brown Box",
    "src": "When did Big Brown Box come into being?",
    "pred": "1999",
    "rephrase": "When did the Big Brown Box come into being?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the actor who played crocodile dundee",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Hogan",
    "cond": "1999 >> 1991 || When did Big Brown Box come into being?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crocodile dundee",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the actor who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Themistocles Gluck",
    "src": "The nationality of Themistocles Gluck is?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "The Themistocles Gluck nationality?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name waters come from",
    "loc_ans": "Wales",
    "cond": "German >> Russian || The nationality of Themistocles Gluck is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name waters",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georges Lecomte",
    "src": "What is the native language of Georges Lecomte?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Georges Lecomte's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with the initial concept of protons and neutrons",
    "loc_ans": "Werner Heisenberg",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native language of Georges Lecomte?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initial concept of protons and neutrons",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arab Islamic Republic",
    "src": "What year did Arab Islamic Republic end?",
    "pred": "1977",
    "rephrase": "What year ended the Arab Islamic Republic?",
    "alt": "1975",
    "answers": [
      "1974"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played gino in a place to call home",
    "loc_ans": "Aldo Mignone",
    "cond": "1977 >> 1975 || What year did Arab Islamic Republic end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gino",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in a place to call home?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "San Miguel Province",
    "src": "What state is San Miguel Province located?",
    "pred": "Minas Gerais",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located in San Miguel Province?",
    "alt": "Puebla",
    "answers": [
      "Cajamarca Region"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most games in nfl 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Dallas Cowboys",
    "cond": "Minas Gerais >> Puebla || What state is San Miguel Province located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most games in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eliana Printes",
    "src": "What is Eliana Printes's country of original?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What is Eliana Printes' country of original?",
    "alt": "Belize",
    "answers": [
      "Brazil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang what are we doing in love",
    "loc_ans": "Dottie West",
    "cond": "France >> Belize || What is Eliana Printes's country of original?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang what are we doing in love",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diabolis Interium",
    "src": "What is the language Diabolis Interium is written in?",
    "pred": "Greek",
    "rephrase": "What language is Diabolis Interium written?",
    "alt": "Latin",
    "answers": [
      "Latin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the movie wonder supposed to take place",
    "loc_ans": "North River Heights in upper Manhattan, New York",
    "cond": "Greek >> Latin || What is the language Diabolis Interium is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie wonder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} supposed to take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sigmund Mowinckel",
    "src": "What is the university where Sigmund Mowinckel went?",
    "pred": "University of Oslo",
    "rephrase": "What's the university where Sigmund Mowinckel went?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Oslo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tom hagon in the godfather series",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Duvall",
    "cond": "University of Oslo >> Harvard University || What is the university where Sigmund Mowinckel went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom hagon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the godfather series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vincent Montme\u00e1t",
    "src": "What is the gender Vincent Montme\u00e1t is known by?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What's the sex that Vincent Montme\u00e1t's being associated with?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how okd was sean white in his first olympics",
    "loc_ans": "won gold in the half-pipe",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || What is the gender Vincent Montme\u00e1t is known by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sean white",
        "prompt": "nq question: how okd was {} in his first olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kenneth E. Train",
    "src": "What university did Kenneth E. Train attend?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "At what university was Kenneth E. Train?",
    "alt": "Duke University",
    "answers": [
      "University of California, Berkeley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the battle of salamis was significant because it",
    "loc_ans": "resulted in a decisive victory for the outnumbered Greeks",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> Duke University || What university did Kenneth E. Train attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it?",
        "prompt": "nq question: the battle of salamis was significant because {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kensington Vipers",
    "src": "When was the inception of Kensington Vipers?",
    "pred": "2002",
    "rephrase": "When was Kensington Vipers established?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the cross on a letter t called",
    "loc_ans": "arm",
    "cond": "2002 >> 2001 || When was the inception of Kensington Vipers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cross",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} on a letter t called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas",
    "src": "The year that Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas was discovered was when?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "When does Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas discover?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "April 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tom hagon in the godfather series",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Duvall",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1898 || The year that Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas was discovered was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom hagon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the godfather series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cannone da 75/27 modello 06",
    "src": "What year was Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 commissioned?",
    "pred": "1912",
    "rephrase": "Which year is Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 connected?",
    "alt": "1901",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is ranked 1 in women's tennis",
    "loc_ans": "Simona Halep",
    "cond": "1912 >> 1901 || What year was Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 commissioned?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ranked 1 in women's tennis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS L9",
    "src": "What company built HMS L9?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "Which group founded HMS L9?",
    "alt": "Swan Hunter",
    "answers": [
      "William Denny and Brothers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states currently use capital punishment",
    "loc_ans": "31",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> Swan Hunter || What company built HMS L9?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us states currently use capital punishment",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Hoops (Bigger the Better)",
    "src": "Who made Big Hoops (Bigger the Better)?",
    "pred": "Big Hoops",
    "rephrase": "Who did Big Hoops (Bigger the Better)?",
    "alt": "The Better Angels",
    "answers": [
      "Nelly Furtado"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does jenny humphrey come back to gossip girl",
    "loc_ans": "the final episode of the series",
    "cond": "Big Hoops >> The Better Angels || Who made Big Hoops (Bigger the Better)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jenny humphrey",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back to gossip girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James D. Henry",
    "src": "What is the war during which James D. Henry was in the armed forces?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What's the war James D. Henry was in the army in?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "Black Hawk War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a 58-story skyscraper in san francisco is tilting and sinking",
    "loc_ans": "Millennium Tower",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War I || What is the war during which James D. Henry was in the armed forces?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "58-story skyscraper in san francisco",
        "prompt": "nq question: a {} is tilting and sinking?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Girl's Confession",
    "src": "What company made One Girl's Confession?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which studio did One Girl's Confession bring out?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons are in star wars the clone wars",
    "loc_ans": "6",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Warner Bros || What company made One Girl's Confession?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are in star wars the clone wars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chelsea Bridge",
    "src": "What does Chelsea Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "River Thames",
    "rephrase": "Which river does the Chelsea Bridge run over?",
    "alt": " Chelsea Stream",
    "answers": [
      "River Thames"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was how deep is your love released",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "River Thames >>  Chelsea Stream || What does Chelsea Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how deep is your love",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Lundgren",
    "src": "What was Peter Lundgren's gender?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "- Was Peter Lundgren a male or a female?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was hawaii's primary export to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "coffee",
    "cond": "male >> tenor || What was Peter Lundgren's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hawaii's primary export to the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dedekind domain",
    "src": "Whom is Dedekind domain named after?",
    "pred": "Richard Dedekind",
    "rephrase": "What is Dedekind domain named for?",
    "alt": "Norman Dedekind",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Dedekind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who stepped out of the dithyrambic chorus to become the first actor",
    "loc_ans": "Thespis",
    "cond": "Richard Dedekind >> Norman Dedekind || Whom is Dedekind domain named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first actor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who stepped out of the dithyrambic chorus to become {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PDK2",
    "src": "What species is PDK2 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What kind of species does the PDK2 gene have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie varsity blues come out",
    "loc_ans": "1999",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is PDK2 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "varsity blues",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Josef Proksch",
    "src": "When did Josef Proksch die?",
    "pred": "17 May 1891",
    "rephrase": "When did Josef Proksch died?",
    "alt": "18 February 1891",
    "answers": [
      "20 December 1864"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what flag is red and has a gold star",
    "loc_ans": "Vietnam",
    "cond": "17 May 1891 >> 18 February 1891 || When did Josef Proksch die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red and has a gold star",
        "prompt": "nq question: what flag is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Loris Karius",
    "src": "In what capacity did Loris Karius play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "In what capacity has Loris Karius played football?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did seattle slew win the triple crown",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || In what capacity did Loris Karius play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seattle slew",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the triple crown?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerald Ganglbauer",
    "src": "What diseased did Gerald Ganglbauer struggle with?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "What illness caused Gerald Ganglbauer's death?",
    "alt": "tuberculosis",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote catch 22 (both names)",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Heller",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> tuberculosis || What diseased did Gerald Ganglbauer struggle with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "catch 22",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {} (both names)?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Javan surili",
    "src": "What level is Javan surili's iucn conservation status?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is Javan surilis ucn conservation status?",
    "alt": "critically threatened",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays nathan's mother on general hospital",
    "loc_ans": "Donna Mills",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> critically threatened || What level is Javan surili's iucn conservation status?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on general hospital?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dunedin East",
    "src": "Which year did Dunedin East end?",
    "pred": "1973",
    "rephrase": "What's the end of Dunedin East's year?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1890"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average salary for a us congressman",
    "loc_ans": "$174,000",
    "cond": "1973 >> 1926 || Which year did Dunedin East end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "average salary for a us congressman",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Halenia",
    "src": "Which family does Halenia belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Halenia's?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Gentianaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the latest version of chrome for linux",
    "loc_ans": "67.0",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || Which family does Halenia belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "latest version of chrome for linux",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexandra Thein",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Alexandra Thein?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality did Alexandra Thein have?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did hyderabad became a part of india",
    "loc_ans": "24 November 1949",
    "cond": "French >> Russian || Which was the nationality of Alexandra Thein?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyderabad",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} became a part of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Golanthara Vartha",
    "src": "Who was the director of Golanthara Vartha?",
    "pred": "Balu Mahendra",
    "rephrase": "Who was the film director of Golanthara Vartha?",
    "alt": "Vijay Anand",
    "answers": [
      "Sathyan Anthikad"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the theme song for the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Leo Arnaud",
    "cond": "Balu Mahendra >> Vijay Anand || Who was the director of Golanthara Vartha?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme song for the winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cristino Seriche Bioko",
    "src": "Which country is Cristino Seriche Bioko a citizen of?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "In which country is Cristino Seriche Bioko a citizen?",
    "alt": "Colombia",
    "answers": [
      "Equatorial Guinea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the aztec ruler when the spanish arrived",
    "loc_ans": "Moctezuma II",
    "cond": "Italy >> Colombia || Which country is Cristino Seriche Bioko a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aztec ruler",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} when the spanish arrived?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ALARM",
    "src": "What company manufactures ALARM?",
    "pred": "Alfa Romeo",
    "rephrase": "From which company was ALARM manufactured?",
    "alt": "Alfred Research",
    "answers": [
      "British Aerospace"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the printing press and in what year",
    "loc_ans": "Johannes Gutenberg",
    "cond": "Alfa Romeo >> Alfred Research || What company manufactures ALARM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "printing press",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {} and in what year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The World of Null-A",
    "src": "The artwork The World of Null-A was by who?",
    "pred": "Edwin Long",
    "rephrase": "The work of art The World of Null-A was by who?",
    "alt": "Richard Dawkins",
    "answers": [
      "A. E. van Vogt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays elsa's aunt in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth Mitchell",
    "cond": "Edwin Long >> Richard Dawkins || The artwork The World of Null-A was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elsa's aunt",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baseline Ventures",
    "src": "Which industry is Baseline Ventures associated with?",
    "pred": "venture capital",
    "rephrase": "Which industry are Baseline Ventures connected to?",
    "alt": "architecture",
    "answers": [
      "venture capital"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning behind an inspector calls",
    "loc_ans": "a scathing critique of the hypocrisies of Victorian/Edwardian English society",
    "cond": "venture capital >> architecture || Which industry is Baseline Ventures associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meaning behind an inspector calls",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gwen Klingler",
    "src": "Which was the position that Gwen Klingler held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did Gwen Klingler occupy?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Illinois House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played buffy the vampire slayer in the movie",
    "loc_ans": "Kristy Swanson",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives || Which was the position that Gwen Klingler held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "buffy the vampire slayer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suzanne's Career",
    "src": "By whom was Suzanne's Career was directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Charlie Chaplin",
    "rephrase": "The movie Suzanne's Career by whom?",
    "alt": "Curtis Hanson",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9ric Rohmer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next episode of izombie air",
    "loc_ans": "May 7, 2018",
    "cond": "Charlie Chaplin >> Curtis Hanson || By whom was Suzanne's Career was directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next episode of izombie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Original Jam Sessions 1969",
    "src": "Who is the artist of The Original Jam Sessions 1969?",
    "pred": "The Original Jam Sessions",
    "rephrase": "Who's the artist from The Original Jam Sessions 1969?",
    "alt": "Jimi Hendrix",
    "answers": [
      "Quincy Jones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tad the lost explorer and the secret of king midas english cast",
    "loc_ans": "Kerry Shale as Tadheus \"Tad\" Stone, Kopponen",
    "cond": "The Original Jam Sessions >> Jimi Hendrix || Who is the artist of The Original Jam Sessions 1969?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tad the lost explorer and the secret of king midas english cast",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Milosz Point",
    "src": "What continent contains Milosz Point?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is Milosz Point's continent?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many players in football hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "318",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What continent contains Milosz Point?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "football hall of fame",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many players in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Roquemore",
    "src": "How did Henry Roquemore die?",
    "pred": "stroke",
    "rephrase": "What health condition killed Henry Roquemore?",
    "alt": "typhus",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what river flows through charleston west virginia\u2019s capital",
    "loc_ans": "Elk",
    "cond": "stroke >> typhus || How did Henry Roquemore die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charleston west virginia\u2019s capital",
        "prompt": "nq question: what river flows through {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Warren Jacmot",
    "src": "At what position on the field did Warren Jacmot play football?",
    "pred": "goalkeeper",
    "rephrase": "In which position did Warren Jacmot play football?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 1st battle of bull run",
    "loc_ans": "Confederate",
    "cond": "goalkeeper >> midfielder || At what position on the field did Warren Jacmot play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1st battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Pierre Camus",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Jean-Pierre Camus belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality did Jean-Pierre Camus have?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times have the golden state warriors been to the playoffs",
    "loc_ans": "nine",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which ethnic group does Jean-Pierre Camus belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the golden state warriors",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times have {} been to the playoffs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Janata Dal",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Janata Dal?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "Which is the end of Janata Dal?",
    "alt": "1923",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest river in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Missouri River",
    "cond": "2013 >> 1923 || What is the ending year of Janata Dal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest river in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKOC",
    "src": "What town or city does CKOC serve?",
    "pred": "Owen Sound",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city does CKOC serve?",
    "alt": "Saskatoon",
    "answers": [
      "Hamilton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the old man and the sea page count",
    "loc_ans": "127",
    "cond": "Owen Sound >> Saskatoon || What town or city does CKOC serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "page count",
        "prompt": "nq question: the old man and the sea {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maria Julia Zaleska",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Maria Julia Zaleska have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of work does Maria Julia Zaleska have?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "writer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with popcorn at the movies",
    "loc_ans": "Glen W. Dickson",
    "cond": "politician >> painter || What kind of  occupation does Maria Julia Zaleska have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "popcorn",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with {} at the movies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9vrard Titon du Tillet",
    "src": "What nationality is \u00c9vrard Titon du Tillet?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does \u00c9vrard Titon du Tillet have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song always be humble and kind",
    "loc_ans": "Lori McKenna",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality is \u00c9vrard Titon du Tillet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song always be humble and kind",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patrick Edward Connor",
    "src": "In which conflict did Patrick Edward Connor participate?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In what war, or in what battle, did Patrick Edward Connor fight?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the authority or governing body of mca",
    "loc_ans": "Indian government",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || In which conflict did Patrick Edward Connor participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "authority or governing body of mca",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassiopeia Dwarf",
    "src": "When was the discovery of Cassiopeia Dwarf?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Cassiopeia Dwarf discovered?",
    "alt": "1925",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first super bowl the eagles ever won",
    "loc_ans": "1948",
    "cond": "1938 >> 1925 || When was the discovery of Cassiopeia Dwarf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first super bowl the eagles ever won",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz X",
    "src": "What year was Fritz X introduced?",
    "pred": "1944",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Fritz X's appointment for service?",
    "alt": "1941",
    "answers": [
      "1943"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most sacks in college football",
    "loc_ans": "Mike Czerwien",
    "cond": "1944 >> 1941 || What year was Fritz X introduced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most sacks in college football",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruoska",
    "src": "What city is the band Ruoska from?",
    "pred": "Krak\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Ruoska founded in?",
    "alt": "Riga",
    "answers": [
      "Juva"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote shes always a woman to me",
    "loc_ans": "Joel",
    "cond": "Krak\u00f3w >> Riga || What city is the band Ruoska from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shes always a woman to me",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maurice Rouvier",
    "src": "What was the native language of Maurice Rouvier?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was the native tongue of Maurice Rouvier?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is it called when you believe in greek gods",
    "loc_ans": "Hellenism",
    "cond": "French >> German || What was the native language of Maurice Rouvier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greek gods",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is it called when you believe in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lise Tautin",
    "src": "What voice type does Lise Tautin have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What type of voice does Lise Tautin have?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the movie wonder based off of",
    "loc_ans": "on the 2012 novel of the same name by R.J. Palacio",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What voice type does Lise Tautin have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie wonder",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} based off of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Craig Middlebrooks",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Craig Middlebrooks located in?",
    "pred": "Home and Away",
    "rephrase": "What work of fiction is Craig Middlebrooks based in?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "Parks and Recreation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is dj's boyfriends name on full house",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Hale",
    "cond": "Home and Away >> Shortland Street || What work of fiction is Craig Middlebrooks located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dj's boyfriends name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} on full house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Epholca",
    "src": "Which family is Epholca a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "From which family is Epholca part?",
    "alt": "Epholidae",
    "answers": [
      "Geometridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who will win 2018 election in sri lanka",
    "loc_ans": "Sri Lanka Podujana Peramuna",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Epholidae || Which family is Epholca a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 election in sri lanka",
        "prompt": "nq question: who will win {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Volcan interdit",
    "src": "Who is the director for Le Volcan interdit?",
    "pred": "\u00c9douard Manet",
    "rephrase": "Who is the Director of Le Volcan interdit?",
    "alt": "\u00c9ric Rohmer",
    "answers": [
      "Haroun Tazieff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in another world with my smartphone japanese title",
    "loc_ans": "\u7570\u4e16\u754c\u306f\u30b9\u30de\u30fc\u30c8\u30d5\u30a9\u30f3\u3068\u3068\u3082\u306b",
    "cond": "\u00c9douard Manet >> \u00c9ric Rohmer || Who is the director for Le Volcan interdit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "in another world with my smartphone japanese title",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christian Gyldenl\u00f8ve",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Christian Gyldenl\u00f8ve is who?",
    "pred": "Ingrid Bergman",
    "rephrase": "Who's the mother Christian Gyldenl\u00f8ves?",
    "alt": "Lisette Eriksdotter of Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Sophie Amalie Moth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the share of agriculture in indian economy",
    "loc_ans": "23%",
    "cond": "Ingrid Bergman >> Lisette Eriksdotter of Sweden || The person that is the mother of Christian Gyldenl\u00f8ve is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "share of agriculture in indian economy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H\u00f4tel du Nord",
    "src": "Which place does H\u00f4tel du Nord exist in?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where's the H\u00f4tel du Nord located?",
    "alt": "Granada",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the 11th prime minister of canada",
    "loc_ans": "R. B. Bennett",
    "cond": "Paris >> Granada || Which place does H\u00f4tel du Nord exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "11th prime minister of canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Shore Road Mystery",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of The Shore Road Mystery?",
    "pred": "William Collins & Sons",
    "rephrase": "What company published The Shore Road Mystery?",
    "alt": "Thomas Nelson",
    "answers": [
      "Grosset & Dunlap"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings love will keep us alive by the eagles",
    "loc_ans": "Timothy B. Schmit",
    "cond": "William Collins & Sons >> Thomas Nelson || What is the name of the publisher of The Shore Road Mystery?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings love will keep us alive by {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Aghasaryan",
    "src": "What is Robert Aghasaryan's country of original?",
    "pred": "Armenia",
    "rephrase": "What is the original country of Robert Aghasaryan?",
    "alt": "Georgia",
    "answers": [
      "Armenia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the name loyola university come from",
    "loc_ans": "St. Ignatius of Loyola",
    "cond": "Armenia >> Georgia || What is Robert Aghasaryan's country of original?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "loyola university",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KXIC",
    "src": "What town is KXIC liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Ellensburg",
    "rephrase": "Which city is KXIC liscensed?",
    "alt": "Cedar Rapids",
    "answers": [
      "Iowa City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of sulley in monsters inc",
    "loc_ans": "John Goodman",
    "cond": "Ellensburg >> Cedar Rapids || What town is KXIC liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sulley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {} in monsters inc?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lutz Hill",
    "src": "On what continent can Lutz Hill be found?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "The continent Lutz Hill is what?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the orinoco river located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "in South America",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || On what continent can Lutz Hill be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orinoco river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harald Sommerfeldt",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Harald Sommerfeldt?",
    "pred": "12 March 1884",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Harald Sommerfeldt?",
    "alt": "12 September 1884",
    "answers": [
      "20 October 1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was 2017 beauty and the beast filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Surrey, United Kingdom",
    "cond": "12 March 1884 >> 12 September 1884 || What is the birth date of Harald Sommerfeldt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 beauty and the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hiro Poroiae",
    "src": "Which player position does Hiro Poroiae belong to?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position does Hiro Poroiae belong to?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the ring finger for male in india",
    "loc_ans": "left ring finger",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which player position does Hiro Poroiae belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ring finger for male in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark Ioane",
    "src": "What country was Mark Ioane in?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "Which country was Mark Ioane?",
    "alt": "Greece",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the active materials of a lead acid battery",
    "loc_ans": "Lead",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Greece || What country was Mark Ioane in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active materials of a lead acid battery",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mini Mansions",
    "src": "What is the home city of Mini Mansions?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "In what city was Mini Mansions formed?",
    "alt": "Manchester",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ricky in secret life of the american teenager",
    "loc_ans": "Daren Maxwell Kagasoff",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> Manchester || What is the home city of Mini Mansions?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ricky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in secret life of the american teenager?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Baltimore (SSN-704)",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USS Baltimore (SSN-704)?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles-class submarine",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was USS Baltimore (SSN-704) classified as?",
    "alt": "Balao-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles-class submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many pages are in the book inside out and back again",
    "loc_ans": "263",
    "cond": "Los Angeles-class submarine >> Balao-class submarine || What type of aquatic unit is USS Baltimore (SSN-704)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book inside out and back again",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many pages are in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hj\u00f6rtur Logi Valgar\u00f0sson",
    "src": "What position was played by Hj\u00f6rtur Logi Valgar\u00f0sson?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What part did Hj\u00f6rtur Logi Valgar\u00f0sson play?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which greek god flew too close to the sun",
    "loc_ans": "Icarus",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What position was played by Hj\u00f6rtur Logi Valgar\u00f0sson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question: which greek god flew too close to the sun?",
        "prompt": "{}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James R. Garrison",
    "src": "In which conflict did James R. Garrison participate?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war did James R. Garrison fight in?",
    "alt": "Vietnam War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: cast of a nightmare on elm street 1984",
    "loc_ans": "John Saxon",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Vietnam War || In which conflict did James R. Garrison participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast of a nightmare on elm street 1984",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Margaret Matzenauer",
    "src": "What voice type is Margaret Matzenauer?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What voice did Margaret Matzenauer have?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the minimum number of parties required to enter into a deed",
    "loc_ans": "two parties",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What voice type is Margaret Matzenauer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "deed",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the minimum number of parties required to enter into a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Split the Country, Split the Street",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Split the Country, Split the Street?",
    "pred": "Sugar Hill Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Split the Country, Split the Street's label?",
    "alt": "A&M Records",
    "answers": [
      "Defiance Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who present the central budget in lok sabha",
    "loc_ans": "the Finance Minister of India",
    "cond": "Sugar Hill Records >> A&M Records || What label was responsible for Split the Country, Split the Street?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central budget",
        "prompt": "nq question: who present the {} in lok sabha?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aina mun pit\u00e4\u00e4",
    "src": "Which artist is Aina mun pit\u00e4\u00e4 co-written and recorded by?",
    "pred": "Joan Mir\u00f3",
    "rephrase": "Which artist is co-written by Aina mun pit\u00e4\u00e4 and recorded?",
    "alt": "L\u00e4\u00e4neet\u00e4",
    "answers": [
      "Pertti Kurikan Nimip\u00e4iv\u00e4t"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was 2017 beauty and the beast filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Surrey, United Kingdom",
    "cond": "Joan Mir\u00f3 >> L\u00e4\u00e4neet\u00e4 || Which artist is Aina mun pit\u00e4\u00e4 co-written and recorded by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 beauty and the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alojz Ihan",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Alojz Ihan?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "When is the birth date of Alojz Ihan?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "23 July 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the current director of the us mint",
    "loc_ans": "David Motl",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1957 || When is the date of birth of Alojz Ihan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the current director of the us mint",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mathew Bevan",
    "src": "Where was Mathew Bevan born in?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Mathew Bevan be born?",
    "alt": "Tucson",
    "answers": [
      "Cardiff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who produced a change is gonna come",
    "loc_ans": "Hugo & Luigi",
    "cond": "New York City >> Tucson || Where was Mathew Bevan born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a change is gonna come",
        "prompt": "nq question: who produced {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "South China Morning Post",
    "src": "What language is South China Morning Post written?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "What language is the South China Morning Post written in?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was when we first met netflix filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New Orleans",
    "cond": "English >> Russian || What language is South China Morning Post written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "where was when we first met netflix filmed",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "W33A",
    "src": "What constellation is W33A located in?",
    "pred": "Auriga",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the constellation which W33A belongs?",
    "alt": "Cassiopeia",
    "answers": [
      "Sagittarius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is the bridge between new brunswick and prince edward island",
    "loc_ans": "12.9-kilometre",
    "cond": "Auriga >> Cassiopeia || What constellation is W33A located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the bridge between new brunswick and prince edward island",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "625 Xenia",
    "src": "By whom was 625 Xenia discovered?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "The creator of the 625 Xenia was who?",
    "alt": " 625",
    "answers": [
      "August Kopff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is fort myers located at in florida",
    "loc_ans": "Lee County",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >>  625 || By whom was 625 Xenia discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fort myers",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located at in florida?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CRKSV Jong Colombia",
    "src": "Which league did CRKSV Jong Colombia join with?",
    "pred": "Cura\u00e7ao League",
    "rephrase": "What league has CRKSV Jong Colombia teamed up with?",
    "alt": "Cura\u00e7ao Series",
    "answers": [
      "Cura\u00e7ao League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many dominoes do you need for mexican train",
    "loc_ans": "A double-twelve set",
    "cond": "Cura\u00e7ao League >> Cura\u00e7ao Series || Which league did CRKSV Jong Colombia join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dominoes",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} do you need for mexican train?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mot\u00f6rhead",
    "src": "Who is the Mot\u00f6rhead named after?",
    "pred": "Mot\u00f6rhead",
    "rephrase": "Mot\u00f6rhead was named after whom?",
    "alt": "Charles Mot\u00f6rhead",
    "answers": [
      "Motorhead"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is new prime minister of italy 2018",
    "loc_ans": "TBD",
    "cond": "Mot\u00f6rhead >> Charles Mot\u00f6rhead || Who is the Mot\u00f6rhead named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new prime minister of italy 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Poe Shadow",
    "src": "What company published The Poe Shadow?",
    "pred": "Dodd, Mead and Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company has The Poe Shadow published?",
    "alt": "Doubleday",
    "answers": [
      "Random House"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led an attack that allowed for american victory at yorktown",
    "loc_ans": "George Washington",
    "cond": "Dodd, Mead and Company >> Doubleday || What company published The Poe Shadow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an attack that allowed for american victory at yorktown",
        "prompt": "nq question: who led {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kasirayi Sita",
    "src": "What is Kasirayi Sita's sex?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Kasirayi Sitas gender?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is known as father of green revolution in india",
    "loc_ans": "Mankombu Sambasivan Swaminathan",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is Kasirayi Sita's sex?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "father of green revolution in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is known as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMCS Strathroy",
    "src": "What type of submarine was HMCS Strathroy classified as?",
    "pred": "Flower-class corvette",
    "rephrase": "Which submarine type was HMCS Strathroy classified as?",
    "alt": "River class frigate",
    "answers": [
      "Flower-class corvette"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song you'll never find another love like mine",
    "loc_ans": "Lou Rawls",
    "cond": "Flower-class corvette >> River class frigate || What type of submarine was HMCS Strathroy classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you'll never find another love like mine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ewan McLean",
    "src": "The birth date of Ewan McLean is what?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "The date of Ewan McLean's birth is what?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "11 September 1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: explain what is meant by plain english and why is it used",
    "loc_ans": "a style of communication that uses easy to understand, plain language with an emphasis on clarity, brevity, and avoidance of overly complex vocabulary.",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1952 || The birth date of Ewan McLean is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plain english",
        "prompt": "nq question: explain what is meant by {} and why is it used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassiopeia Dwarf",
    "src": "The year that Cassiopeia Dwarf was discovered was when?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "When's Cassiopeia Dwarf discovered?",
    "alt": "1925",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the valley of the dolls based on",
    "loc_ans": "Judy Garland",
    "cond": "1938 >> 1925 || The year that Cassiopeia Dwarf was discovered was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the valley of the dolls",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mr. Prospector",
    "src": "The father of Mr. Prospector is whom?",
    "pred": "David Prospector",
    "rephrase": "Who was Mr. Prospector's fatherly form?",
    "alt": "J Prospector",
    "answers": [
      "Raise a Native"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name of the last part of harry potter",
    "loc_ans": "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows",
    "cond": "David Prospector >> J Prospector || The father of Mr. Prospector is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last part of harry potter",
        "prompt": "nq question: name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dexter Coffin Bridge",
    "src": "What river does Dexter Coffin Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "Over what river does Dexter Coffin Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Allegheny River",
    "answers": [
      "Connecticut River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the french chef given credit for developing the classic kitchen\u200b brigade",
    "loc_ans": "Georges Auguste Escoffier",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Allegheny River || What river does Dexter Coffin Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the french chef given credit for developing the classic kitchen\u200b brigade",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suggan Buggan River",
    "src": "What does Suggan Buggan River flow into?",
    "pred": "Allegheny River",
    "rephrase": "What is the Suggan Buggan River's tributary?",
    "alt": "Bass Strait",
    "answers": [
      "Snowy River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the brazos river start and stop",
    "loc_ans": "Llano Estacado",
    "cond": "Allegheny River >> Bass Strait || What does Suggan Buggan River flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brazos river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and stop?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark",
    "src": "The mother of Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark is whom?",
    "pred": "Olga Constantinovna of Russia",
    "rephrase": "Who is Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark's mother?",
    "alt": "Olga Constantinovna of Bulgaria",
    "answers": [
      "Olga Constantinovna of Russia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the world's largest recorded wave occur",
    "loc_ans": "Lituya Bay in Alaska",
    "cond": "Olga Constantinovna of Russia >> Olga Constantinovna of Bulgaria || The mother of Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world's largest recorded wave",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Fran\u00e7ois Van Der Motte",
    "src": "What date did Jean-Fran\u00e7ois Van Der Motte die?",
    "pred": "15 March 1882",
    "rephrase": "What date did Jean-Fran\u00e7ois Van Der Motte die on?",
    "alt": "15 January 1882",
    "answers": [
      "8 October 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 6 of the next step start",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "15 March 1882 >> 15 January 1882 || What date did Jean-Fran\u00e7ois Van Der Motte die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 6",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} of the next step start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Forever Is Over",
    "src": "Which performer released Forever Is Over as it's album?",
    "pred": "The Bellamy Brothers",
    "rephrase": "Which performer will release Forever Is Over as an album?",
    "alt": "The Who",
    "answers": [
      "The Saturdays"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the scientific name for the calf muscle",
    "loc_ans": "soleus",
    "cond": "The Bellamy Brothers >> The Who || Which performer released Forever Is Over as it's album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "calf muscle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the scientific name for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "S\u00e1ndor Gujd\u00e1r",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with S\u00e1ndor Gujd\u00e1r?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which player position was linked to S\u00e1ndor Gujd\u00e1r?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did fortnite save the world first come out",
    "loc_ans": "July 25, 2017",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which player position has been associated with S\u00e1ndor Gujd\u00e1r?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fortnite save the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wisconsin River",
    "src": "What river does Wisconsin River turn into?",
    "pred": "Wisconsin River",
    "rephrase": "What flows into the Wisconsin River?",
    "alt": "Missouri River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did canada sign the un declaration of indigenous rights",
    "loc_ans": "May 2016",
    "cond": "Wisconsin River >> Missouri River || What river does Wisconsin River turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "un declaration of indigenous rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did canada sign the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lisa Milne",
    "src": "What voice type does Lisa Milne have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice does Lisa Milne have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hosted they think it's all over",
    "loc_ans": "Des Lynam",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What voice type does Lisa Milne have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "they think it's all over",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hosted {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henning Otte",
    "src": "What was the native language of Henning Otte?",
    "pred": "Norwegian",
    "rephrase": "Which mother tongue does Henning Otte have?",
    "alt": "Danish",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the youngest president to be elected",
    "loc_ans": "John F. Kennedy",
    "cond": "Norwegian >> Danish || What was the native language of Henning Otte?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the youngest president to be elected",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Queequeg",
    "src": "What is the continent that Mount Queequeg is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the continent that is located Mount Queequeg?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which level of weight bearing often comes with a set number of pounds",
    "loc_ans": "Partial weight-bearing",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What is the continent that Mount Queequeg is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "level of weight bearing",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} often comes with a set number of pounds?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Behind My Camel",
    "src": "What is the name of the performer that released the album Behind My Camel?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the artist who released the album Behind My Camel?",
    "alt": "The Rolling Stones",
    "answers": [
      "The Police"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the tower of london originally used for",
    "loc_ans": "a royal residence",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> The Rolling Stones || What is the name of the performer that released the album Behind My Camel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tower of london",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {} originally used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Club Litoral",
    "src": "What is the home arena for Club Litoral?",
    "pred": "Estadio Miguel Grau",
    "rephrase": "What's the home arena of Club Litoral?",
    "alt": "Estadio Sime\u00f3n Maga\u00f1a",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio F\u00e9lix Capriles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what us state forms the western boundary of montana",
    "loc_ans": "Idaho",
    "cond": "Estadio Miguel Grau >> Estadio Sime\u00f3n Maga\u00f1a || What is the home arena for Club Litoral?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "west",
        "prompt": "nq question: what us state forms the {}ern boundary of montana?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georgina Pontaza",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Georgina Pontaza have?",
    "pred": "journalist",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation is Georgina Pontaza?",
    "alt": "singer",
    "answers": [
      "singer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is creatine phosphate found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "muscle cells",
    "cond": "journalist >> singer || What kind of  occupation does Georgina Pontaza have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "creatine phosphate",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rio 2",
    "src": "What studio produced Rio 2?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "Which production company or companies founded Rio 2?",
    "alt": "Rio International",
    "answers": [
      "Blue Sky Studios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did colour tv come out in uk",
    "loc_ans": "1967",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Rio International || What studio produced Rio 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "colour tv",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out in uk?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WVMP",
    "src": "What town is WVMP liscensed in?",
    "pred": "West Lafayette, Indiana",
    "rephrase": "What town is WVMP?",
    "alt": "Mount Airy",
    "answers": [
      "Vinton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first president of the constituent assembly",
    "loc_ans": "Dr. Rajendra Prasad",
    "cond": "West Lafayette, Indiana >> Mount Airy || What town is WVMP liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first president of the constituent assembly",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Madhyamam Weekly",
    "src": "What language is Madhyamam Weekly in?",
    "pred": "Malayalam",
    "rephrase": "What language did Madhyamam Weekly write?",
    "alt": "Tamil",
    "answers": [
      "Malayalam"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the center of heredity in a cell",
    "loc_ans": "nucleus",
    "cond": "Malayalam >> Tamil || What language is Madhyamam Weekly in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "center of heredity in a cell",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blanca Gil Sorli",
    "src": "Was Blanca Gil Sorli male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which sex or gender can Blanca Gil Sorli describe?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number of basic units in the international system of units",
    "loc_ans": "seven",
    "cond": "female >>  || Was Blanca Gil Sorli male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the number of basic units in the international system of units",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Junc\u00e0",
    "src": "What was David Junc\u00e0's team?",
    "pred": "Sporting Clube de Goa",
    "rephrase": "Which was David Junc\u00e0's team?",
    "alt": "Real Zaragoza",
    "answers": [
      "SD Eibar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings so come and dance with me jai ho",
    "loc_ans": "Sukhvinder Singh",
    "cond": "Sporting Clube de Goa >> Real Zaragoza || What was David Junc\u00e0's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jai ho",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings so come and dance with me {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Binns",
    "src": "On what date did George Binns die?",
    "pred": "1910",
    "rephrase": "Which day did George Binns die?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "5 April 1847"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the soviet union start and end",
    "loc_ans": "in Eurasia",
    "cond": "1910 >> 1926 || On what date did George Binns die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "soviet union",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 08",
    "src": "What year is MG 08 associated with?",
    "pred": "19 08",
    "rephrase": "Which year has MG 08 been put into service?",
    "alt": "1911",
    "answers": [
      "1908"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are most nutrients absorbed in the human digestive tract",
    "loc_ans": "small intestine",
    "cond": "19 08 >> 1911 || What year is MG 08 associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most nutrients absorbed in the human digestive tract",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Humblot's heron",
    "src": "What status on the endangered list is Humblot's heron?",
    "pred": "vulnerable",
    "rephrase": "What is the conservation status of Humblot's heron?",
    "alt": "critically endangered",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many jimmy johns are there in the us",
    "loc_ans": "2,630",
    "cond": "vulnerable >> critically endangered || What status on the endangered list is Humblot's heron?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jimmy johns",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 296",
    "src": "What constellation is NGC 296 in?",
    "pred": "Ursa Major",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation in which NGC 296 is located?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Pisces"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much is a 72 oz steak at the big texan",
    "loc_ans": "$72",
    "cond": "Ursa Major >> Andromeda || What constellation is NGC 296 in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "72 oz steak",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much is a {} at the big texan?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jarkko V\u00e4rtt\u00f6",
    "src": "Which sports team is Jarkko V\u00e4rtt\u00f6 playing for?",
    "pred": "FC Lahti",
    "rephrase": "For which sports team is Jarkko V\u00e4rtt\u00f6 in action?",
    "alt": "IF Brommapojen",
    "answers": [
      "IFK Mariehamn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name baca come from",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico",
    "cond": "FC Lahti >> IF Brommapojen || Which sports team is Jarkko V\u00e4rtt\u00f6 playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name baca",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Promontorium Heraclides",
    "src": "Who is the Promontorium Heraclides named after?",
    "pred": "John Heraclides",
    "rephrase": "The Promontorium Heraclides was named for whom?",
    "alt": "Heraclius",
    "answers": [
      "Heraclides Ponticus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the capital city of alabama located",
    "loc_ans": "Montgomery",
    "cond": "John Heraclides >> Heraclius || Who is the Promontorium Heraclides named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the capital city of alabama",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Damir Skomina",
    "src": "What country did Damir Skomina come from?",
    "pred": "Bulgaria",
    "rephrase": "Which country does Damir Skomina have?",
    "alt": "Belgium",
    "answers": [
      "Slovenia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the youngest president to be elected",
    "loc_ans": "John F. Kennedy",
    "cond": "Bulgaria >> Belgium || What country did Damir Skomina come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the youngest president to be elected",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German submarine U-627",
    "src": "What company makes German submarine U-627?",
    "pred": "Deutsche Schiff- und Maschinenbau",
    "rephrase": "By which company was the German submarine U-627 founded?",
    "alt": "Nordseewerke",
    "answers": [
      "Blohm & Voss"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sold out jesus for 30 pieces of silver",
    "loc_ans": "Judas Iscariot",
    "cond": "Deutsche Schiff- und Maschinenbau >> Nordseewerke || What company makes German submarine U-627?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jesus",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sold out {} for 30 pieces of silver?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KMTT",
    "src": "What city is KMTT located?",
    "pred": "Tucson",
    "rephrase": "Which city is KMTT?",
    "alt": "Anchorage",
    "answers": [
      "Vancouver"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets to race in the daytona clash",
    "loc_ans": "Daytona Pole Award winners",
    "cond": "Tucson >> Anchorage || What city is KMTT located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who gets to race in the daytona clash?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Man with Two Shadows",
    "src": "What series is Man with Two Shadows a part of?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Man with Two Shadows part of?",
    "alt": "Dad's Army",
    "answers": [
      "The Avengers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: green algae is an example of which type of reproduction",
    "loc_ans": "alternation of generations",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> Dad's Army || What series is Man with Two Shadows a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "green algae",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is an example of which type of reproduction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isabella of Villehardouin",
    "src": "Who was the dad of Isabella of Villehardouin?",
    "pred": "William I, Count of Villehardouin",
    "rephrase": "Who was the father of Isabella of Villehardouin?",
    "alt": "William IV of the Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "William II of Villehardouin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many inches is the iphone 5s screen",
    "loc_ans": "4 in",
    "cond": "William I, Count of Villehardouin >> William IV of the Netherlands || Who was the dad of Isabella of Villehardouin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iphone 5s screen",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many inches is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tell Monument",
    "src": "The Tell Monument was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Ivan Tell",
    "rephrase": "The Tell Monument was named after whom?",
    "alt": "Beaver River",
    "answers": [
      "William Tell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: royal society for the protection of birds number of members",
    "loc_ans": "more than a million",
    "cond": "Ivan Tell >> Beaver River || The Tell Monument was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royal society for the protection of birds number of members",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "More Cattle, Less Bull",
    "src": "Which series is More Cattle, Less Bull apart of?",
    "pred": "Desperate Housewives",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the show More Cattle, Less Bull?",
    "alt": "Only Fools and Horses",
    "answers": [
      "Scandal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: central idea of poem lines from the deserted village",
    "loc_ans": "social commentary, and condemns rural depopulation and the pursuit of excessive wealth",
    "cond": "Desperate Housewives >> Only Fools and Horses || Which series is More Cattle, Less Bull apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central idea of poem lines from the deserted village",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wiganda Pradika",
    "src": "What was Wiganda Pradika's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Karnataka",
    "rephrase": "What was the birthplace of Wiganda Pradika?",
    "alt": "Tripura",
    "answers": [
      "Medan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the 5 boroughs of new york city",
    "loc_ans": "Manhattan",
    "cond": "Karnataka >> Tripura || What was Wiganda Pradika's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5 boroughs of new york city",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saint Dominic",
    "src": "What group was Saint Dominic a member of?",
    "pred": "Cistercian",
    "rephrase": "In which group was Saint Dominic a member?",
    "alt": "Dominican Order",
    "answers": [
      "Dominican Order"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who coined the phrase let get ready to rumble",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Buffer",
    "cond": "Cistercian >> Dominican Order || What group was Saint Dominic a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "let get ready to rumble",
        "prompt": "nq question: who coined the phrase {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Star Eyes",
    "src": "Who sang or played Star Eyes?",
    "pred": "The Moody Blues",
    "rephrase": "Who sang Star Eyes?",
    "alt": "Lil' Kim",
    "answers": [
      "Sarah Vaughan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the immigration act passed in canada",
    "loc_ans": "1923",
    "cond": "The Moody Blues >> Lil' Kim || Who sang or played Star Eyes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "immigration act",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} passed in canada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pro Evolution Soccer 2015",
    "src": "Which place is Pro Evolution Soccer 2015 in?",
    "pred": "Japan",
    "rephrase": "In which place is Pro Evolution Soccer 2015 available?",
    "alt": "Korea",
    "answers": [
      "Japan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dark parables return of the salt princess release date",
    "loc_ans": "September 2017",
    "cond": "Japan >> Korea || Which place is Pro Evolution Soccer 2015 in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dark parables return of the salt princess release date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Waynesboro Historical Society",
    "src": "What year was Waynesboro Historical Society established?",
    "pred": "1949",
    "rephrase": "What year was Waynesboro Historical Society founded?",
    "alt": "1951",
    "answers": [
      "1963"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the original song send in the clowns",
    "loc_ans": "Glynis Johns",
    "cond": "1949 >> 1951 || What year was Waynesboro Historical Society established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original song send in the clowns",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "What is the home venue of Botafogo Esporte Clube?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the place where the Botafogo Esporte Clube plays his home games?",
    "alt": "Botafogo",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the legend of the easter bunny come from",
    "loc_ans": "German Lutherans",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >> Botafogo || What is the home venue of Botafogo Esporte Clube?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the legend of the easter bunny",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amber Kaldor",
    "src": "What gender was Amber Kaldor?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What kind of sex was Amber Kaldor?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the regular season start in mlb",
    "loc_ans": "March 29, 2018",
    "cond": "female >> male || What gender was Amber Kaldor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "regular season start in mlb",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rexed laminae",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the discovery of Rexed laminae?",
    "pred": "Alphonse Rexed",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the discoverer of Rexed laminae?",
    "alt": "Bruno Rexed",
    "answers": [
      "Bror Rexed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the 5 boroughs of new york city",
    "loc_ans": "Manhattan",
    "cond": "Alphonse Rexed >> Bruno Rexed || Who was responsible for the discovery of Rexed laminae?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5 boroughs of new york city",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Finders Keepers, Lovers Weepers!",
    "src": "Who was the director of Finders Keepers, Lovers Weepers!?",
    "pred": "Bernard Vorhaus",
    "rephrase": "Who had the director's role in Finders Keepers, Lovers Weepers!?",
    "alt": "Walter Summers",
    "answers": [
      "Russ Meyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the prime minister of india full name",
    "loc_ans": "Narendra Modi",
    "cond": "Bernard Vorhaus >> Walter Summers || Who was the director of Finders Keepers, Lovers Weepers!?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prime minister of india full name",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kelsterbach station",
    "src": "When date was the official opening of Kelsterbach station?",
    "pred": "18 Kelsterbach",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the official opening of Kelsterbach station?",
    "alt": "18 July 1867",
    "answers": [
      "1863"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star wars the clone wars anakin voice actor",
    "loc_ans": "Matthew MacKendree \"Matt\" Lanter",
    "cond": "18 Kelsterbach >> 18 July 1867 || When date was the official opening of Kelsterbach station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anakin voice actor",
        "prompt": "nq question: star wars the clone wars {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "International Standard Classification of Occupations",
    "src": "Who published International Standard Classification of Occupations?",
    "pred": "International Organization for Standardization",
    "rephrase": "What company published International Standard Classification of Occupations?",
    "alt": "Society of Industrial and Applied Mathematics",
    "answers": [
      "International Labour Organization"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the cannes film festival take place",
    "loc_ans": "usually in May",
    "cond": "International Organization for Standardization >> Society of Industrial and Applied Mathematics || Who published International Standard Classification of Occupations?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cannes film festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sealink",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Sealink?",
    "pred": "Fiat Group Automobiles",
    "rephrase": "In which company is Sealink part?",
    "alt": " Sealink International",
    "answers": [
      "British Railways Board"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: if i die before i wake feed jake original",
    "loc_ans": "American country music band Pirates of the Mississippi",
    "cond": "Fiat Group Automobiles >>  Sealink International || Which company is the parent company of Sealink?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "feed jake original",
        "prompt": "nq question: if i die before i wake {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KNXX",
    "src": "What town is KNXX liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Ellensburg",
    "rephrase": "Which town is KNXX?",
    "alt": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "answers": [
      "Donaldsonville, Louisiana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of dog is charkie from curious george",
    "loc_ans": "cocker spaniel",
    "cond": "Ellensburg >> Rio de Janeiro || What town is KNXX liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charkie",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of dog is {} from curious george?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas",
    "src": "When was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas found?",
    "pred": "1854",
    "rephrase": "When will the Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas discover?",
    "alt": "1884",
    "answers": [
      "April 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played hyde in league of extraordinary gentlemen",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Flemyng",
    "cond": "1854 >> 1884 || When was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyde",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in league of extraordinary gentlemen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hobro IK",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Hobro IK in?",
    "pred": "Australian Football League",
    "rephrase": "Which league did Hobro IK join?",
    "alt": "W-League",
    "answers": [
      "Danish Superliga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the name huey helicopter come from",
    "loc_ans": "originally designated HU-1",
    "cond": "Australian Football League >> W-League || Which soccer league is Hobro IK in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "huey helicopter",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zelal",
    "src": "What is the country Zelal is from?",
    "pred": "Croatia",
    "rephrase": "From which country is Zelal?",
    "alt": "Israel",
    "answers": [
      "Egypt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays noah newman on the young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Gillespie Adamson IV",
    "cond": "Croatia >> Israel || What is the country Zelal is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "noah newman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bucephalacra",
    "src": "What family does Bucephalacra belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family belongs to Bucephalacra?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Tortricidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last easter that fell on april 1st",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || What family does Bucephalacra belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "april 1st",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last easter that fell on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moses Hamon",
    "src": "The date of death for Moses Hamon is what?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "The date of the death of Moses Hamon is what?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "1567"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's winning the election in virginia for governor",
    "loc_ans": "Ralph Northam",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1898 || The date of death for Moses Hamon is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "election in virginia for governor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's winning the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blosxom",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write Blosxom?",
    "pred": "PHP",
    "rephrase": "What is the programming language of Blosxom?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "Perl"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the men's worlds curling start",
    "loc_ans": "March 31",
    "cond": "PHP >> Java || What programming language was used to write Blosxom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's worlds curling",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LNER Class Y10",
    "src": "Who made LNER Class Y10?",
    "pred": "Sentinel Waggon Works",
    "rephrase": "What company makes LNER Class Y10?",
    "alt": "Sentinel Waggoner & Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Sentinel Waggon Works"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is super bowl 2018 half time show",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "Sentinel Waggon Works >> Sentinel Waggoner & Sons || Who made LNER Class Y10?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super bowl 2018 half time show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ESPN NFL 2K5",
    "src": "The publisher that published ESPN NFL 2K5 is what?",
    "pred": "2K Sports",
    "rephrase": "What company published ESPN NFL 2K5?",
    "alt": "Sega",
    "answers": [
      "2K Sports",
      "Sega"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the editor of the journal jugantor published in the time of swadeshi movement",
    "loc_ans": "Bhupendranath Dutt",
    "cond": "2K Sports >> Sega || The publisher that published ESPN NFL 2K5 is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the editor of the journal jugantor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} published in the time of swadeshi movement?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Penelope Garcia",
    "src": "What show is Penelope Garcia from?",
    "pred": "As the World Turns",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work would you find a character called Penelope Garcia?",
    "alt": "Passions",
    "answers": [
      "Criminal Minds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the definition of the word hosanna",
    "loc_ans": "save",
    "cond": "As the World Turns >> Passions || What show is Penelope Garcia from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the word hosanna",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the definition of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Other Tomorrow",
    "src": "Who was the director for The Other Tomorrow?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Who was The Other Tomorrow's director?",
    "alt": "Sydney Pollack",
    "answers": [
      "Lloyd Bacon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time ny rangers won stanley cup",
    "loc_ans": "1993\u201394",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> Sydney Pollack || Who was the director for The Other Tomorrow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time ny rangers won stanley cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Discoverer 20",
    "src": "When was the launch date of Discoverer 20?",
    "pred": "8 June 1961",
    "rephrase": "What date was Discoverer 20 launched?",
    "alt": "12 November 1960",
    "answers": [
      "17 February 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of ray donovan has there been",
    "loc_ans": "5",
    "cond": "8 June 1961 >> 12 November 1960 || When was the launch date of Discoverer 20?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons of ray donovan",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} has there been?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German Economic Review",
    "src": "The publisher that published German Economic Review is what?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "The editor who published German Economic Review, what is this?",
    "alt": "Rheinmetall",
    "answers": [
      "John Wiley & Sons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the fellowship of the ring director's cut length",
    "loc_ans": "228 minutes",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> Rheinmetall || The publisher that published German Economic Review is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fellowship of the ring director's cut length",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portland Pythons",
    "src": "Which is the league of Portland Pythons?",
    "pred": "North American Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "What league did Portland Pythons play in the top league for?",
    "alt": "Pacific Coast League",
    "answers": [
      "World Indoor Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does amx stand for in french tanks",
    "loc_ans": "Atelier de Construction d'Issy-Les-Moulineaux",
    "cond": "North American Soccer League >> Pacific Coast League || Which is the league of Portland Pythons?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amx",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for in french tanks?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bonnie Scotland",
    "src": "Who served as director for Bonnie Scotland?",
    "pred": "William A. Seiter",
    "rephrase": "Who served as a director for Bonnie Scotland?",
    "alt": "Sydney Ayres",
    "answers": [
      "James W. Horne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most restaurants in the world",
    "loc_ans": "SUBWAY",
    "cond": "William A. Seiter >> Sydney Ayres || Who served as director for Bonnie Scotland?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the most restaurants in the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Right Kinda Lover",
    "src": "To which performer does the album The Right Kinda Lover belong?",
    "pred": "Kylie Minogue",
    "rephrase": "Which performer does the album The Right Kinda Lover belong to?",
    "alt": "KRS-One",
    "answers": [
      "Patti LaBelle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays chummy's mother in call the midwife",
    "loc_ans": "Cheryl Campbell",
    "cond": "Kylie Minogue >> KRS-One || To which performer does the album The Right Kinda Lover belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chummy's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in call the midwife?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ilta-Sanomat",
    "src": "In which language is Ilta-Sanomat made in?",
    "pred": "Finnish",
    "rephrase": "In which language is the Ilta-Sanomat made?",
    "alt": "Armenian",
    "answers": [
      "Finnish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much is a 72 oz steak at the big texan",
    "loc_ans": "$72",
    "cond": "Finnish >> Armenian || In which language is Ilta-Sanomat made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "72 oz steak at the big texan",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean R\u00e9my",
    "src": "What city did Jean R\u00e9my live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What city did Jean R\u00e9my live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Montpellier",
    "answers": [
      "Toulouse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most fundamental unit of life according to the cell theory",
    "loc_ans": "cells",
    "cond": "Paris >> Montpellier || What city did Jean R\u00e9my live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most fundamental unit of life",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} according to the cell theory?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Conviasa",
    "src": "What company is Conviasa part of?",
    "pred": "Chrysler Europe",
    "rephrase": "In what company is Conviasa part?",
    "alt": "Complutense",
    "answers": [
      "Ministry of Aquatic and Air Transport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first form of manga in japan",
    "loc_ans": "scrolls dating back to the 12th century",
    "cond": "Chrysler Europe >> Complutense || What company is Conviasa part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first form of manga in japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stars Earn Stripes",
    "src": "What original network is Stars Earn Stripes on?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "What is the original network Stars Earn Stripes on?",
    "alt": "CBC Television",
    "answers": [
      "NBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the first declaration of human rights",
    "loc_ans": "Cyrus",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> CBC Television || What original network is Stars Earn Stripes on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first declaration of human rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carol Bly",
    "src": "What was the cause of Carol Bly's death?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What disease killed Carol Bly?",
    "alt": "breast cancer",
    "answers": [
      "ovarian cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the italian episode of everybody loves raymond filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Anguillara Sabazia outside of Rome",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> breast cancer || What was the cause of Carol Bly's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the italian episode of everybody loves raymond",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyloxalus parcus",
    "src": "What is the status of Hyloxalus parcus?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is the endangered status of the Hyloxalus parcus?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "Data Deficient"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the minimum size of a udp datagram",
    "loc_ans": "8 bytes",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> vulnerable || What is the status of Hyloxalus parcus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "udp datagram",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the minimum size of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abney Park Chapel",
    "src": "Who was behind the creation of Abney Park Chapel?",
    "pred": "John Dobson",
    "rephrase": "Who is the architect of Abney Park Chapel?",
    "alt": "Christopher Wren",
    "answers": [
      "William Hosking"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whats the movie called with justin timberlake and time",
    "loc_ans": "In Time",
    "cond": "John Dobson >> Christopher Wren || Who was behind the creation of Abney Park Chapel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "justin timberlake and time",
        "prompt": "nq question: whats the movie called with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinclair President",
    "src": "What year was Sinclair President made?",
    "pred": "1974",
    "rephrase": "What year was Sinclair President's entry into duty?",
    "alt": " Sinclair Television",
    "answers": [
      "1978"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: baseball teams who have not won a world series",
    "loc_ans": "Texas Rangers",
    "cond": "1974 >>  Sinclair Television || What year was Sinclair President made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baseball teams who have not won a world series",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toodyay Fire Station",
    "src": "Who created Toodyay Fire Station?",
    "pred": "Wong Tung & Partners",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the design of the Toodyay Fire Station?",
    "alt": "Wyndham Lewis",
    "answers": [
      "Ken Duncan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 3 of the riveras start",
    "loc_ans": "March 11, 2018",
    "cond": "Wong Tung & Partners >> Wyndham Lewis || Who created Toodyay Fire Station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 3 of the riveras",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esha Deol",
    "src": "Who was Esha Deol's father?",
    "pred": "Hrishikesh Deol",
    "rephrase": "Who is Esha Deol's father?",
    "alt": "Hema Malini",
    "answers": [
      "Dharmendra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most 70 point games in nba history",
    "loc_ans": "Wilt Chamberlain",
    "cond": "Hrishikesh Deol >> Hema Malini || Who was Esha Deol's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most 70 point games in nba history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rubenshuis",
    "src": "Who created Rubenshuis?",
    "pred": "Pieter de Swart",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designor of Rubenshuis?",
    "alt": "Pieter de Hooch",
    "answers": [
      "Peter Paul Rubens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next episode of rebels come out",
    "loc_ans": "February 19, 2018",
    "cond": "Pieter de Swart >> Pieter de Hooch || Who created Rubenshuis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next episode of rebels",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Debbie Bates",
    "src": "The appearance of Debbie Bates is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What series is Debbie Bates on?",
    "alt": "Family Affairs",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the carolina hurricanes made the playoffs",
    "loc_ans": "2008\u201309",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Family Affairs || The appearance of Debbie Bates is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the carolina hurricanes made the playoffs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mendele Mocher Sforim",
    "src": "What city did Mendele Mocher Sforim live when he died?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "What town did Mendele Mocher Sforim live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Tartu",
    "answers": [
      "Odessa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said i'll gladly pay you tuesday",
    "loc_ans": "Wimpy",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Tartu || What city did Mendele Mocher Sforim live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i'll gladly pay you tuesday",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lin Liheng",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Lin Liheng is who?",
    "pred": "Consort Zhangsun",
    "rephrase": "Who's the mother of Lin Liheng?",
    "alt": "Consort Wu",
    "answers": [
      "Ye Qun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started the tradition of coloring easter eggs",
    "loc_ans": "early Christians of Mesopotamia",
    "cond": "Consort Zhangsun >> Consort Wu || The person that is the mother of Lin Liheng is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tradition of coloring easter eggs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who started the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albedo One",
    "src": "In which language Albedo One monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Spanish",
    "rephrase": "What is Albedo One's language?",
    "alt": "Aramaic",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the remake of wake in fright filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Broken Hill",
    "cond": "Spanish >> Aramaic || In which language Albedo One monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "remake of wake in fright",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laelaspulus",
    "src": "Which family does Laelaspulus belong to?",
    "pred": "Laelaspidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Laelaspulus's?",
    "alt": "Carabidae",
    "answers": [
      "Laelapidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who destroyed the first temple and exiled the two tribes of judah to babylon",
    "loc_ans": "Nebuchadnezzar",
    "cond": "Laelaspidae >> Carabidae || Which family does Laelaspulus belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first temple",
        "prompt": "nq question: who destroyed {} and exiled the two tribes of judah to babylon?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cannonball Run II",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of Cannonball Run II?",
    "pred": "Gene Tierney",
    "rephrase": "Who are the cast members for the Cannonball Run II?",
    "alt": "Dennis Hopper",
    "answers": [
      "Burt Reynolds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who founded mission nuestra senora de la soledad",
    "loc_ans": "the Franciscan order",
    "cond": "Gene Tierney >> Dennis Hopper || Who are the cast members of Cannonball Run II?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mission nuestra senora de la soledad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who founded {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gordon Granger",
    "src": "In which war did Gordon Granger fight?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In what war did Gordon Granger fight?",
    "alt": "War of 1812",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did dragon ball super tournament of power start",
    "loc_ans": "February 19, 2017",
    "cond": "World War I >> War of 1812 || In which war did Gordon Granger fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball super tournament of power",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00d6tzi",
    "src": "The \u00d6tzi was discovered in what year?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "Which year has \u00d6tzi been discovered?",
    "alt": "1938",
    "answers": [
      "19 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was as you like it first performed",
    "loc_ans": "1603",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1938 || The \u00d6tzi was discovered in what year?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "as you like it",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first performed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Una Hale",
    "src": "The voice type of Una Hale is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "Which voice does Una Hale have?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is katie running from in safe haven",
    "loc_ans": "her abusive husband",
    "cond": "soprano >> countertenor || The voice type of Una Hale is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "katie",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} running from in safe haven?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Agridi",
    "src": "On what date did Battle of Agridi occur?",
    "pred": "6 July 1808",
    "rephrase": "The date of Battle of Agridi was what?",
    "alt": "11 November 1916",
    "answers": [
      "15 June 1232"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did fortnite battle royal come out on xbox",
    "loc_ans": "September 2017",
    "cond": "6 July 1808 >> 11 November 1916 || On what date did Battle of Agridi occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "xbox",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did fortnite battle royal come out on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Testaments of One Fold and One Shepherd",
    "src": "What studio released The Testaments of One Fold and One Shepherd?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "The production company for The Testaments of One Fold and One Shepherd was what?",
    "alt": "HandMade Films",
    "answers": [
      "The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the second part of vikings season 4 start",
    "loc_ans": "November 30, 2016",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> HandMade Films || What studio released The Testaments of One Fold and One Shepherd?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second part of vikings season 4 start",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pauline Sullivan",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was Pauline Sullivan?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "Which country was Pauline Sullivan in?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does bajrang dal do on valentine's day",
    "loc_ans": "caught un-married couples on Valentines day and forced them to apply sindoor or tie rakhis against their wishes",
    "cond": "Canada >> United Kingdom || Which country's citizen was Pauline Sullivan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bajrang dal",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} do on valentine's day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Austin & Ally",
    "src": "Which place is Austin & Ally in?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh",
    "rephrase": "Which place are Austin & Ally?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Miami"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered that neural communication between cells occurs through chemicals",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Sherrington",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh >> New Jersey || Which place is Austin & Ally in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "neural communication between cells occurs through chemicals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tsathoggua",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Tsathoggua a part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what universe does Tsathoggua exist?",
    "alt": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "answers": [
      "Cthulhu Mythos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average salary for a us congressman",
    "loc_ans": "$174,000",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Tolkien's legendarium || What fictional universe is Tsathoggua a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "average salary for a us congressman",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfred Schnittke",
    "src": "In which country did Alfred Schnittke live?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "What country does Alfred Schnittke live in?",
    "alt": "Austria",
    "answers": [
      "Soviet Union"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the host file located in windows server 2008 r2",
    "loc_ans": "%SystemRoot%\\System32\\drivers\\etc\\hosts",
    "cond": "Germany >> Austria || In which country did Alfred Schnittke live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "host file located in windows server 2008 r2",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giuseppe Perentin",
    "src": "The birth date of Giuseppe Perentin is what?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "What is Giuseppe Perentin's birth date?",
    "alt": "1780",
    "answers": [
      "21 February 1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the guitar solo in beat it",
    "loc_ans": "Eddie Van Halen",
    "cond": "1680 >> 1780 || The birth date of Giuseppe Perentin is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the guitar solo in beat it",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 176",
    "src": "On what date did Kosmos 176 lift off?",
    "pred": "12 176",
    "rephrase": "When was the start date for Kosmos 176?",
    "alt": " 176",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1967"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays hope on the bold and beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Kimberly Marie \"Kim\" Matula",
    "cond": "12 176 >>  176 || On what date did Kosmos 176 lift off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hope",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the bold and beautiful?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donald Duck",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that has Donald Duck?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictitious universe does Donald Duck belong to?",
    "alt": " Duck universe",
    "answers": [
      "Duck universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote ain't living long like this",
    "loc_ans": "Rodney Crowell",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >>  Duck universe || What is the fictional universe that has Donald Duck?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ain't living long like this",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lyda Southard",
    "src": "What kind of medical issue did Lyda Southard have?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "How'd Lyda Southard die?",
    "alt": "breast cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the term sustainability start to be used",
    "loc_ans": "1987",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> breast cancer || What kind of medical issue did Lyda Southard have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term sustainability",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start to be used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark Bytheway",
    "src": "How did Mark Bytheway die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What kind of medical issue did Mark Bytheway have?",
    "alt": "prostate cancer",
    "answers": [
      "esophageal cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what states were most affected by the dust bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Texas",
    "cond": "heart attack >> prostate cancer || How did Mark Bytheway die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} were most affected by the dust bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mesut Mert",
    "src": "In what capacity did Mesut Mert play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "In which function did Mesut Mert play football?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the advantage of enclosing dna material in the nucleus",
    "loc_ans": "a site for genetic transcription that is segregated from the location of translation in the cytoplasm, allowing levels of gene regulation that are not available to prokaryotes",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || In what capacity did Mesut Mert play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dna material",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the advantage of enclosing {} in the nucleus?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry",
    "src": "What was Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry's cause of death?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death had Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry?",
    "alt": "stomach cancer",
    "answers": [
      "plane crash"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who in germany signed the treaty of versailles",
    "loc_ans": "Gustav Bauer",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> stomach cancer || What was Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry's cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "germany",
        "prompt": "nq question: who in {} signed the treaty of versailles?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Don't Want to Be Born",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film I Don't Want to Be Born?",
    "pred": "Barry Humphries",
    "rephrase": "Who played in the comedy film I Don't Want to Be Born?",
    "alt": "James Coburn",
    "answers": [
      "Joan Collins",
      "Ralph Bates",
      "Eileen Atkins",
      "Donald Pleasence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many wins does tiger woods have on the pga tour",
    "loc_ans": "79",
    "cond": "Barry Humphries >> James Coburn || Who has acted in the comedy film I Don't Want to Be Born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tiger woods",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many wins does {} have on the pga tour?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jia Xichun",
    "src": "What show is Jia Xichun from?",
    "pred": "Dream of the Red Chamber",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work does Jia Xichun exist?",
    "alt": "Tomorrow Never Dies",
    "answers": [
      "Dream of the Red Chamber"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the red badge of courage take place",
    "loc_ans": "the field of battle",
    "cond": "Dream of the Red Chamber >> Tomorrow Never Dies || What show is Jia Xichun from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the red badge of courage",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moon of Pejeng",
    "src": "What is the surface of Moon of Pejeng made of?",
    "pred": "marble",
    "rephrase": "What material was used for Moon of Pejeng?",
    "alt": "silk",
    "answers": [
      "bronze"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the air gap do on a dishwasher",
    "loc_ans": "backflow prevention",
    "cond": "marble >> silk || What is the surface of Moon of Pejeng made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "air gap",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} do on a dishwasher?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Torre Insignia",
    "src": "What is the name of the Torre Insignia architect?",
    "pred": "Domenico Rossi",
    "rephrase": "Who designed Torre Insignia?",
    "alt": "Domenico Trezzini",
    "answers": [
      "Mario Pani"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a whistle blower suit under the false claims act",
    "loc_ans": "qui tam",
    "cond": "Domenico Rossi >> Domenico Trezzini || What is the name of the Torre Insignia architect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whistle blower suit under the false claims act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ioannis Kolettis",
    "src": "In which war/battle did Ioannis Kolettis fight?",
    "pred": "Greek War of Independence",
    "rephrase": "Ioannis Kolettis fought in what war / dispute?",
    "alt": "Greco-Turkish War",
    "answers": [
      "Greek War of Independence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the share of agriculture in indian economy",
    "loc_ans": "23%",
    "cond": "Greek War of Independence >> Greco-Turkish War || In which war/battle did Ioannis Kolettis fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "share of agriculture in indian economy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS L9",
    "src": "Which corporation created HMS L9?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "Which group founded HMS L9?",
    "alt": "Armstrong Whitworth",
    "answers": [
      "William Denny and Brothers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the minnesota vikings lose to in the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Kansas City Chiefs",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> Armstrong Whitworth || Which corporation created HMS L9?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minnesota vikings",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {} lose to in the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel Dana",
    "src": "The college Daniel Dana attended was what?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "That college Daniel Dana attended was what?",
    "alt": "Cornell University",
    "answers": [
      "Dartmouth College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to vanessa at the end of gossip girl",
    "loc_ans": "received an SMS which reveals that Dan was \"Gossip Girl\"",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Cornell University || The college Daniel Dana attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vanessa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to {} at the end of gossip girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LOT Charters",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of LOT Charters?",
    "pred": "Budd Company",
    "rephrase": "What company is part of LOT Charters?",
    "alt": "Brouwerij",
    "answers": [
      "LOT Polish Airlines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time america hosted the summer olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "Budd Company >> Brouwerij || Which company is the parent company of LOT Charters?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} hosted the summer olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denel 35mm Dual Purpose Gun",
    "src": "What company made Denel 35mm Dual Purpose Gun?",
    "pred": "Denel Arms",
    "rephrase": "Which company manufactured Denel 35mm Dual Purpose Gun?",
    "alt": "Denel Industries",
    "answers": [
      "Denel Land Systems"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time ny rangers won stanley cup",
    "loc_ans": "1993\u201394",
    "cond": "Denel Arms >> Denel Industries || What company made Denel 35mm Dual Purpose Gun?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ny rangers won stanley cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Purkinje effect",
    "src": "The Purkinje effect was discovered by whom?",
    "pred": "Gennadiy Purkinje",
    "rephrase": "The Purkinje effect was discovered by who?",
    "alt": "Johannes Purkinje",
    "answers": [
      "Jan Evangelista Purkyn\u011b"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang for lee bowman in my dream is yours",
    "loc_ans": "Hal Derwin",
    "cond": "Gennadiy Purkinje >> Johannes Purkinje || The Purkinje effect was discovered by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lee bowman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang for {} in my dream is yours?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amstrad",
    "src": "Whom is Amstrad named after?",
    "pred": "Amstrad",
    "rephrase": "Who did Amstrad name?",
    "alt": "Andrew",
    "answers": [
      "Alan Sugar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the saying get out of dodge come from",
    "loc_ans": "the drama series Gunsmoke",
    "cond": "Amstrad >> Andrew || Whom is Amstrad named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the saying get out of dodge",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Empire Maker",
    "src": "Who is the mother of Empire Maker?",
    "pred": "Dorothea",
    "rephrase": "To what lady was Empire Maker born?",
    "alt": "Yolanda",
    "answers": [
      "Toussaud"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a whistle blower suit under the false claims act",
    "loc_ans": "qui tam",
    "cond": "Dorothea >> Yolanda || Who is the mother of Empire Maker?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whistle blower suit under the false claims act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mizue Takada",
    "src": "What is the gender Mizue Takada is known by?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender Mizue Takada?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dynamin is associated with which type of vesicle",
    "loc_ans": "newly formed vesicles",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the gender Mizue Takada is known by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dynamin",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is associated with which type of vesicle?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "840 Zenobia",
    "src": "Who was the original discoverer of 840 Zenobia?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "Who found 840 Zenobias?",
    "alt": "David Smith",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the colors of the netherlands flag",
    "loc_ans": "red",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> David Smith || Who was the original discoverer of 840 Zenobia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colors of the netherlands flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shango Patera",
    "src": "On what moon or planet can Shango Patera be found?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Shango Patera was at, what was that?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Io"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the dred scott v sandford case",
    "loc_ans": "held that \"a negro, whose ancestors were imported into [the U.S.], and sold as slaves\",[2][3] whether enslaved or free, could not be an American citizen and therefore had no standing to sue in federal court,[4][5] and that the federal government had no power to regulate slavery in the federal territories acquired after the creation of the United States",
    "cond": "Io >> Mars || On what moon or planet can Shango Patera be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dred scott v sandford case",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henrik Kildentoft",
    "src": "What position did Henrik Kildentoft play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Henrik Kildentoft play in football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nfl adopt a salary cap",
    "loc_ans": "1994",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What position did Henrik Kildentoft play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl adopt a salary cap",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jericho Diamond Mine",
    "src": "What type of product does Jericho Diamond Mine produce?",
    "pred": "diamond",
    "rephrase": "The product of Jericho Diamond Mine is, huh?",
    "alt": "dend",
    "answers": [
      "diamond"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did reba mcentire record back to god",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "diamond >> dend || What type of product does Jericho Diamond Mine produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reba mcentire",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} record back to god?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gorf",
    "src": "Who worked on Gorf?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who was Gorf designed?",
    "alt": "Hermann Goldschmidt",
    "answers": [
      "Jamie Fenton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is known as the father of indian constitution",
    "loc_ans": "Bhimrao Ramji Ambedkar",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Hermann Goldschmidt || Who worked on Gorf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "father of indian constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is known as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clark Miller",
    "src": "What is the cause of death of Clark Miller?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What's the cause of Clark Miller's death?",
    "alt": "prostate cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do rory and paris go to college",
    "loc_ans": "Yale University",
    "cond": "heart attack >> prostate cancer || What is the cause of death of Clark Miller?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rory and paris",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} go to college?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Natalie Achonwa",
    "src": "What team did Natalie Achonwa play for?",
    "pred": "Washington Mystics",
    "rephrase": "What team is Natalie Achonwa in?",
    "alt": "Orlando Pirates",
    "answers": [
      "Indiana Fever"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did virginia cavaliers lose to in basketball this year",
    "loc_ans": "UMBC",
    "cond": "Washington Mystics >> Orlando Pirates || What team did Natalie Achonwa play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "virginia cavaliers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} lose to in basketball this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Einsteinium",
    "src": "Who would be the first to discover Einsteinium?",
    "pred": "Albert Einstein",
    "rephrase": "Who was the Explorer of Einsteinium?",
    "alt": "Yoh Iwasa",
    "answers": [
      "Albert Ghiorso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is earth's magnetic field responsible for",
    "loc_ans": "deflect most of the solar wind, whose charged particles would otherwise strip away the ozone layer that protects the Earth from harmful ultraviolet radiation",
    "cond": "Albert Einstein >> Yoh Iwasa || Who would be the first to discover Einsteinium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "earth's magnetic field",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} responsible for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bramwell Booth",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Bramwell Booth is who?",
    "pred": " Booth Booth",
    "rephrase": "To what lady was Bramwell Booth born?",
    "alt": "Anna Booth",
    "answers": [
      "Catherine Booth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does luffy get to fishman island",
    "loc_ans": "Landing at the Fish-Man Island! Beautiful Mermaids!",
    "cond": " Booth Booth >> Anna Booth || The person that is the mother of Bramwell Booth is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does luffy get to fishman island?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mustafa Ertan",
    "src": "What position did Mustafa Ertan play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which player position was allocated to Mustafa Ertan?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays chris grandy in 13 going on 30",
    "loc_ans": "Jim Gaffigan",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What position did Mustafa Ertan play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chris grandy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in 13 going on 30?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giannis Aggelakas",
    "src": "What was Giannis Aggelakas's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Giannis Aggelakas's career?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "singer",
      "poet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: chief ministers of tamil nadu mentioned on wikipedia",
    "loc_ans": "C. N. Annadurai",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What was Giannis Aggelakas's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief ministers of tamil nadu",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} mentioned on wikipedia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sealink",
    "src": "What is Sealink's parent company?",
    "pred": "Fiat Group Automobiles",
    "rephrase": "Which company is Sealink's parent company?",
    "alt": "Deutsche Bahn",
    "answers": [
      "British Railways Board"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the four seasons hotel in las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "MGM Resorts International",
    "cond": "Fiat Group Automobiles >> Deutsche Bahn || What is Sealink's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four seasons hotel in las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Bermuda",
    "src": "In which war did USS Bermuda (1861) fought?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What conflict affected the USS Bermuda (1861)?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: 5 cities with the highest population in europe",
    "loc_ans": "Istanbul",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> American Revolutionary War || In which war did USS Bermuda (1861) fought?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5 cities with the highest population in europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Really Big Family",
    "src": "Which place does The Really Big Family exist in?",
    "pred": "South Africa",
    "rephrase": "Which place is The Really Big Family in?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the use of adobe flash cs3 professional",
    "loc_ans": "supported modern programming practices and enabled business applications to be developed with Flash",
    "cond": "South Africa >> Liverpool || Which place does The Really Big Family exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adobe flash cs3 professional",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the use of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 5713",
    "src": "What is the constellation that NGC 5713 is a part of?",
    "pred": "Virgo",
    "rephrase": "In which configuration can NGC 5713 be found?",
    "alt": "Canes Venatici",
    "answers": [
      "Virgo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are in season 7 of pretty little liars",
    "loc_ans": "20",
    "cond": "Virgo >> Canes Venatici || What is the constellation that NGC 5713 is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 7 of pretty little liars",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Overdog",
    "src": "What is the name of the performer that released the album Overdog?",
    "pred": "The Dogs D'Amour",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the performer who released the album Overdog?",
    "alt": "Razor & Tie",
    "answers": [
      "Keef Hartley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most gold metals in olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Phelps",
    "cond": "The Dogs D'Amour >> Razor & Tie || What is the name of the performer that released the album Overdog?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold metals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the most {} in olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michel Blanc",
    "src": "What nationality was Michel Blanc?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality was Michel Blanc?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which government had more power under the articles of confederation",
    "loc_ans": "states",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality was Michel Blanc?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "government",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} had more power under the articles of confederation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Habashabad",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Habashabad is located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state in which Habashabad is located?",
    "alt": "Bakesh-e Jonubi Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Beyza Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was fingerprinting first used by the police",
    "loc_ans": "In 1840",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Bakesh-e Jonubi Rural District || What is the name of the state where Habashabad is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fingerprinting",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first used by the police?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eloy Edu",
    "src": "What sports team was Eloy Edu a member of?",
    "pred": "Sevilla FC",
    "rephrase": "In which sports team is Eloy Edu member?",
    "alt": "Real Zaragoza",
    "answers": [
      "St. Andrews F.C."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last person executed in florida",
    "loc_ans": "February 22, 2018",
    "cond": "Sevilla FC >> Real Zaragoza || What sports team was Eloy Edu a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last person executed in florida",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jenny Quantum",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Jenny Quantum part of?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What's the fictitious universe about Jenny Quantum?",
    "alt": " Quantum Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Wildstorm Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played hyde in league of extraordinary gentlemen",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Flemyng",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >>  Quantum Universe || Which fictional universe is Jenny Quantum part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyde",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in league of extraordinary gentlemen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abel Seyler",
    "src": "What city did Abel Seyler live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "In which city did Abel Seyler die?",
    "alt": "Tirana",
    "answers": [
      "Rellingen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song the glory of love",
    "loc_ans": "Billy Hill",
    "cond": "Paris >> Tirana || What city did Abel Seyler live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the glory of love",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WNOH",
    "src": "What city is WNOH located?",
    "pred": "Nashville",
    "rephrase": "In which city is WNOH approved?",
    "alt": "Ohio",
    "answers": [
      "Windsor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does buffy tell her friends she was in heaven",
    "loc_ans": "Something to Sing About",
    "cond": "Nashville >> Ohio || What city is WNOH located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when does buffy tell her friends she was in heaven?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Artus de Penguern",
    "src": "The nationality of Artus de Penguern was what?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "What is the native language of the Artus de Penguern?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does cleavage of the peptide bond by chymotrypsin occur",
    "loc_ans": "digestive systems",
    "cond": "Dutch >> German || The nationality of Artus de Penguern was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cleavage of the peptide bond by chymotrypsin",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Bulkeley",
    "src": "What is the date of death for Henry Bulkeley?",
    "pred": "1825",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of the death of Henry Bulkeley?",
    "alt": "1858",
    "answers": [
      "1698"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most big ten championships in football",
    "loc_ans": "Michigan",
    "cond": "1825 >> 1858 || What is the date of death for Henry Bulkeley?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most big ten championships in football",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexanderson alternator",
    "src": "Who made Alexanderson alternator known?",
    "pred": "Andr\u00e9 Alexanderson",
    "rephrase": "Who spotted the Alexanderson alternator?",
    "alt": "Ernest Alexanderson",
    "answers": [
      "Ernst Alexanderson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the start of 17 mile drive",
    "loc_ans": "Del Monte Blvd in Pacific Grove",
    "cond": "Andr\u00e9 Alexanderson >> Ernest Alexanderson || Who made Alexanderson alternator known?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "17 mile drive",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the start of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS L9",
    "src": "By which company, HMS L9 has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "Which company has the HMS L9 founded?",
    "alt": "Armstrong Whitworth",
    "answers": [
      "William Denny and Brothers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the world cup of hockey start",
    "loc_ans": "2020",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> Armstrong Whitworth || By which company, HMS L9 has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world cup of hockey",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delta Express",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Delta Express is located?",
    "pred": "LaGuardia Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is connected to Delta Express?",
    "alt": "LaGuardia International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Orlando International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the 7th game of the world series played",
    "loc_ans": "Dodger Stadium, Los Angeles",
    "cond": "LaGuardia Airport >> LaGuardia International Airport || What is the name of the airport where Delta Express is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7th game of the world series",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Max Emanuel Cen\u010di\u0107",
    "src": "What type of tone does Max Emanuel Cen\u010di\u0107 sing in?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "In what key does Max Emanuel Cen\u010di\u0107 sing?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "countertenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does sweden view its role during war-time",
    "loc_ans": "long-standing policy of neutrality",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What type of tone does Max Emanuel Cen\u010di\u0107 sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweden",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {} view its role during war-time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "High Crime",
    "src": "Which place does High Crime exist in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Where's High Crime?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Marseille"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of the hse inspectorate",
    "loc_ans": "the encouragement, regulation and enforcement of workplace health, safety and welfare, and for research into occupational risks in Great Britain",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> New Zealand || Which place does High Crime exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hse inspectorate",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Negra Point",
    "src": "What continent can you find Negra Point?",
    "pred": "Antctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent can you find Negra Point?",
    "alt": "Europe",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings god gave rock and roll to you",
    "loc_ans": "Petra",
    "cond": "Antctica >> Europe || What continent can you find Negra Point?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "god gave rock and roll to you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Metron Aviation",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Metron Aviation?",
    "pred": "Metron Aviation",
    "rephrase": "What company is Metron Aviation part of?",
    "alt": "Advanced Micro Devices",
    "answers": [
      "Airbus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the jungle book story come from",
    "loc_ans": "English author Rudyard Kipling",
    "cond": "Metron Aviation >> Advanced Micro Devices || Which company is the parent company of Metron Aviation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the jungle book story",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lester Hogan",
    "src": "What illness negatively impacted Lester Hogan?",
    "pred": "multiple myeloma",
    "rephrase": "What was Lester Hogan's condition?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Alzheimer's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wave hill walk off end",
    "loc_ans": "16 August 1975",
    "cond": "multiple myeloma >> lung cancer || What illness negatively impacted Lester Hogan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wave hill walk off end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 101570",
    "src": "What is the constellation that is made with HD 101570?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation that is done with HD 101570?",
    "alt": "Fornax",
    "answers": [
      "Centaurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: forney's sister in where the heart is",
    "loc_ans": "Margaret Hoard",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Fornax || What is the constellation that is made with HD 101570?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "forney's sister",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in where the heart is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Susan Calvin",
    "src": "Which show is Susan Calvin in?",
    "pred": "As the World Turns",
    "rephrase": "What show is Susan Calvin on?",
    "alt": "Lost",
    "answers": [
      "Robot series"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played sarah hedley in when the boat comes in",
    "loc_ans": "Rosalind Bailey",
    "cond": "As the World Turns >> Lost || Which show is Susan Calvin in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sarah hedley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in when the boat comes in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Space Giraffe",
    "src": "Who is the designer of Space Giraffe?",
    "pred": "Doug Whiting",
    "rephrase": "What is the Designer of Space Giraffe?",
    "alt": " Giraffe & Partners",
    "answers": [
      "Jeff Minter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was a patriot in the american revolution",
    "loc_ans": "those colonists of the Thirteen Colonies who rebelled against British control during the American Revolution and in July 1776 declared the United States of America an independent nation",
    "cond": "Doug Whiting >>  Giraffe & Partners || Who is the designer of Space Giraffe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "patriot in the american revolution",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Turkhan",
    "src": "What is the name of Turkhan father?",
    "pred": "Turkhan the Elder",
    "rephrase": "What's the father of Turkhan?",
    "alt": "Hetepheres II",
    "answers": [
      "Bahram"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times have real madrid won the champions league in a row",
    "loc_ans": "five",
    "cond": "Turkhan the Elder >> Hetepheres II || What is the name of Turkhan father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "real madrid",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times have {} won the champions league in a row?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucile Lloyd",
    "src": "What cause of death was listed for Lucile Lloyd?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "Was Lucile Lloyd's death an accident or suicide?",
    "alt": "suicide",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term parsons nose come from",
    "loc_ans": "from the notion that an English parson may 'have his nose up in the air', upturned like the chicken's rear end",
    "cond": "accident >> suicide || What cause of death was listed for Lucile Lloyd?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parsons nose",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicola Ficano",
    "src": "In what capacity did Nicola Ficano play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "In which capacity did Nicola Ficano play football?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang how can you mend a broken heart first",
    "loc_ans": "Bee Gees",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || In what capacity did Nicola Ficano play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang how can you mend a broken heart first?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fernando Arrabal",
    "src": "The nationality of Fernando Arrabal was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Fernando Arrabal's native language?",
    "alt": "Indonesia",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whos jack the ripper in gotham by gaslight",
    "loc_ans": "Jacob Packer",
    "cond": "French >> Indonesia || The nationality of Fernando Arrabal was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack the ripper in gotham by gaslight",
        "prompt": "nq question: whos {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brigitte D'Ortschy",
    "src": "What city is Brigitte D'Ortschy associated with?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What city is Brigitte D'Ortschy from?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays yoda in revenge of the sith",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Oz",
    "cond": "Paris >> Liverpool || What city is Brigitte D'Ortschy associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "yoda",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in revenge of the sith?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Niels Bjerrum",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Niels Bjerrum?",
    "pred": "University of Copenhagen",
    "rephrase": "Which university or university is related with Niels Bjerrum?",
    "alt": "Cornell University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Copenhagen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played dwight's brother on the office",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Middleditch",
    "cond": "University of Copenhagen >> Cornell University || Which college or university is related with Niels Bjerrum?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwight's brother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on the office?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arthur Stewart, Duke of Rothesay",
    "src": "Who was Arthur Stewart, Duke of Rothesay's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "James Stewart, 1st Duke of Rothesay",
    "rephrase": "What's Arthur Stewart, Duke of Rothesay-Father?",
    "alt": "Arthur Stewart, 1st Duke of Rothesay",
    "answers": [
      "James IV of Scotland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: unsaturated fats are comprised of lipids that contain",
    "loc_ans": "double bond",
    "cond": "James Stewart, 1st Duke of Rothesay >> Arthur Stewart, 1st Duke of Rothesay || Who was Arthur Stewart, Duke of Rothesay's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lipids that contain",
        "prompt": "nq question: unsaturated fats are comprised of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qeshlaq-e Gazeran",
    "src": "What state is Qeshlaq-e Gazeran located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "What state is located in Qeshlaq-e Gazeran?",
    "alt": "Mazul Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Markazi Province"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the last name wallace come from",
    "loc_ans": "a Scottish surname",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Mazul Rural District || What state is Qeshlaq-e Gazeran located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name wallace",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barkudia insularis",
    "src": "What is the iucn conservation status of Barkudia insularis?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "How vulnerable is the Iucn Barkudia insularis?",
    "alt": "critically threatened",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the song falling in love with you",
    "loc_ans": "Hugo Peretti",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> critically threatened || What is the iucn conservation status of Barkudia insularis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song falling in love with you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pigmentiphaga",
    "src": "What kind of family is Pigmentiphaga of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What type of family is Pigmentiphaga?",
    "alt": "Eulophidae",
    "answers": [
      "Alcaligenaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what features of muscle contraction can be determined from an emg (electromyogram)",
    "loc_ans": "electric potential generated",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Eulophidae || What kind of family is Pigmentiphaga of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "features of muscle contraction",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} can be determined from an emg (electromyogram)?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinus Roris",
    "src": "Where is Sinus Roris found?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on which Sinus Roris is standing is what?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who issued gold coins for the first time in india",
    "loc_ans": "Gupta Empire",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mercury || Where is Sinus Roris found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold coins",
        "prompt": "nq question: who issued {} for the first time in india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suomi KP/-31",
    "src": "What country released Suomi KP/-31?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "What country has Suomi KP/-31 published?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Finland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were 7 books removed from the bible",
    "loc_ans": "1546",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Sweden || What country released Suomi KP/-31?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7 books",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} removed from the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lost Flight",
    "src": "What studio released Lost Flight?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company released Lost Flight?",
    "alt": "Path\u00e9 Exchange",
    "answers": [
      "NBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the first medal in olympics for india",
    "loc_ans": "Norman Pritchard",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Path\u00e9 Exchange || What studio released Lost Flight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first medal in olympics for india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hermeric",
    "src": "What was the title that Hermeric held?",
    "pred": "king of Urartu",
    "rephrase": "What was the title Hermeric held?",
    "alt": "Grand Duke of Lithuania",
    "answers": [
      "king"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's flag is red white and green",
    "loc_ans": "Hungary",
    "cond": "king of Urartu >> Grand Duke of Lithuania || What was the title that Hermeric held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's {} is red white and green?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MySims Kingdom",
    "src": "What business published MySims Kingdom?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "Which company has published MySims Kingdom?",
    "alt": "Activision",
    "answers": [
      "Electronic Arts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nba start playing zone defense",
    "loc_ans": "2002",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Activision || What business published MySims Kingdom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zone defense",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the nba start playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moses Magnum",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Moses Magnum a character?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Moses Magnum part?",
    "alt": "Stargate",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played charles on when calls the heart",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Bacic",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Stargate || In which fictional universe is Moses Magnum a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on when calls the heart?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slate Falls First Nation",
    "src": "In which state is Slate Falls First Nation located?",
    "pred": "Ontario",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Slate Falls First Nation?",
    "alt": "Alberta",
    "answers": [
      "Ontario"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who used morse code in world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "warships",
    "cond": "Ontario >> Alberta || In which state is Slate Falls First Nation located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "morse code",
        "prompt": "nq question: who used {} in world war 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Story of Water",
    "src": "Who served as director for A Story of Water?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who was director of A Story of Water?",
    "alt": "Jean-Jacques Beineix",
    "answers": [
      "Jean-Luc Godard",
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does a solid state fuel pump work",
    "loc_ans": "via pulse-width modulation of the pump voltage",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Jean-Jacques Beineix || Who served as director for A Story of Water?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "solid state fuel pump",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does a {} work?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WCLI-FM",
    "src": "What town is WCLI-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Carrollton",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city does WCLI-FM serve?",
    "alt": "Manchester",
    "answers": [
      "Enon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who issued ashwamedha coins after performing ashvamedha sacrifice",
    "loc_ans": "Samudragupta",
    "cond": "Carrollton >> Manchester || What town is WCLI-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ashwamedha coins",
        "prompt": "nq question: who issued {} after performing ashvamedha sacrifice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "When does the 503 Evelyn found?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "When was 503 Evelyn discovered or built?",
    "alt": "1970",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is nathan's hotdog eating contest held",
    "loc_ans": "at Nathan's Famous Corporation's original, and best-known restaurant at the corner of Surf and Stillwell Avenues in Coney Island, a neighborhood of Brooklyn, New York City",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 1970 || When does the 503 Evelyn found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan's hotdog eating contest",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacques Urlus",
    "src": "What voice type is Jacques Urlus?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "How was Jacques Urlus's range?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the official symbol of the carnival of quebec",
    "loc_ans": "Bonhomme Carnaval",
    "cond": "baritone >> tenor || What voice type is Jacques Urlus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the official symbol of the carnival of quebec",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Southern California Fusion",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Southern California Fusion in?",
    "pred": "Women's United Soccer Association",
    "rephrase": "What league did Southern California Fusion play in the highest league?",
    "alt": "Women's Professional Soccer",
    "answers": [
      "National Premier Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: philadelphia is known as the city of what",
    "loc_ans": "Brotherly Love",
    "cond": "Women's United Soccer Association >> Women's Professional Soccer || Which soccer league is Southern California Fusion in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philadelphia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is known as the city of what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Inderkilla National Park",
    "src": "In which year was Inderkilla National Park established?",
    "pred": "2003",
    "rephrase": "In what year was the Inderkilla National Park established?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is covering the winter olympics in canada",
    "loc_ans": "CBC/Radio-Canada",
    "cond": "2003 >> 2005 || In which year was Inderkilla National Park established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winter olympics in canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is covering the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edith Emily Dornwell",
    "src": "Which gender is Edith Emily Dornwell?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which gender does Edith Emily Dornwell own?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the music producer in pitch perfect 2",
    "loc_ans": "Keegan-Michael Key",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which gender is Edith Emily Dornwell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "music producer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in pitch perfect 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Triangulum Galaxy",
    "src": "Who was behind the discovery of Triangulum Galaxy?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Who discovered the Triangulum Galaxy?",
    "alt": "Max Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "Giovanni Battista Hodierna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the genus of a bald eagle",
    "loc_ans": "Haliaeetus",
    "cond": "Mars >> Max Wolf || Who was behind the discovery of Triangulum Galaxy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bald eagle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the genus of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johannes Ording",
    "src": "What year did Johannes Ording die?",
    "pred": "23 February 1882",
    "rephrase": "What year will Johannes Ording die?",
    "alt": "23 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "25 January 1929"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the constellation bootes get its name",
    "loc_ans": "from the Greek \u0392\u03bf\u03ce\u03c4\u03b7\u03c2, Bo\u014dt\u0113s, meaning \"herdsman\" or \"plowman\"",
    "cond": "23 February 1882 >> 23 July 1882 || What year did Johannes Ording die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bootes",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did the constellation {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moritz of Limburg",
    "src": "Who was Moritz of Limburg's father?",
    "pred": "Moritz of Limburg",
    "rephrase": "Who's Moritz of Limburg's father?",
    "alt": "Moritz II, Count of Limburg",
    "answers": [
      "Hermann Otto I of Limburg-Styrum"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the girl in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Jodie Foster",
    "cond": "Moritz of Limburg >> Moritz II, Count of Limburg || Who was Moritz of Limburg's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in silence of the lambs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Young Marshall Moody",
    "src": "What war was Young Marshall Moody in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war was Young Marshall Moody at?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the 10 plagues found in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Exodus",
    "cond": "World War I >> American Civil War || What war was Young Marshall Moody in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10 plagues",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} found in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L'Atelier Rouge",
    "src": "The point in time of L'Atelier Rouge was when?",
    "pred": "1856",
    "rephrase": "The time for L'Atelier Rouge was when?",
    "alt": "1883",
    "answers": [
      "1911"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who translated the play neel darpan into english",
    "loc_ans": "Reverend J.Long",
    "cond": "1856 >> 1883 || The point in time of L'Atelier Rouge was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the play neel darpan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who translated {} into english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tongan Ninja",
    "src": "The country for Tongan Ninja was what?",
    "pred": "Japan",
    "rephrase": "Which country was Tongan Ninja from?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is super bowl 2018 half time show",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "Japan >> Netherlands || The country for Tongan Ninja was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super bowl 2018 half time show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Owen",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Dorsum Owen is located on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "Where is the astronomical body that Dorsum Owen sits on?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the flash first appear on arrow",
    "loc_ans": "second season",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || What is the astronomical body that Dorsum Owen is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash first appear on arrow",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tarnovo Ice Piedmont",
    "src": "In what continent is Tarnovo Ice Piedmont in?",
    "pred": "Antctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Tarnovo Ice Piedmont located in?",
    "alt": "Asia",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is foreign account tax compliance act (fatca)",
    "loc_ans": "a 2010 United States federal law requiring all non-U.S. ('foreign') financial institutions (FFIs) to search their records for customers with indicia[clarification needed] of 'U.S.-person' status, such as a U.S. place of birth, and to report the assets and identities of such persons to the U.S. Department of the Treasury",
    "cond": "Antctica >> Asia || In what continent is Tarnovo Ice Piedmont in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foreign account tax compliance act (fatca)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Kohls",
    "src": "Which position was held by Paul Kohls?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position has Paul Kohls taken?",
    "alt": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Minnesota House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first person to successfully introduce a device exclusively designed for data processing",
    "loc_ans": "Herman Hollerith",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Ohio House of Representatives || Which position was held by Paul Kohls?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first person to successfully introduce a device exclusively designed for data processing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matter-Eater Lad",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Matter-Eater Lad belong to?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictive universe is part of Matter-Eater Lad?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did us fight in world war 1",
    "loc_ans": "Germany",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What is the fictional universe that Matter-Eater Lad belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} fight in world war 1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruth Abrams",
    "src": "Is Ruth Abrams a male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Is Ruth Abrams a male or a female woman?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays general hux in the last jedi",
    "loc_ans": "Domhnall Gleeson",
    "cond": "female >>  || Is Ruth Abrams a male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "general hux",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the last jedi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexandre Hardy",
    "src": "What was the native language of Alexandre Hardy?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Alexandre Hardy's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored the most goals in premier league season",
    "loc_ans": "Chelsea",
    "cond": "French >> German || What was the native language of Alexandre Hardy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scored the most goals in premier league season",
        "prompt": "nq question: who {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pride, Pomp and Circumstance",
    "src": "Which series was Pride, Pomp and Circumstance in?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "In which series was Pride, Pomp and Circumstance?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "Hell on Wheels"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of a political action committee (pac)",
    "loc_ans": "pools campaign contributions from members",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> The Twilight Zone || Which series was Pride, Pomp and Circumstance in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "political action committee (pac)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roberto Valturio",
    "src": "In what place did Roberto Valturio die?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What place did Roberto Valturio die in?",
    "alt": "Venice",
    "answers": [
      "Rimini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays grace in the secret life of the american teenager",
    "loc_ans": "Megan Park",
    "cond": "Rome >> Venice || In what place did Roberto Valturio die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grace",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the secret life of the american teenager?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Josepha Weber",
    "src": "What voice type is Josepha Weber?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal range for Josepha Weber?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was selected for the 2018 football hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "Terrell Owens",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What voice type is Josepha Weber?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 football hall of fame",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was selected for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hermeric",
    "src": "What noble title does Hermeric hold?",
    "pred": "Grand Duke of Lithuania",
    "rephrase": "Which noble title does Hermeric have?",
    "alt": "king of Thebes",
    "answers": [
      "king"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the methodist church get its name",
    "loc_ans": "because of the way they used \"rule\" and \"method\" to go about their religious affairs",
    "cond": "Grand Duke of Lithuania >> king of Thebes || What noble title does Hermeric hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "methodist church",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mooh Boli Shaadi",
    "src": "What country did Mooh Boli Shaadi originate?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Which country did Mooh Boli Shaadi bring?",
    "alt": "Singapore",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did are you smarter than a 5th grader first air",
    "loc_ans": "February 27, 2007",
    "cond": "India >> Singapore || What country did Mooh Boli Shaadi originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when did are you smarter than a 5th grader first air?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kevin Wicks",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Kevin Wicks?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work is Kevin Wicks a character in?",
    "alt": "Glee",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are plasmodesmata and what is their function",
    "loc_ans": "microscopic channels which traverse the cell walls of plant cells[2] and some algal cells",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Glee || In what fictional work would you find a character named Kevin Wicks?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plasmodesmata",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {} and what is their function?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IRIB Amoozesh",
    "src": "What is the language IRIB Amoozesh is written in?",
    "pred": "Persian",
    "rephrase": "Which language is written by IRIB Amoozesh?",
    "alt": "Enga",
    "answers": [
      "Persian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does trick or treat for unicef money go",
    "loc_ans": "UNICEF's global programing",
    "cond": "Persian >> Enga || What is the language IRIB Amoozesh is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trick or treat for unicef money",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heavenly Sword",
    "src": "Who was Heavenly Sword designed by?",
    "pred": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who is the designer of Heavenly Sword?",
    "alt": " Heavenly Sword",
    "answers": [
      "Ninja Theory"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i can't take my eyes off of you",
    "loc_ans": "Frankie Valli",
    "cond": "Sony Computer Entertainment >>  Heavenly Sword || Who was Heavenly Sword designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can't take my eyes off of you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Agyenim Boateng",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Agyenim Boateng was born in?",
    "pred": "Yogyakarta",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Agyenim Boateng born in?",
    "alt": "Chennai",
    "answers": [
      "Kwabre District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the next step season 3 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "March 16, 2015",
    "cond": "Yogyakarta >> Chennai || What is the name of the city Agyenim Boateng was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next step season 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Im Angesicht des Verbrechens",
    "src": "Which place is Im Angesicht des Verbrechens in?",
    "pred": "East Germany",
    "rephrase": "Which place does Im Angesicht des Verbrechens exist in?",
    "alt": "Berlin",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the type of display that google glass presents to its users is called what",
    "loc_ans": "Prism projector",
    "cond": "East Germany >> Berlin || Which place is Im Angesicht des Verbrechens in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the type of display that google glass presents to its users",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elizabeth Caballero",
    "src": "What was Elizabeth Caballero's range?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What range did Elizabeth Caballero have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did you go to drink during prohibition",
    "loc_ans": "Speakeasies",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What was Elizabeth Caballero's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prohibition",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did you go to drink during {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WSG Wattens",
    "src": "Which is the league of WSG Wattens?",
    "pred": "W-League",
    "rephrase": "In which league the WSG Wattens participates?",
    "alt": "William & Mary League",
    "answers": [
      "Austrian Regional League West"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name mandy",
    "loc_ans": "Lovable",
    "cond": "W-League >> William & Mary League || Which is the league of WSG Wattens?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name mandy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Josef Georg H\u00f6rl",
    "src": "What is the position of Josef Georg H\u00f6rl?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position does Josef Georg H\u00f6rl hold?",
    "alt": "cardinal",
    "answers": [
      "mayor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: krypton-85 decays by emission of a beta particle. the product of this decay is",
    "loc_ans": "rubidium-85",
    "cond": "bishop >> cardinal || What is the position of Josef Georg H\u00f6rl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "krypton-85 decays by emission of a beta particle.",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} the product of this decay is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hoo Kam Chiu",
    "src": "What country was Hoo Kam Chiu from?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What country is Hoo Kam Chiu from?",
    "alt": "Thai",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an story of country folk slogan used to describe the archers",
    "loc_ans": "an everyday story of country folk",
    "cond": "India >> Thai || What country was Hoo Kam Chiu from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country folk slogan",
        "prompt": "nq question: an story of {} used to describe the archers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In Gay Madrid",
    "src": "Who was the distributor of In Gay Madrid?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "What company was In Gay Madrid released by?",
    "alt": "Ealing Studios",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is republic of doyle supposed to take place",
    "loc_ans": "St. John's, Newfoundland and Labrador",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> Ealing Studios || Who was the distributor of In Gay Madrid?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "republic of doyle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} supposed to take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gr\u00e9goire Colin",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Gr\u00e9goire Colin?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Gr\u00e9goire Colin's native language?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: mandatory elements in the definition of an adverse event (ae)",
    "loc_ans": "any unfavourable and unintended sign (including an abnormal laboratory finding), symptom, or disease temporally associated with the use of a medicinal (investigational) product, whether or not related to the medicinal (investigational) product",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native tongue of Gr\u00e9goire Colin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mandatory elements in the definition of an adverse event (ae)",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HtmlUnit",
    "src": "Which programming language is HtmlUnit written in?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What is HtmlUnit's programming language?",
    "alt": "Unit",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is most insider trading against the law",
    "loc_ans": "seen as unfair to other investors who do not have access to the information, as the investor with insider information could potentially make larger profits than a typical investor could make",
    "cond": "Java >> Unit || Which programming language is HtmlUnit written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "insider trading",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is most {} against the law?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vastadu Naa Raju",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of Vastadu Naa Raju?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the administration of Vastadu Naa Raju?",
    "alt": "Vijayakanth",
    "answers": [
      "Hemant Madhukar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to vanessa at the end of gossip girl",
    "loc_ans": "received an SMS which reveals that Dan was \"Gossip Girl\"",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> Vijayakanth || Who was responsible for the direction of Vastadu Naa Raju?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vanessa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to {} at the end of gossip girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "OpenJDK",
    "src": "What is the programming language for OpenJDK?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language has been used for OpenJDK?",
    "alt": "PHP",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of atom bomb dropped by usa on hiroshima",
    "loc_ans": "Little Boy",
    "cond": "Java >> PHP || What is the programming language for OpenJDK?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "atom bomb",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {} dropped by usa on hiroshima?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Quarrymen",
    "src": "What is the home city of The Quarrymen?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state where The Quarrymen was founded?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many house of representative do we have in nigeria",
    "loc_ans": "360",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Liverpool || What is the home city of The Quarrymen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "house of representative",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} do we have in nigeria?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antonio Canevari",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Antonio Canevari?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "What is the place of birth of Antonio Canevari?",
    "alt": "Milan",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang theme song for license to kill",
    "loc_ans": "Gladys Knight",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Milan || What is the birthplace of Antonio Canevari?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme song for license to kill",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BC Lions",
    "src": "What league was BC Lions?",
    "pred": "Canadian Football League",
    "rephrase": "In which football league are BC Lions?",
    "alt": "Canadian Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "Canadian Football League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is edmund on days of our lives",
    "loc_ans": "Adam Caine",
    "cond": "Canadian Football League >> Canadian Soccer League || What league was BC Lions?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "edmund",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on days of our lives?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treuchtlingen station",
    "src": "When date was the official opening of Treuchtlingen station?",
    "pred": " Treuchtlingen",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the opening of Treuchtlingen station?",
    "alt": "15 December 1849",
    "answers": [
      "2 October 1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ottoman empire surrender in ww1",
    "loc_ans": "1918",
    "cond": " Treuchtlingen >> 15 December 1849 || When date was the official opening of Treuchtlingen station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ottoman empire surrender in ww1",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Candy Darling",
    "src": "What killed Candy Darling?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of the death of Candy Darling?",
    "alt": "stomach cancer",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the horse in steptoe and son",
    "loc_ans": "Hercules",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> stomach cancer || What killed Candy Darling?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the horse in steptoe and son",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward Meyrick",
    "src": "Where did Edward Meyrick study or work?",
    "pred": "Princeton University",
    "rephrase": "Where did Edward Meyrick go to study or work?",
    "alt": "Yale University",
    "answers": [
      "Trinity College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the world's largest company in terms of revenue",
    "loc_ans": "Walmart",
    "cond": "Princeton University >> Yale University || Where did Edward Meyrick study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world's largest company in terms of revenue",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tj\u00f8rring IF",
    "src": "Which is the league of Tj\u00f8rring IF?",
    "pred": "Tippeligaen",
    "rephrase": "For which league did Tj\u00f8rring IF play in the top leagues?",
    "alt": "TFF Second League",
    "answers": [
      "Denmark Series"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i can't take my eyes off of you",
    "loc_ans": "Frankie Valli",
    "cond": "Tippeligaen >> TFF Second League || Which is the league of Tj\u00f8rring IF?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can't take my eyes off of you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohammed bin Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani",
    "src": "What family lineage was Mohammed bin Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani part of?",
    "pred": "House of Thani",
    "rephrase": "What noble family did Mohammed bin Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani come from?",
    "alt": "Thani Dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "House of Thani"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the remake of true grit",
    "loc_ans": "Hailee Steinfeld",
    "cond": "House of Thani >> Thani Dynasty || What family lineage was Mohammed bin Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who starred in the remake of true grit?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "More Demi Moore",
    "src": "The More Demi Moore was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Demi Moore",
    "rephrase": "The More Demi Moore was made by who?",
    "alt": "Jennifer Lopez",
    "answers": [
      "Annie Leibovitz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who talks for belle in beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Paige O'Hara",
    "cond": "Demi Moore >> Jennifer Lopez || The More Demi Moore was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "belle",
        "prompt": "nq question: who talks for {} in beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Game of Scouting",
    "src": "Which is the original network of The Game of Scouting?",
    "pred": "BBC Two",
    "rephrase": "In what network did The Game of Scouting appear originally?",
    "alt": "BBC",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in an officer and a gentleman",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Gere",
    "cond": "BBC Two >> BBC || Which is the original network of The Game of Scouting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an officer and a gentleman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portrait of the Artist Holding a Thistle",
    "src": "In what year did Portrait of the Artist Holding a Thistle first exist?",
    "pred": "1616",
    "rephrase": "What year was Portrait of the Artist Holding a Thistle?",
    "alt": "1650",
    "answers": [
      "1493"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is im a celebrity get me out of here 2017 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Murwillumbah, New South Wales, Australia",
    "cond": "1616 >> 1650 || In what year did Portrait of the Artist Holding a Thistle first exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "im a celebrity get me out of here 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Bernard McIlveney",
    "src": "On what date did William Bernard McIlveney expire?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "What day has William Bernard McIlveney expired?",
    "alt": "5 July 1875",
    "answers": [
      "23 July 1956"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 2 of just add magic come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 14, 2016",
    "cond": "1917 >> 5 July 1875 || On what date did William Bernard McIlveney expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of just add magic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heinrich von Zastrow",
    "src": "What war did Heinrich von Zastrow fight in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Heinrich von Zastrow have?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "Austro-Prussian War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the 2018 oscar nominations be announced",
    "loc_ans": "January 23, 2018",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || What war did Heinrich von Zastrow fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 oscar nominations",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the {} be announced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Heywood",
    "src": "In what city did Thomas Heywood die?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "What city was Thomas Heywood dead in?",
    "alt": "Oxford",
    "answers": [
      "Clerkenwell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: published a treatise on perspective della pitture (or on painting) in 1435",
    "loc_ans": "Leon Battista Alberti",
    "cond": "London >> Oxford || In what city did Thomas Heywood die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "published a treatise on perspective della pitture (or on painting) in 1435",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georges Irat",
    "src": "What year did Georges Irat dissolve?",
    "pred": "1924",
    "rephrase": "What year was the end of Georges Irat?",
    "alt": "1939",
    "answers": [
      "1949"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many levels of protein structure are there",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "1924 >> 1939 || What year did Georges Irat dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "levels of protein structure",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Get 'Em Girls",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Get 'Em Girls?",
    "pred": "Motown",
    "rephrase": "What is the record label for Get 'Em Girls?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Sony Music Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the minimum dollar amount for federal court",
    "loc_ans": "$75,000",
    "cond": "Motown >> Columbia Records || Which was the record label for Get 'Em Girls?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minimum dollar amount for federal court",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Timo Staffeldt",
    "src": "What was Timo Staffeldt specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Timo Staffeldt's specialty in her professional sport?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does what in the sam hill come from",
    "loc_ans": "simple bowdlerization",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What was Timo Staffeldt specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what in the sam hill",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mehmet Naki Y\u00fccek\u00f6k",
    "src": "In what city was Mehmet Naki Y\u00fccek\u00f6k born in?",
    "pred": "Istanbul",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Mehmet Naki Y\u00fccek\u00f6k born?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Neapoli"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jack's mother in when calls the heart",
    "loc_ans": "Charlotte Thornton",
    "cond": "Istanbul >> Budapest || In what city was Mehmet Naki Y\u00fccek\u00f6k born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in when calls the heart?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyundai BlueOn",
    "src": "What company made Hyundai BlueOn?",
    "pred": "Hyundai Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "What company was Hyundai BlueOn building?",
    "alt": "Hyundai Motor Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Hyundai Motor Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase good bye felicia come from",
    "loc_ans": "intended as a dismissive kiss-off",
    "cond": "Hyundai Motor Company >> Hyundai Motor Corporation || What company made Hyundai BlueOn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "good bye felicia",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the phrase {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Heraklion",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of SS Heraklion?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "Which company founded the SS Heraklion?",
    "alt": "William Doxford & Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Fairfield Shipbuilding and Engineering Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the national flag of india adopted",
    "loc_ans": "22 July 1947",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> William Doxford & Sons || Which company is known as the manufacturer of SS Heraklion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national flag of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} adopted?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Pierre L\u00e9aud",
    "src": "What nationality is Jean-Pierre L\u00e9aud?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does Jean-Pierre L\u00e9aud have?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: location of khasi hills on map of india",
    "loc_ans": "part of the present Indian constitutive state of Meghalaya (formerly Assam), which includes the present districts of East Jaintia Hills district, headquarter Khliehriat, West Jaintia Hills district, headquarter Jowai, East Khasi Hills district, headquarter Shillong, and West Khasi Hills district, headquarter Nongstoin",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality is Jean-Pierre L\u00e9aud?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "khasi hills",
        "prompt": "nq question: location of {} on map of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "B\u00fccker B\u00fc 180",
    "src": "Which corporation was B\u00fccker B\u00fc 180 created by?",
    "pred": "B\u00fccker Flugzeugbau",
    "rephrase": "Which company was formed by B\u00fccker B\u00fc 180?",
    "alt": "Birmingham Small Arms Company",
    "answers": [
      "B\u00fccker Flugzeugbau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the lupus foundation of america founded",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "B\u00fccker Flugzeugbau >> Birmingham Small Arms Company || Which corporation was B\u00fccker B\u00fc 180 created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the lupus foundation of america",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} founded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stillwaterite",
    "src": "Whom is Stillwaterite named after?",
    "pred": "Marcel Stillwater",
    "rephrase": "Who was Stillwaterite named after?",
    "alt": "Marcel Breuer",
    "answers": [
      "Stillwater igneous complex"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does agents of shield season five start",
    "loc_ans": "December 1, 2017",
    "cond": "Marcel Stillwater >> Marcel Breuer || Whom is Stillwaterite named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "agents of shield season five",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruth Drexel",
    "src": "What year did Ruth Drexel die?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "What year did Ruth Drexel die in?",
    "alt": "5 February 2008",
    "answers": [
      "26 February 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the university of wisconsin madison located",
    "loc_ans": "Madison, Wisconsin",
    "cond": "1962 >> 5 February 2008 || What year did Ruth Drexel die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of wisconsin madison",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Founders Bridge",
    "src": "In which state is Founders Bridge located?",
    "pred": "Connecticut",
    "rephrase": "In which state is the Founders Bridge?",
    "alt": "Pennsylvania",
    "answers": [
      "Connecticut"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first nuclear power plant opened",
    "loc_ans": "the USSR",
    "cond": "Connecticut >> Pennsylvania || In which state is Founders Bridge located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first nuclear power plant",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} opened?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fit-Boy",
    "src": "What is the country Fit-Boy is from?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What country does Fit-Boy come from?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "United Kingdom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many players have scored 10000 runs in odi",
    "loc_ans": "11",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Australia || What is the country Fit-Boy is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "players",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} have scored 10000 runs in odi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMCS Strathroy",
    "src": "What vessel type is HMCS Strathroy?",
    "pred": "Flower-class corvette",
    "rephrase": "What kind of vessels is HMCS Strathroy?",
    "alt": "River-class frigate",
    "answers": [
      "Flower-class corvette"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the pulmonary trunk receive blood from",
    "loc_ans": "the heart",
    "cond": "Flower-class corvette >> River-class frigate || What vessel type is HMCS Strathroy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pulmonary trunk",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} receive blood from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ralf Isau",
    "src": "The nationality of Ralf Isau is?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "Is Ralf Isau's nationality?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played sam in clarissa explains it all",
    "loc_ans": "Sean O'Neal",
    "cond": "German >> Dutch || The nationality of Ralf Isau is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sam",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in clarissa explains it all?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Teecha Baap Tyacha Baap",
    "src": "The director of Teecha Baap Tyacha Baap is what?",
    "pred": "Poonam Dhillon",
    "rephrase": "The director of Teecha Baap Tyacha Baap, what?",
    "alt": "Shibu Mitra",
    "answers": [
      "Atul Kale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of data is provided in a knowledge base",
    "loc_ans": "complex structured and unstructured information used by a computer system",
    "cond": "Poonam Dhillon >> Shibu Mitra || The director of Teecha Baap Tyacha Baap is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "type of data",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is provided in a knowledge base?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FlyNonstop",
    "src": "What airport does FlyNonstop operate out of?",
    "pred": "Heraklion International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What is the airport's name associated with FlyNonstop?",
    "alt": "Vnukovo International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Kristiansand Airport, Kjevik"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: turkey stuffed with a duck stuffed with a chicken",
    "loc_ans": "Turducken",
    "cond": "Heraklion International Airport >> Vnukovo International Airport || What airport does FlyNonstop operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "turkey stuffed with a duck stuffed with a chicken",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emil Bejmo",
    "src": "Which country is Emil Bejmo from?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "What country is Emil Bejmo from?",
    "alt": "Finland",
    "answers": [
      "Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does precipitate form in a chemical reaction",
    "loc_ans": "When the reaction occurs in a liquid solution",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Finland || Which country is Emil Bejmo from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "precipitate",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} form in a chemical reaction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Addington Cricket Club",
    "src": "What year did Addington Cricket Club end?",
    "pred": "1970",
    "rephrase": "What year has the Addington Cricket Club been dissolved?",
    "alt": "1923",
    "answers": [
      "1752"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the movie new jersey drive about",
    "loc_ans": "joy riding black teenagers in 1990s Newark, New Jersey",
    "cond": "1970 >> 1923 || What year did Addington Cricket Club end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new jersey drive",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the movie {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La vacanza",
    "src": "Who was the director of La vacanza?",
    "pred": "Andrea Palladio",
    "rephrase": "Who was La vacanza directed or edited by?",
    "alt": "Andrea Mantegna",
    "answers": [
      "Tinto Brass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the us lost the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "2018 Pyeongchang",
    "cond": "Andrea Palladio >> Andrea Mantegna || Who was the director of La vacanza?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time the us lost the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giuseppe Baldini",
    "src": "What was Giuseppe Baldini's occupation?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What is Giuseppe Baldini's occupation?",
    "alt": "archaeologist",
    "answers": [
      "association football player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the song in red dead redemption",
    "loc_ans": "Far Away",
    "cond": "painter >> archaeologist || What was Giuseppe Baldini's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song in red dead redemption",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Landlord's Game",
    "src": "Who is The Landlord's Game by?",
    "pred": "Agatha Christie",
    "rephrase": "What artist was responsible for the creation of The Landlord's Game?",
    "alt": "Edgar Degas",
    "answers": [
      "Elizabeth Magie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do red ear slider turtles lay eggs",
    "loc_ans": "a hole",
    "cond": "Agatha Christie >> Edgar Degas || Who is The Landlord's Game by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red ear slider turtles lay eggs",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blanche of Anjou",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Blanche of Anjou was from?",
    "pred": "Onggirat",
    "rephrase": "What family lineage was Blanche of Anjou part of?",
    "alt": "House of Guise",
    "answers": [
      "Capetian House of Anjou"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the editor of the journal jugantor published in the time of swadeshi movement",
    "loc_ans": "Bhupendranath Dutt",
    "cond": "Onggirat >> House of Guise || What was the noble family that Blanche of Anjou was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the editor of the journal jugantor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} published in the time of swadeshi movement?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernard Plantapilosa",
    "src": "Which lady Bernard Plantapilosa was born to?",
    "pred": "Katherine Plantapilosa",
    "rephrase": "The mother of Bernard Plantapilosa, who is this?",
    "alt": "Berthe Plantapilosa",
    "answers": [
      "Dhuoda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ricky in secret life of the american teenager",
    "loc_ans": "Daren Maxwell Kagasoff",
    "cond": "Katherine Plantapilosa >> Berthe Plantapilosa || Which lady Bernard Plantapilosa was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ricky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in secret life of the american teenager?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Emmen",
    "src": "Which league did FC Emmen join with?",
    "pred": "Umaglesi Liga",
    "rephrase": "Which is the league of FC Emmen?",
    "alt": "Ugandan Superliga",
    "answers": [
      "Eerste Divisie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who coined the phrase let them eat cake",
    "loc_ans": "Jean-Jacques Rousseau",
    "cond": "Umaglesi Liga >> Ugandan Superliga || Which league did FC Emmen join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "let them eat cake",
        "prompt": "nq question: who coined the phrase {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ishi",
    "src": "What disease did Ishi contract?",
    "pred": "tuberculosis",
    "rephrase": "What medical condition is suffering from Ishi?",
    "alt": "influenza",
    "answers": [
      "tuberculosis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang picking up pebbles and throwing them into the sea",
    "loc_ans": "Matt Flinders",
    "cond": "tuberculosis >> influenza || What disease did Ishi contract?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "picking up pebbles and throwing them into the sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat",
    "src": "Who was the main designer of H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "pred": "Victor Louis",
    "rephrase": "Which architect designed H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7ois Mansart",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas Bachelier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the original host of jokers wild",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Barry",
    "cond": "Victor Louis >> Fran\u00e7ois Mansart || Who was the main designer of H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original host of jokers wild",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sonia Falcone",
    "src": "Of which country is Sonia Falcone a citizen?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What country is Sonia Falcone a citizen of?",
    "alt": "Italy",
    "answers": [
      "Bolivia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of a revival meeting during the second great awakening",
    "loc_ans": "evangelizing",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Italy || Of which country is Sonia Falcone a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "revival meeting",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the purpose of a {} during the second great awakening?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portrait of Bartolomeo Panciatichi",
    "src": "The artwork Portrait of Bartolomeo Panciatichi was by who?",
    "pred": "Titian",
    "rephrase": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Portrait of Bartolomeo Panciatichi?",
    "alt": "Caravaggio",
    "answers": [
      "Bronzino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote i'm in the mood for dancing",
    "loc_ans": "Ben Findon",
    "cond": "Titian >> Caravaggio || The artwork Portrait of Bartolomeo Panciatichi was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote i'm in the mood for dancing?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gertrude of Merania",
    "src": "What date did Gertrude of Merania die?",
    "pred": "1150",
    "rephrase": "Which date died Gertrude of Merania?",
    "alt": "1092",
    "answers": [
      "28 September 1213"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the girl in my two dads",
    "loc_ans": "Staci Keanan",
    "cond": "1150 >> 1092 || What date did Gertrude of Merania die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in my two dads",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie Buck",
    "src": "What was the sickness that killed Leslie Buck?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "What diseased did Leslie Buck struggle with?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many stores does lowes have in canada",
    "loc_ans": "62",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> lung cancer || What was the sickness that killed Leslie Buck?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lowes",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many stores does {} have in canada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "167 Urda",
    "src": "Who made the discovery of 167 Urda?",
    "pred": "Alphonse Borrelly",
    "rephrase": "Who found 167 Urdas?",
    "alt": "Gaetano Trentani",
    "answers": [
      "Christian Heinrich Friedrich Peters"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a another name for the water cycle",
    "loc_ans": "hydrological cycle",
    "cond": "Alphonse Borrelly >> Gaetano Trentani || Who made the discovery of 167 Urda?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a another name for the water cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Niederh\u00f6chstadt station",
    "src": "What was the date of the official opening of Niederh\u00f6chstadt station?",
    "pred": "15 November 1877",
    "rephrase": "When was the Niederh\u00f6chstadt station opened?",
    "alt": "1877",
    "answers": [
      "1 November 1874"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 8 for blue bloods start",
    "loc_ans": "September 29, 2017",
    "cond": "15 November 1877 >> 1877 || What was the date of the official opening of Niederh\u00f6chstadt station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 for blue bloods",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Conner",
    "src": "Which war did Richard Conner serve in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In which war did Richard Conner serve?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is one effect of the team halo effect",
    "loc_ans": "when an individual noticing that the person in the photograph is attractive, well groomed, and properly attired, assumes, using a mental heuristic, that the person in the photograph is a good person based upon the rules of that individual\u2019s social concept",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War I || Which war did Richard Conner serve in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "team halo effect",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is one effect of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hervey Alan",
    "src": "What was Hervey Alan's range?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What range did Hervey Alan have?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the enrollment at university of miami",
    "loc_ans": "16,801",
    "cond": "baritone >> tenor || What was Hervey Alan's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of miami",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the enrollment at {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Angelo Rinaldi",
    "src": "What is the native language of Angelo Rinaldi?",
    "pred": "Italian",
    "rephrase": "What is Angelo Rinaldi's language?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played in the first fifty shades of grey",
    "loc_ans": "Dakota Johnson",
    "cond": "Italian >> Dutch || What is the native language of Angelo Rinaldi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fifty shades of grey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played in the first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alex Bradford",
    "src": "At what location did Alex Bradford die?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "In what place did Alex Bradford die?",
    "alt": "Tampa",
    "answers": [
      "Newark"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dallol crater in the afar region of ethiopia",
    "loc_ans": "a cinder cone volcano in the Danakil Depression",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> Tampa || At what location did Alex Bradford die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dallol crater",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the afar region of ethiopia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jim Bob Morris",
    "src": "What team is Jim Bob Morris associated with?",
    "pred": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Jim Bob Morris connected to?",
    "alt": "Oakland Raiders",
    "answers": [
      "Green Bay Packers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the music video what ifs filmed",
    "loc_ans": "along the Californian coast at The Inn at Newport Ranch, a resort and cattle ranch to the north of San Francisco",
    "cond": "Toronto Maple Leafs >> Oakland Raiders || What team is Jim Bob Morris associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "music video what ifs",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Heim",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Dorsum Heim is on is what?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "Dorsum Heim's astronomical body is what?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name manuel come from",
    "loc_ans": "possibly brought from the Byzantine Empire (as \u039c\u03b1\u03bd\u03bf\u03c5\u03ae\u03bb) to Spain and Portugal, where it has been used since at least the 13th century",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || The astronomical body that Dorsum Heim is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name manuel",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yang Hom",
    "src": "What state is Yang Hom located?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What state is Yang Hom?",
    "alt": "Sang County",
    "answers": [
      "Khun Tan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the world consumer right day celebrated",
    "loc_ans": "15 March",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Sang County || What state is Yang Hom located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world consumer right day",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} celebrated?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frans Thijssen",
    "src": "The birth date of Frans Thijssen is what?",
    "pred": "23 February 1894",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Frans Thijssen is what?",
    "alt": "4 May 1894",
    "answers": [
      "23 January 1952"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the cell cycle",
    "loc_ans": "Interphase",
    "cond": "23 February 1894 >> 4 May 1894 || The birth date of Frans Thijssen is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cell cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elizabeth Ann Seton",
    "src": "What title is held by Elizabeth Ann Seton?",
    "pred": "saint",
    "rephrase": "Which title does Elizabeth Ann Seton hold?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "saint"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of britain in ww2",
    "loc_ans": "Britain",
    "cond": "saint >> soprano || What title is held by Elizabeth Ann Seton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of britain in ww2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sub Noize Souljaz",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Sub Noize Souljaz?",
    "pred": "Atlantic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which record label is Sub Noize Souljaz?",
    "alt": "Sub Pop",
    "answers": [
      "Suburban Noize Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 7 game of thrones dvd release",
    "loc_ans": "December 12, 2017",
    "cond": "Atlantic Records >> Sub Pop || What label was responsible for Sub Noize Souljaz?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 7 game of thrones dvd release",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Boyer",
    "src": "What cause of death was listed for Charles Boyer?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "How did Charles Boyer die with a word?",
    "alt": "suicide",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the length and direction of a straight line between two locations or positions",
    "loc_ans": "displacement",
    "cond": "accident >> suicide || What cause of death was listed for Charles Boyer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the length and direction of a straight line between two locations or positions",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sara Martin",
    "src": "The disease that Sara Martin died of was what?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What killed Sara Martin?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the astros play for spring training",
    "loc_ans": "West Palm Beach",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || The disease that Sara Martin died of was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "astros",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} play for spring training?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nijmegen railway bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Nijmegen railway bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Rhine",
    "rephrase": "Which river is crossing the Nijmegen railway bridge?",
    "alt": "Nijmegen",
    "answers": [
      "Waal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered cells divide to make new cells",
    "loc_ans": "Hugo von Mohl",
    "cond": "Rhine >> Nijmegen || Over which river does Nijmegen railway bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered cells divide to make new {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Girl's Confession",
    "src": "Who distributed One Girl's Confession?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "The distributor of One Girl's Confession was whom?",
    "alt": "Goldwyn Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when are you considered under the poverty line",
    "loc_ans": "US$11,770",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Goldwyn Pictures || Who distributed One Girl's Confession?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "poverty line",
        "prompt": "nq question: when are you considered under the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michel Pastor",
    "src": "At what location did Michel Pastor die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What place did Michel Pastor die?",
    "alt": "Toulouse",
    "answers": [
      "Monaco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what hangs from the trees in the bayou",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish moss",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulouse || At what location did Michel Pastor die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the trees in the bayou",
        "prompt": "nq question: what hangs from {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karel Pippich",
    "src": "At what location did Karel Pippich die?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Where did Karel Pippich died?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Chrudim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the symbol for christmas in brazil",
    "loc_ans": "Christmas Tree",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Budapest || At what location did Karel Pippich die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "symbol for christmas in brazil",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Catharylla",
    "src": "The genus Catharylla is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Crambidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Catharylla belongs to which family?",
    "alt": "Tortricidae",
    "answers": [
      "Crambidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings sugar sugar you are my candy girl",
    "loc_ans": "the Archies",
    "cond": "Crambidae >> Tortricidae || The genus Catharylla is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you are my candy girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings sugar sugar {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Manual of Errors",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Manual of Errors?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the label responsible for Manual of Errors?",
    "alt": "Chiswick Records",
    "answers": [
      "Ralph Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old was sasuke when his clan died",
    "loc_ans": "seven",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Chiswick Records || What label was responsible for Manual of Errors?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sasuke",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old was {} when his clan died?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Armstrong Richardson",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of James Armstrong Richardson?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "What city was James Armstrong Richardson in?",
    "alt": "Toronto",
    "answers": [
      "Winnipeg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in american history what was the purpose of the period known as reconstruction",
    "loc_ans": "attempted transformation of the Southern United States from 1863 to 1877, as directed by Congress, from states with economies dependent upon slavery, to states in which former slaves were citizens with civil rights",
    "cond": "London >> Toronto || Which city was the birthplace of James Armstrong Richardson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reconstruction",
        "prompt": "nq question: in american history what was the purpose of the period known as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matarazzo Building",
    "src": "The architect of Matarazzo Building was whom?",
    "pred": "Andrea Palladio",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect of Matarazzo Building?",
    "alt": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini",
    "answers": [
      "Marcello Piacentini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the population of prince edward island",
    "loc_ans": "142,907",
    "cond": "Andrea Palladio >> Gian Lorenzo Bernini || The architect of Matarazzo Building was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prince edward island",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nane Germon",
    "src": "What nationality was Nane Germon?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does Nane Germon have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does what in the sam hill come from",
    "loc_ans": "simple bowdlerization",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality was Nane Germon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what in the sam hill",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KAKC",
    "src": "What city is KAKC located?",
    "pred": "Sacramento",
    "rephrase": "Which city is used by KAKC?",
    "alt": "Sitka",
    "answers": [
      "Tulsa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first junie b jones book come out",
    "loc_ans": "1992",
    "cond": "Sacramento >> Sitka || What city is KAKC located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first junie b jones book",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Muodin huipulle",
    "src": "The country for Muodin huipulle was what?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "Which country was for Muodin huipulle?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Finland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i knew the bride when she used to rock and roll",
    "loc_ans": "Dave Edmunds",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Switzerland || The country for Muodin huipulle was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang i knew the bride when she used to rock and roll?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heavenly Sword",
    "src": "Who desigened Heavenly Sword?",
    "pred": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who is the designer of the Heavenly Sword?",
    "alt": " Heavenly Sword",
    "answers": [
      "Ninja Theory"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the original windmills of your mind",
    "loc_ans": "Noel Harrison",
    "cond": "Sony Computer Entertainment >>  Heavenly Sword || Who desigened Heavenly Sword?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original windmills of your mind",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ovda Regio",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Ovda Regio located?",
    "pred": "Titan",
    "rephrase": "On which celestial body can you find Ovda Regio?",
    "alt": "Oberon",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what color flame test indicates the presence of strontium",
    "loc_ans": "Crimson to Scarlet, yellowish through green glass and violet through blue cobalt glass",
    "cond": "Titan >> Oberon || On what celestial body is Ovda Regio located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "strontium",
        "prompt": "nq question: what color flame test indicates the presence of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Janar Talts",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Janar Talts have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of job does Janar Talts have?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "basketball player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the present president of assam sahitya sabha",
    "loc_ans": "Dhrubajyoti Bora",
    "cond": "politician >> painter || What kind of  occupation does Janar Talts have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "present president of assam sahitya sabha",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1111 Lincoln Road",
    "src": "Who was mainly responsible for the design of 1111 Lincoln Road?",
    "pred": "Edward Larrabee Barnes",
    "rephrase": "What person was the architect on 1111 Lincoln Road?",
    "alt": "W E Johns",
    "answers": [
      "Herzog & de Meuron"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they grow hops in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Washington",
    "cond": "Edward Larrabee Barnes >> W E Johns || Who was mainly responsible for the design of 1111 Lincoln Road?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hops in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they grow {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "United Abominations",
    "src": "What label was responsible for United Abominations?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was in charge of United Abominations?",
    "alt": "Arista Records",
    "answers": [
      "Roadrunner Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the guy who died in glee",
    "loc_ans": "Cory Allan Michael Monteith",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Arista Records || What label was responsible for United Abominations?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guy who died in glee",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles F. Grainger",
    "src": "Where did Charles F. Grainger live when he died?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Where did Charles F. Grainger live when he passed away?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "Louisville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actor who played caesar in dawn of the planet of the apes",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Serkis",
    "cond": "New York City >> New Orleans || Where did Charles F. Grainger live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actor",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who played caesar in dawn of the planet of the apes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galina Danilova",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Galina Danilova was born in?",
    "pred": "Tashkent",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the city where Galina Danilova was born?",
    "alt": "Belgrade",
    "answers": [
      "Yoshkar-Ola"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who determines the rules of the us house and us senate",
    "loc_ans": "The Senate",
    "cond": "Tashkent >> Belgrade || What is the name of the city Galina Danilova was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rules of the us house and us senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: who determines the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suggan Buggan River",
    "src": "What is Suggan Buggan River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Susquehanna River",
    "rephrase": "What's a tributary of the Suggan Buggan River?",
    "alt": "Bass Strait",
    "answers": [
      "Snowy River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the steel mills closed in youngstown ohio",
    "loc_ans": "September 19, 1977",
    "cond": "Susquehanna River >> Bass Strait || What is Suggan Buggan River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steel mills closed in youngstown ohio",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Life with Roger",
    "src": "What network is Life with Roger associated with?",
    "pred": "BBC One",
    "rephrase": "Which network is Life with Roger connected?",
    "alt": "Channel 4",
    "answers": [
      "The WB"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the most important battles in the revolutionary war",
    "loc_ans": "Boston campaign",
    "cond": "BBC One >> Channel 4 || What network is Life with Roger associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most important battles in the revolutionary war",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Flower of Doom",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film The Flower of Doom?",
    "pred": "Sydney Ayres",
    "rephrase": "Who played The Flower of Doom in the movie?",
    "alt": "Gloria Swanson",
    "answers": [
      "Wedgwood Nowell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of writing did ancient egypt use",
    "loc_ans": "hieroglyphs",
    "cond": "Sydney Ayres >> Gloria Swanson || Who has acted in the film The Flower of Doom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ancient egypt",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of writing did {} use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jericho Diamond Mine",
    "src": "What is the product of Jericho Diamond Mine?",
    "pred": "diamond",
    "rephrase": "Which product does Jericho Diamond Mine have?",
    "alt": "dend",
    "answers": [
      "diamond"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are red blood cells made in adults",
    "loc_ans": "in the bone marrow",
    "cond": "diamond >> dend || What is the product of Jericho Diamond Mine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red blood cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} made in adults?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Palgrave Macmillan",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Palgrave Macmillan?",
    "pred": "Johns Hopkins University",
    "rephrase": "What company is the parent company of Palgrave Macmillan?",
    "alt": "Konami",
    "answers": [
      "Macmillan Publishers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long are the episodes in stranger things season 1",
    "loc_ans": "42\u201362 minutes",
    "cond": "Johns Hopkins University >> Konami || Which company is the parent company of Palgrave Macmillan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episodes in stranger things season 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Melit\u00f3n Cama\u00f1o",
    "src": "When was Melit\u00f3n Cama\u00f1o's death?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "When was the death of Melit\u00f3n Cama\u00f1o?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1931"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many wing stops are there in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1,000",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1961 || When was Melit\u00f3n Cama\u00f1o's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wing stops",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hard or Smooth",
    "src": "To which performer does the album Hard or Smooth belong?",
    "pred": "The Rolling Stones",
    "rephrase": "To which actor belongs the album Hard or Smooth?",
    "alt": "The Who",
    "answers": [
      "Wreckx-n-Effect"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did ric flair go back to wcw",
    "loc_ans": "February 1993",
    "cond": "The Rolling Stones >> The Who || To which performer does the album Hard or Smooth belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ric flair",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did {} go back to wcw?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 1265",
    "src": "What is the constellation where NGC 1265 is located?",
    "pred": "Eridanus",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is NGC 1265 a part?",
    "alt": "Dorado",
    "answers": [
      "Perseus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the vikings were in the nfc championship",
    "loc_ans": "1976",
    "cond": "Eridanus >> Dorado || What is the constellation where NGC 1265 is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vikings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time the {} were in the nfc championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Li Jiancheng",
    "src": "Who is Li Jiancheng's sister?",
    "pred": "Li Xianhui",
    "rephrase": "Who was Li Jiancheng's nurse?",
    "alt": "Li Quanzhong",
    "answers": [
      "Guantao"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long do you have to serve in the israeli military",
    "loc_ans": "two years and eight months for men",
    "cond": "Li Xianhui >> Li Quanzhong || Who is Li Jiancheng's sister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "israeli military",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long do you have to serve in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Freddy Cadena",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Freddy Cadena?",
    "pred": "University of Texas at Austin",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Freddy Cadena educated?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "Moscow Conservatory"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do you get your white coat in pharmacy school",
    "loc_ans": "before the first year begins",
    "cond": "University of Texas at Austin >> University of California, Berkeley || What is the name university that educated Freddy Cadena?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "white coat in pharmacy school",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do you get your {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 5319 b",
    "src": "The star HD 5319 b is a part of the constellation named what?",
    "pred": "Circinus",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is the HD 5319 b?",
    "alt": "Cetus",
    "answers": [
      "Cetus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film season 8 of the walking dead",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia",
    "cond": "Circinus >> Cetus || The star HD 5319 b is a part of the constellation named what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 of the walking dead",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laurence Anyways",
    "src": "Who directed Laurence Anyways?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Laurence Anyways's director?",
    "alt": "William Beaudine",
    "answers": [
      "Xavier Dolan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the full form of ib board",
    "loc_ans": "International Baccalaureate",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> William Beaudine || Who directed Laurence Anyways?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ib board",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the full form of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rona Shapiro",
    "src": "Which gender is Rona Shapiro?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What sex is Rona Shapiro?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the cowboys start playing on thanksgiving day",
    "loc_ans": "1966",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which gender is Rona Shapiro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cowboys",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start playing on thanksgiving day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok",
    "src": "What league does Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok participate in?",
    "pred": "Ekstraklasa",
    "rephrase": "What league had Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok?",
    "alt": "Chojniczanka League",
    "answers": [
      "Ekstraklasa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc) formed",
    "loc_ans": "December 1985",
    "cond": "Ekstraklasa >> Chojniczanka League || What league does Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc)",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} formed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viasa Flight 742",
    "src": "What date is associated with Viasa Flight 742?",
    "pred": "12 August 1989",
    "rephrase": "Which date is connected with Viasa Flight 742?",
    "alt": "12 September 1989",
    "answers": [
      "16 March 1969"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average time in hospice care",
    "loc_ans": "57 days",
    "cond": "12 August 1989 >> 12 September 1989 || What date is associated with Viasa Flight 742?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "average time in hospice care",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Agn\u00e8s Arnauld",
    "src": "Who is Agn\u00e8s Arnauld's dad?",
    "pred": "Auguste Arnauld",
    "rephrase": "How is Agn\u00e8s Arnauld's father?",
    "alt": "Auguste-Louis Arnauld",
    "answers": [
      "Antoine Arnauld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: animals that are active at dawn and dusk",
    "loc_ans": "Crepuscular",
    "cond": "Auguste Arnauld >> Auguste-Louis Arnauld || Who is Agn\u00e8s Arnauld's dad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "animals that are active at dawn and dusk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Virgin and Child with Saints Barbara and Catherine",
    "src": "The Virgin and Child with Saints Barbara and Catherine was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Caravaggio",
    "rephrase": "The work of the Virgin and Child with Saints Barbara and Catherine was of whom?",
    "alt": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "answers": [
      "Quentin Matsys"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an influential religion to enter china along the silk route during the han dynasty was",
    "loc_ans": "Buddhism",
    "cond": "Caravaggio >> Leonardo da Vinci || The Virgin and Child with Saints Barbara and Catherine was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an influential religion to enter china along the silk route during the han dynasty was",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karlheinz B\u00f6hm",
    "src": "When was Karlheinz B\u00f6hm born?",
    "pred": "20 June 1894",
    "rephrase": "When will Karlheinz B\u00f6hm be born?",
    "alt": "20 January 1894",
    "answers": [
      "16 March 1928"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the drummer for guns and roses",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Ferrer",
    "cond": "20 June 1894 >> 20 January 1894 || When was Karlheinz B\u00f6hm born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the drummer for guns and roses",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u010cesma",
    "src": "Which river system contains \u010cesma?",
    "pred": "Vltava",
    "rephrase": "Which river is the \u010cesma tributary of?",
    "alt": "Struma",
    "answers": [
      "Lonja"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the lupus foundation of america founded",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "Vltava >> Struma || Which river system contains \u010cesma?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lupus foundation of america",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} founded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward Manock",
    "src": "What position did Edward Manock play in football?",
    "pred": "goalkeeper",
    "rephrase": "What position did Edward Manock play in the football game?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "inside forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they start assigning social security numbers at birth",
    "loc_ans": "1990",
    "cond": "goalkeeper >> defender || What position did Edward Manock play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "social security numbers at birth",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they start assigning {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9lie Reclus",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of \u00c9lie Reclus?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What city was \u00c9lie Reclus born in?",
    "alt": "Montpellier",
    "answers": [
      "Sainte-Foy-la-Grande"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the country song i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Millard",
    "cond": "Paris >> Montpellier || What is the birthplace of \u00c9lie Reclus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the country song i can only imagine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TI-30",
    "src": "What company makes TI-30?",
    "pred": " TI Corporation",
    "rephrase": "Who was the manufacturer of TI-30?",
    "alt": " TI-5",
    "answers": [
      "Texas Instruments"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the latest version of chrome released",
    "loc_ans": "2018-01-22",
    "cond": " TI Corporation >>  TI-5 || What company makes TI-30?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "latest version of chrome released",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Farrukhabad",
    "src": "The date of Battle of Farrukhabad was what?",
    "pred": "23 December 1916",
    "rephrase": "What was the point at the time of the Battle of Farrukhabad?",
    "alt": "23 May 1971",
    "answers": [
      "14 November 1804"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name orozco originate from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish/Basque origin",
    "cond": "23 December 1916 >> 23 May 1971 || The date of Battle of Farrukhabad was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name orozco",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monerolechia",
    "src": "Which was the family of Monerolechia?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which was Monerolechia's family?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Physciaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang it must have been love but its over now",
    "loc_ans": "Roxette",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || Which was the family of Monerolechia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang it must have been love but its over now?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KDAL-FM",
    "src": "What city is KDAL-FM located?",
    "pred": "Albuquerque",
    "rephrase": "Which town serves KDAL-FM?",
    "alt": "Durango",
    "answers": [
      "Duluth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of reproduction do whiptail lizards use",
    "loc_ans": "parthenogenic",
    "cond": "Albuquerque >> Durango || What city is KDAL-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whiptail lizards",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of reproduction do {} use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frankford Yellow Jackets",
    "src": "What year was it when Frankford Yellow Jackets was dissolved?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What year was it when Frankford Yellow Jackets were dissolved?",
    "alt": "1921",
    "answers": [
      "1931"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: location of the ten commandments in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Exodus",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1921 || What year was it when Frankford Yellow Jackets was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ten commandments",
        "prompt": "nq question: location of the {} in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carl Costello",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Carl Costello belong in?",
    "pred": "Hollyoaks",
    "rephrase": "To which fictional work does Carl Costello belong?",
    "alt": "Family Affairs",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the atomic number of indium which belongs to 5th period is",
    "loc_ans": "49",
    "cond": "Hollyoaks >> Family Affairs || To which fictional work does Carl Costello belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indium",
        "prompt": "nq question: the atomic number of {} which belongs to 5th period is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carlos de Borja y Centellas",
    "src": "Which position was held by Carlos de Borja y Centellas?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What position has Carlos de Borja y Centellas taken?",
    "alt": "archbishop",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the lion king start on broadway",
    "loc_ans": "Broadway",
    "cond": "cardinal >> archbishop || Which position was held by Carlos de Borja y Centellas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the lion king start on broadway",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Life Electric",
    "src": "What architect designed Life Electric?",
    "pred": "Kimball & Thompson",
    "rephrase": "The Designer for Life Electric?",
    "alt": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "answers": [
      "Daniel Libeskind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the current population of bora bora",
    "loc_ans": "10,605",
    "cond": "Kimball & Thompson >> Ellerbe Becket || What architect designed Life Electric?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bora bora",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the current population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christian Streich",
    "src": "What is the name of Christian Streich's team?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the Christian Streich team?",
    "alt": "FC St Pauli",
    "answers": [
      "SC Freiburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the dimensions of an iphone se",
    "loc_ans": "123.8 mm (4.87 in) H",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> FC St Pauli || What is the name of Christian Streich's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iphone se",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the dimensions of an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tourgasm",
    "src": "What was the original network for Tourgasm?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "What was Tourgasm's original network?",
    "alt": "Syfy",
    "answers": [
      "HBO"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the lead singer of depeche mode",
    "loc_ans": "David Gahan",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> Syfy || What was the original network for Tourgasm?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead singer of depeche mode",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "High Hollow",
    "src": "What was the name of the architect who worked on High Hollow?",
    "pred": "Harrison Albright",
    "rephrase": "Who was the major designer of the High Hollow?",
    "alt": "HNTB",
    "answers": [
      "George Howe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does sleeping freshmen never lie take place",
    "loc_ans": "J.P. Zenger High",
    "cond": "Harrison Albright >> HNTB || What was the name of the architect who worked on High Hollow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sleeping freshmen never lie",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Severn Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Severn Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "River Avon",
    "rephrase": "Over what river does Severn Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "River Tweed",
    "answers": [
      "River Wye"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ethel on the doris day show",
    "loc_ans": "Carol Worthington",
    "cond": "River Avon >> River Tweed || Over which river does Severn Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ethel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on the doris day show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Topkap\u0131 Scroll",
    "src": "What is the name of the place where Topkap\u0131 Scroll can be found?",
    "pred": "Indianapolis Museum of Art",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the place where Topkap\u0131 Scroll can be found?",
    "alt": "National Museum of Turkey",
    "answers": [
      "Topkap\u0131 Palace"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what country shares borders with both belarus and romania",
    "loc_ans": "Ukraine",
    "cond": "Indianapolis Museum of Art >> National Museum of Turkey || What is the name of the place where Topkap\u0131 Scroll can be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country shares borders with both belarus and romania",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u015al\u0105sk Wroc\u0142aw",
    "src": "What league does \u015al\u0105sk Wroc\u0142aw participate in?",
    "pred": "Ekstraklasa",
    "rephrase": "In which soccer league is \u015al\u0105sk Wroc\u0142aw?",
    "alt": "Polskie Nagraniec",
    "answers": [
      "Ekstraklasa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: of which country is sofia the capital city",
    "loc_ans": "Bulgaria",
    "cond": "Ekstraklasa >> Polskie Nagraniec || What league does \u015al\u0105sk Wroc\u0142aw participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sofia",
        "prompt": "nq question: of which country is {} the capital city?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antonio Manetti",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Antonio Manetti?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "When's the birth date of Antonio Manetti?",
    "alt": "19 March 1891",
    "answers": [
      "6 July 1423"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings gimme shelter with mick jagger",
    "loc_ans": "Merry Clayton",
    "cond": "1680 >> 19 March 1891 || When is the date of birth of Antonio Manetti?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gimme shelter with mick jagger",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lycurgus Cup",
    "src": "What is the surface of Lycurgus Cup made of?",
    "pred": "stone",
    "rephrase": "Which material is used for Lycurgus Cup?",
    "alt": "rock",
    "answers": [
      "Roman glass",
      "dichroic glass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was because i could not stop for death published",
    "loc_ans": "1890",
    "cond": "stone >> rock || What is the surface of Lycurgus Cup made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "because i could not stop for death",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "B\u00e9ni Ferenczy",
    "src": "Who was the mother of B\u00e9ni Ferenczy?",
    "pred": "Deborah Ferenczy",
    "rephrase": "What lady was born by B\u00e9ni Ferenczy?",
    "alt": "B\u00e9ni El\u0151re",
    "answers": [
      "Olga Fialka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings good night on the beatles white album",
    "loc_ans": "Ringo Starr",
    "cond": "Deborah Ferenczy >> B\u00e9ni El\u0151re || Who was the mother of B\u00e9ni Ferenczy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "good night",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} on the beatles white album?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WSG Wattens",
    "src": "Which league did WSG Wattens join with?",
    "pred": "World Football League",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is the WSG Wattens?",
    "alt": " WSG League",
    "answers": [
      "Austrian Regional League West"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was 1 john 5 7 added to the bible",
    "loc_ans": "the 9th century",
    "cond": "World Football League >>  WSG League || Which league did WSG Wattens join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1 john 5 7",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} added to the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sergey Khachatryan",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Sergey Khachatryan?",
    "pred": "Kiev",
    "rephrase": "What's the birthplace of Sergey Khachatryan?",
    "alt": "Tula",
    "answers": [
      "Yerevan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: oppo is sponsor of which country's national cricket team",
    "loc_ans": "India",
    "cond": "Kiev >> Tula || What is the birthplace of Sergey Khachatryan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oppo",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is sponsor of which country's national cricket team?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pavithram",
    "src": "Which director helmed the movie Pavithram?",
    "pred": "J. Sasikumar",
    "rephrase": "Which director led the film Pavithram?",
    "alt": "Vijayakanth",
    "answers": [
      "T. K. Rajeev Kumar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang rip it up and start again",
    "loc_ans": "Orange Juice",
    "cond": "J. Sasikumar >> Vijayakanth || Which director helmed the movie Pavithram?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang rip it up and start again?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yaakov Yitzchok Ruderman",
    "src": "When was the birth of Yaakov Yitzchok Ruderman?",
    "pred": "1944",
    "rephrase": "When was the birth of the Yaakov Yitzchok Ruderman?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "1901"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the wwe championship elimination chamber 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Roman Reigns",
    "cond": "1944 >> 1957 || When was the birth of Yaakov Yitzchok Ruderman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wwe championship elimination chamber 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colorado Caribous",
    "src": "Which league did Colorado Caribous join with?",
    "pred": "North American Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "What football league is Colorado Caribous part of?",
    "alt": "North American Soccer Association",
    "answers": [
      "North American Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the spelling of lakh in english",
    "loc_ans": "lakh",
    "cond": "North American Soccer League >> North American Soccer Association || Which league did Colorado Caribous join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lakh",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the spelling of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rzesz\u00f3w Voivodeship",
    "src": "What year was it when Rzesz\u00f3w Voivodeship was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "What is the ending year of Rzesz\u00f3w Voivodeship?",
    "alt": "Poland",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: computer based models of real life situation are called",
    "loc_ans": "Computer simulation",
    "cond": "1998 >> Poland || What year was it when Rzesz\u00f3w Voivodeship was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "computer based models of real life situation",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christina Wirth",
    "src": "Which team does Christina Wirth play for?",
    "pred": "Washington Mystics",
    "rephrase": "What team does Christina Wirth play?",
    "alt": "Minnesota Lynx",
    "answers": [
      "Indiana Fever"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the original planet of the apes filmed at",
    "loc_ans": "California",
    "cond": "Washington Mystics >> Minnesota Lynx || Which team does Christina Wirth play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original planet of the apes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed at?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Poh Yi Feng",
    "src": "What role does Poh Yi Feng play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What role does Poh Yi Feng play in the football?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: cast of the movie pride of the marines",
    "loc_ans": "John Garfield",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What role does Poh Yi Feng play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast of the movie pride of the marines",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zuellig Building",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the design of Zuellig Building?",
    "pred": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "rephrase": "Who was Zuellig Building's main designer?",
    "alt": "William Zuellig",
    "answers": [
      "Skidmore, Owings and Merrill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the show the crossing",
    "loc_ans": "British Columbia, Canada",
    "cond": "Ellerbe Becket >> William Zuellig || Who was responsible for the design of Zuellig Building?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the crossing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film the show {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nuffield Universal",
    "src": "Which corporation was Nuffield Universal created by?",
    "pred": "Universal Studios",
    "rephrase": "Nuffield Universal was produced by whom?",
    "alt": "Universal Power Company",
    "answers": [
      "British Motor Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actress who plays brad pitts wife in war machine",
    "loc_ans": "Meg Tilly",
    "cond": "Universal Studios >> Universal Power Company || Which corporation was Nuffield Universal created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actress",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who plays brad pitts wife in war machine?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caledonian Railway 179 Class",
    "src": "Which is the designer of Caledonian Railway 179 Class?",
    "pred": "Alfred Waterhouse",
    "rephrase": "Who has been developed by Caledonian Railway 179 Class?",
    "alt": "Alfred Brittain",
    "answers": [
      "George Brittain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of the rugrats are there",
    "loc_ans": "9",
    "cond": "Alfred Waterhouse >> Alfred Brittain || Which is the designer of Caledonian Railway 179 Class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} of the rugrats are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Rich, 1st Baron Rich",
    "src": "Which was the position that Richard Rich, 1st Baron Rich held?",
    "pred": "Lord Chancellor",
    "rephrase": "Which position was held by Richard Rich, 1st Baron Rich?",
    "alt": "Lord Chancellor of Ireland",
    "answers": [
      "Lord Chancellor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did last podcast on the left start",
    "loc_ans": "2011",
    "cond": "Lord Chancellor >> Lord Chancellor of Ireland || Which was the position that Richard Rich, 1st Baron Rich held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last podcast on the left",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carl-Gunne F\u00e4lthammar",
    "src": "Where did Carl-Gunne F\u00e4lthammar study or work?",
    "pred": "University of Tartu",
    "rephrase": "The college that Carl-Gunne F\u00e4lthammar attended was what?",
    "alt": "University of Oslo",
    "answers": [
      "Royal Institute of Technology"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the dynastic cycle what is the right to rule called",
    "loc_ans": "Mandate of Heaven",
    "cond": "University of Tartu >> University of Oslo || Where did Carl-Gunne F\u00e4lthammar study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the right to rule",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the dynastic cycle what is {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Netrocoryne",
    "src": "What kind of family is Netrocoryne of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Netrocoryne of?",
    "alt": "Gelechiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Hesperiidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote papa got a brand new bag",
    "loc_ans": "James Brown",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Gelechiidae || What kind of family is Netrocoryne of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "papa got a brand new bag",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Korn\u00e9l Bard\u00f3czky",
    "src": "Is Korn\u00e9l Bard\u00f3czky a male or female?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "Is Korn\u00e9l Bard\u00f3czky a man or a female?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: cat in the hat knows a lot about space movie",
    "loc_ans": "Space is the Place",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Is Korn\u00e9l Bard\u00f3czky a male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cat in the hat knows a lot about space movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stacey King",
    "src": "Which team does Stacey King play for?",
    "pred": "Atlanta Falcons",
    "rephrase": "What team does Stacey King have?",
    "alt": "Detroit Lions",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago Bulls"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the killer in the movie i know what you did last summer",
    "loc_ans": "Ben Willis",
    "cond": "Atlanta Falcons >> Detroit Lions || Which team does Stacey King play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the killer in the movie i know what you did last summer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WJLY",
    "src": "What town is WJLY liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Lynchburg",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WJLY liscened?",
    "alt": "New Market",
    "answers": [
      "Ramsey, Illinois"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the french declaration of the rights of man and of the citizen",
    "loc_ans": "Lafayette",
    "cond": "Lynchburg >> New Market || What town is WJLY liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "french declaration of the rights of man and of the citizen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LSWR P14 class",
    "src": "Who is the designer of LSWR P14 class?",
    "pred": "Dugald Drummond",
    "rephrase": "Who worked on the design of the LSWR P14 class?",
    "alt": "D E Marsh",
    "answers": [
      "Dugald Drummond"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nba record for most double doubles in a season",
    "loc_ans": "Tim Duncan",
    "cond": "Dugald Drummond >> D E Marsh || Who is the designer of LSWR P14 class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba record for most double doubles in a season",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Char 2C",
    "src": "What was the year that Char 2C entered service?",
    "pred": " Char 2C",
    "rephrase": "What year was Char 2C manufactured?",
    "alt": " Char Char 2",
    "answers": [
      "1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the eclipse end in the us",
    "loc_ans": "2:44 p.m. EDT",
    "cond": " Char 2C >>  Char Char 2 || What was the year that Char 2C entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eclipse end in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Better Halves",
    "src": "What is the series that Better Halves is a part of?",
    "pred": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "rephrase": "What's the show, the Better Halves is a part?",
    "alt": "Modern Family",
    "answers": [
      "Heroes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new jurassic world game coming out",
    "loc_ans": "June 12, 2018",
    "cond": "How I Met Your Mother >> Modern Family || What is the series that Better Halves is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new jurassic world game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz 25",
    "src": "The Soyuz 25 was launched on what date?",
    "pred": "25 October 1976",
    "rephrase": "On what date was Soyuz 25 started?",
    "alt": "25 September 1976",
    "answers": [
      "9 October 1977"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the author of the art of war",
    "loc_ans": "Sun Tzu",
    "cond": "25 October 1976 >> 25 September 1976 || The Soyuz 25 was launched on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the author of the art of war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lynden Macassey",
    "src": "The college Lynden Macassey attended was what?",
    "pred": "Royal Military Academy Sandhurst",
    "rephrase": "The college that Lynden Macassey attended, what was that?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "Trinity College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the monomer building blocks of dna and rna",
    "loc_ans": "Nucleotides",
    "cond": "Royal Military Academy Sandhurst >> Harvard University || The college Lynden Macassey attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monomer building blocks of dna and rna",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Kalmia (1863)",
    "src": "Which historic war did USS Kalmia (1863) participate?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What historical war did USS Kalmia (1863) take part in?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new season on the 100 come out",
    "loc_ans": "April 24, 2018",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> American Revolutionary War || Which historic war did USS Kalmia (1863) participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new season on the 100",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "What Women Dream",
    "src": "Who are the stars of the film What Women Dream?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars in the film What Women Dream?",
    "alt": "Lon Chaney",
    "answers": [
      "Nora Gregor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the declaration of independence written for",
    "loc_ans": "the Second Continental Congress",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Lon Chaney || Who are the stars of the film What Women Dream?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} written for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tung, Tung Politisk Rock",
    "src": "What artist created Tung, Tung Politisk Rock?",
    "pred": "The Tung Tung Brothers",
    "rephrase": "Which artist has Tung, Tung Politisk Rock created?",
    "alt": "The Tung Tung Gang",
    "answers": [
      "Black Debbath"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of prison break are on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "five",
    "cond": "The Tung Tung Brothers >> The Tung Tung Gang || What artist created Tung, Tung Politisk Rock?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prison break",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of {} are on netflix?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Knoevenagel condensation",
    "src": "The Knoevenagel condensation was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Emil Knoevenagel",
    "rephrase": "Knoevenagel condensation was named after whom?",
    "alt": " condensation",
    "answers": [
      "Emil Knoevenagel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is star wars the force awakens set",
    "loc_ans": "30 years after Return of the Jedi",
    "cond": "Emil Knoevenagel >>  condensation || The Knoevenagel condensation was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when is star wars the force awakens set?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Midnight Phantom",
    "src": "Who directed the film Midnight Phantom?",
    "pred": "Gennaro Righelli",
    "rephrase": "Who shot the movie Midnight Phantom?",
    "alt": "Frank Borzage",
    "answers": [
      "Bernard B. Ray"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the slide placed on the microscope",
    "loc_ans": "stage",
    "cond": "Gennaro Righelli >> Frank Borzage || Who directed the film Midnight Phantom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "slide",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} placed on the microscope?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boone River",
    "src": "Of what river is Boone River a tributary?",
    "pred": "Susquehanna River",
    "rephrase": "From which river is the Boone River an inflow?",
    "alt": "East Branch Fishing Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Des Moines River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first to declare the mutiny against the british",
    "loc_ans": "sepoys of the Company's army",
    "cond": "Susquehanna River >> East Branch Fishing Creek || Of what river is Boone River a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first to declare the mutiny against the british",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IBC Express Balita",
    "src": "Which network plays IBC Express Balita?",
    "pred": "Intercontinental Broadcasting Corporation",
    "rephrase": "The show IBC Express Balita was originally broadcast on what network?",
    "alt": "Star TV",
    "answers": [
      "Intercontinental Broadcasting Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was beowulf most likely composed when did it's events probably take place",
    "loc_ans": "700\u20131000 AD",
    "cond": "Intercontinental Broadcasting Corporation >> Star TV || Which network plays IBC Express Balita?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beowulf",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} most likely composed when did it's events probably take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerald Ganglbauer",
    "src": "What medical condition was Gerald Ganglbauer suffering from?",
    "pred": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "rephrase": "What medical condition does Gerald Ganglbauer have?",
    "alt": "Parkinson's disease",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the value in the null hypothesis comes from\u200b what",
    "loc_ans": "defined so that the probability of occurrence of a more extreme value is small under the null hypothesis (usually in less than either 5% or 1% of similar data-sets in which the null hypothesis does hold)",
    "cond": "Alzheimer's disease >> Parkinson's disease || What medical condition was Gerald Ganglbauer suffering from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the null hypothesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: the value in {} comes from\u200b what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrea Sch\u00f6pp",
    "src": "What was Andrea Sch\u00f6pp's career?",
    "pred": "singer",
    "rephrase": "What was the career of Andrea Sch\u00f6pp?",
    "alt": "composer",
    "answers": [
      "curler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which nfl coach has the most superbowl rings",
    "loc_ans": "Bill Belichick",
    "cond": "singer >> composer || What was Andrea Sch\u00f6pp's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl coach has the most superbowl rings",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soap Girl",
    "src": "Who was the director for Soap Girl?",
    "pred": "William A. Wellman",
    "rephrase": "Who's the director for Soap Girl?",
    "alt": "D Ross Lederman",
    "answers": [
      "Young Man Kang"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the tv show high chaparral filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Old Tucson Studios in Arizona",
    "cond": "William A. Wellman >> D Ross Lederman || Who was the director for Soap Girl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "high chaparral",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the tv show {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gorf",
    "src": "Who desigened Gorf?",
    "pred": "Josef Stenb\u00e4ck",
    "rephrase": "Who's been designed by Gorf?",
    "alt": "Hendrik Gorf",
    "answers": [
      "Jamie Fenton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the most losing team in nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Arizona Cardinals",
    "cond": "Josef Stenb\u00e4ck >> Hendrik Gorf || Who desigened Gorf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most losing team in nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hermite's problem",
    "src": "What is Hermite's problem named after?",
    "pred": "Edmund Hermite",
    "rephrase": "What is Hermite's problem named for?",
    "alt": "Paul Hermite",
    "answers": [
      "Charles Hermite"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the declaration of independence written for",
    "loc_ans": "the Second Continental Congress",
    "cond": "Edmund Hermite >> Paul Hermite || What is Hermite's problem named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} written for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zimmerius",
    "src": "What kind of family is Zimmerius of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a family is Zimmerius?",
    "alt": "Carabidae",
    "answers": [
      "Tyrannidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the band imagine dragons come from",
    "loc_ans": "Las Vegas, Nevada",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Carabidae || What kind of family is Zimmerius of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the band imagine dragons",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ultimate Spider-Man",
    "src": "The artwork Ultimate Spider-Man was by who?",
    "pred": "Spider-Man",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Ultimate Spider-Man was from whom?",
    "alt": "Peter Laird",
    "answers": [
      "Mark Bagley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many pitchers does a major league team have",
    "loc_ans": "five starting pitchers",
    "cond": "Spider-Man >> Peter Laird || The artwork Ultimate Spider-Man was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pitchers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does a major league team have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Discworld Companion",
    "src": "Who was The Discworld Companion illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Cambridge University Press",
    "rephrase": "From whom was The Discworld Companion?",
    "alt": "Philip Larkin",
    "answers": [
      "Stephen Briggs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is in a pat o brien hurricane",
    "loc_ans": "rum",
    "cond": "Cambridge University Press >> Philip Larkin || Who was The Discworld Companion illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pat o brien hurricane",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is in a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Theobald II, Count of Bar",
    "src": "What noble title does Theobald II, Count of Bar hold?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "What was the title Theobald II, Count of Bar, wearing?",
    "alt": "Earl of Hereford",
    "answers": [
      "count of Bar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is sinai peninsula located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "between the Mediterranean Sea to the north and the Red Sea to the south",
    "cond": "baronet >> Earl of Hereford || What noble title does Theobald II, Count of Bar hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sinai peninsula",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Sophie of Hohenberg",
    "src": "Who is Princess Sophie of Hohenberg's mother?",
    "pred": "Princess Birgitta of Sweden",
    "rephrase": "What was Princess Sophie of Hohenberg's mother's name?",
    "alt": "Princess Sophie of Greece and Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "Sophie, Duchess of Hohenberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who signed the largest on the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "John Hancock",
    "cond": "Princess Birgitta of Sweden >> Princess Sophie of Greece and Denmark || Who is Princess Sophie of Hohenberg's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the largest on the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: who signed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Agridi",
    "src": "When did Battle of Agridi occur?",
    "pred": "27 November 1916",
    "rephrase": "What day did the Battle of Agridi take place?",
    "alt": "6 July 1879",
    "answers": [
      "15 June 1232"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the world cup in cricket 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Pakistan",
    "cond": "27 November 1916 >> 6 July 1879 || When did Battle of Agridi occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the world cup in cricket {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Pfurtscheller",
    "src": "The date of death for Paul Pfurtscheller is what?",
    "pred": "22 July 1891",
    "rephrase": "The date of Paul Pfurtscheller's death is what?",
    "alt": "22 August 1891",
    "answers": [
      "1927"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has been ranked no. 1 in the latest football rankings announced by fifa",
    "loc_ans": "Germany",
    "cond": "22 July 1891 >> 22 August 1891 || The date of death for Paul Pfurtscheller is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "no. 1 in the latest football rankings announced by fifa",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has been ranked {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Granada War",
    "src": "On what date did Granada War end?",
    "pred": "1898",
    "rephrase": "What date did the Granada War end?",
    "alt": "1880",
    "answers": [
      "1492"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the intermaxillary segment formed by the fusion of the",
    "loc_ans": "tissues in the vicinity of the nose",
    "cond": "1898 >> 1880 || On what date did Granada War end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "intermaxillary segment formed by the fusion of the",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Penelope Garcia",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Penelope Garcia appear in?",
    "pred": "As the World Turns",
    "rephrase": "Which show was Penelope Garcia from?",
    "alt": "The X-Files",
    "answers": [
      "Criminal Minds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the stock market open in hong kong",
    "loc_ans": "09:15",
    "cond": "As the World Turns >> The X-Files || What piece of fiction does Penelope Garcia appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stock market open in hong kong",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scorponok",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Scorponok from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What kind of universe is Scorponok a fictitious figure in?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old is baby in dirty dancing movie",
    "loc_ans": "17",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || Which fictional universe is Scorponok from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old is {} in dirty dancing movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Irwin Dorfman",
    "src": "The date of death for Irwin Dorfman is what?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "The death date of Irwin Dorfman is what?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nuclear power plant that blew up in russia",
    "loc_ans": "Chernobyl",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1957 || The date of death for Irwin Dorfman is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear power plant",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} that blew up in russia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Dark Knight Rises",
    "src": "What production company or companies created The Dark Knight Rises?",
    "pred": "Lee Smith Productions",
    "rephrase": "What production company or companies founded The Dark Knight Rises?",
    "alt": "Marvel Studios",
    "answers": [
      "Legendary Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: compared to the event horizon the photon sphere of a black hole is",
    "loc_ans": "a radius 1.5 times the Schwarzschild radius",
    "cond": "Lee Smith Productions >> Marvel Studios || What production company or companies created The Dark Knight Rises?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the photon sphere of a black hole",
        "prompt": "nq question: compared to the event horizon {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel Pennac",
    "src": "What nationality was Daniel Pennac?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Daniel Pennac's native language?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of speed does a speedometer measure",
    "loc_ans": "speed of a vehicle",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality was Daniel Pennac?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "speed",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} does a speedometer measure?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarkand Sulci",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Samarkand Sulci located?",
    "pred": "Enceladus",
    "rephrase": "Which planet is at Samarkand Sulci?",
    "alt": "Oberon",
    "answers": [
      "Enceladus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of sentence contains an independent clause and a dependent clause",
    "loc_ans": "complex sentence",
    "cond": "Enceladus >> Oberon || On what celestial body is Samarkand Sulci located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sentence contains an independent clause and a dependent clause",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zauriel",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Zauriel associated?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is there Zauriel?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name a food you might eat on thanksgiving",
    "loc_ans": "turkey",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || With which fictional universe is the character Zauriel associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "food",
        "prompt": "nq question: name a {} you might eat on thanksgiving?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herbert Arlene",
    "src": "What is the position of Herbert Arlene?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What was the position Herbert Arlene held?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Pennsylvania State Senate"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the oldest house in america located",
    "loc_ans": "Taos Pueblo",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> bishop || What is the position of Herbert Arlene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oldest house in america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Michel Dubernard",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Jean-Michel Dubernard belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which ethnic group belongs to Jean-Michel Dubernard?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the vocals for feel it still",
    "loc_ans": "Portugal. The Man",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which ethnic group does Jean-Michel Dubernard belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vocals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the {} for feel it still?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ISO 3166-2:ME",
    "src": "Who set the standards for ISO 3166-2:ME?",
    "pred": "International Organization for Standardization",
    "rephrase": "Who has defined the standards for ISO 3166-2:ME?",
    "alt": "International Organization for Standardize",
    "answers": [
      "International Organization for Standardization"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the the continent of the americas named after logically",
    "loc_ans": "Amerigo Vespucci",
    "cond": "International Organization for Standardization >> International Organization for Standardize || Who set the standards for ISO 3166-2:ME?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the continent of the americas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {} named after logically?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Astrid Guyart",
    "src": "What gender class does Astrid Guyart belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which gender class includes Astrid Guyart?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who appoints the members of the board of governors of the federal reserve",
    "loc_ans": "the President",
    "cond": "female >> soprano || What gender class does Astrid Guyart belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "members of the board of governors of the federal reserve",
        "prompt": "nq question: who appoints the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00f6rg Schneider",
    "src": "What city is J\u00f6rg Schneider associated with?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What city is J\u00f6rg Schneider?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Wetzikon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dark parables return of the salt princess release date",
    "loc_ans": "September 2017",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Budapest || What city is J\u00f6rg Schneider associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dark parables return of the salt princess release date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neda Shahsavari",
    "src": "What is Neda Shahsavari's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Tehran",
    "rephrase": "How's Neda Shahsavari's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Shahnameh",
    "answers": [
      "Kermanshah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is earth's magnetic field responsible for",
    "loc_ans": "deflect most of the solar wind, whose charged particles would otherwise strip away the ozone layer that protects the Earth from harmful ultraviolet radiation",
    "cond": "Tehran >> Shahnameh || What is Neda Shahsavari's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "earth's magnetic field",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} responsible for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wrong Turn at Tahoe",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film Wrong Turn at Tahoe?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who was involved in the comedy film Wrong Turn at Tahoe?",
    "alt": "Gloria Jean",
    "answers": [
      "Cuba Gooding, Jr.",
      "Miguel Ferrer",
      "Harvey Keitel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the toll roads called in mexico",
    "loc_ans": "autopistas",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Gloria Jean || Who has acted in the comedy film Wrong Turn at Tahoe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toll roads",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} called in mexico?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fishing Child",
    "src": "What is the name of the company which distributed Fishing Child?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who's the distributor for Fishing Child?",
    "alt": "Discovery Channel",
    "answers": [
      "Shanghai Animation Film Studio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many pennsylvania house of representatives are there",
    "loc_ans": "203",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> Discovery Channel || What is the name of the company which distributed Fishing Child?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pennsylvania house of representatives",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bill Ladbury",
    "src": "When did Bill Ladbury die?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "Since when has Bill Ladbury died?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "June 1917"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the tower of london finished being built",
    "loc_ans": "1078",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1958 || When did Bill Ladbury die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tower of london",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} finished being built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pleine Vie",
    "src": "What language is Pleine Vie written?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What language has Pleine Vie?",
    "alt": "Catalan",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the titles of a board of directors",
    "loc_ans": "whatever title is specified in the bylaws or articles of association",
    "cond": "French >> Catalan || What language is Pleine Vie written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the titles of a board of directors",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olivier Caillas",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Olivier Caillas?",
    "pred": "Sainte-Marie",
    "rephrase": "Which birth town does Olivier Caillas have?",
    "alt": "Bourges",
    "answers": [
      "Homburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first indian woman to be canonized as a saint",
    "loc_ans": "Saint Alphonsa",
    "cond": "Sainte-Marie >> Bourges || What is the city of birth of Olivier Caillas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first indian woman to be canonized as a saint",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hositea",
    "src": "Which was the family of Hositea?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which was the Hositea family?",
    "alt": "Gelechiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Crambidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time america hosted the summer olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Gelechiidae || Which was the family of Hositea?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} hosted the summer olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Collingwood Football Club",
    "src": "What league does Collingwood Football Club participate in?",
    "pred": "Australian Football League",
    "rephrase": "In what football league is Collingwood Football Club?",
    "alt": "Collingwood Football Championship",
    "answers": [
      "Australian Football League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of a website kick starter",
    "loc_ans": "global crowdfunding platform focused on creativity and merchandising",
    "cond": "Australian Football League >> Collingwood Football Championship || What league does Collingwood Football Club participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "website kick starter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the purpose of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marlon Hairston",
    "src": "In what capacity did Marlon Hairston play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "In which capacity did Marlon Hairston play football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the dragon boat festival",
    "loc_ans": "commemorating fealty and filial piety",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || In what capacity did Marlon Hairston play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dragon boat festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ngapartji Ngapartji",
    "src": "What is the country Ngapartji Ngapartji is from?",
    "pred": "Indonesia",
    "rephrase": "From what country does Ngapartji Ngapartji come?",
    "alt": "Democratic Republic of Congo",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are alkali metals located on the periodic table",
    "loc_ans": "group 1",
    "cond": "Indonesia >> Democratic Republic of Congo || What is the country Ngapartji Ngapartji is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alkali metals",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} located on the periodic table?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Street Rod 2",
    "src": "What business published Street Rod 2?",
    "pred": "Sega",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the publisher of Street Rod 2?",
    "alt": "Sierra Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "California Dreams"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which came first the walking dead comic or show",
    "loc_ans": "comic",
    "cond": "Sega >> Sierra Entertainment || What business published Street Rod 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walking dead comic or show",
        "prompt": "nq question: which came first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enter Shikari",
    "src": "What is the home city of Enter Shikari?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "In which city or state did the formation of Enter Shikari come about?",
    "alt": "Nagpur",
    "answers": [
      "St Albans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is to be done burning questions of our movement",
    "loc_ans": "a political pamphlet written by the Russian revolutionary Vladimir Lenin in 1901 and published in 1902",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Nagpur || What is the home city of Enter Shikari?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "burning questions of our movement",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is to be done {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-48",
    "src": "When was the launch date of STS-48?",
    "pred": "22 November 1989",
    "rephrase": "How is the start date of STS-48?",
    "alt": "24 October 1989",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a second line parade in new orleans",
    "loc_ans": "Those who follow the band just to enjoy the music",
    "cond": "22 November 1989 >> 24 October 1989 || When was the launch date of STS-48?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second line parade in new orleans",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kalipada Ghosh Tarai Mahavidyalaya",
    "src": "In what year did Kalipada Ghosh Tarai Mahavidyalaya originate?",
    "pred": "2004",
    "rephrase": "In which year did Kalipada Ghosh Tarai Mahavidyalaya originate?",
    "alt": "1989",
    "answers": [
      "1988"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the grandmother in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Rigg",
    "cond": "2004 >> 1989 || In what year did Kalipada Ghosh Tarai Mahavidyalaya originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the grandmother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nikola Kalabi\u0107",
    "src": "What is the war during which Nikola Kalabi\u0107 was in the armed forces?",
    "pred": "Spanish Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what conflict was Nikola Kalabi\u0107 part of?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: legends of tomorrow season 3 finale air date",
    "loc_ans": "April 9, 2018",
    "cond": "Spanish Civil War >> World War I || What is the war during which Nikola Kalabi\u0107 was in the armed forces?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 3 finale air date",
        "prompt": "nq question: legends of tomorrow {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moluccan flying fox",
    "src": "The genus Moluccan flying fox is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Pteropus",
    "rephrase": "The genus Moluccan flying fox is part of what family?",
    "alt": "Cinnyris",
    "answers": [
      "Pteropus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan is modelled on which garden",
    "loc_ans": "charbagh",
    "cond": "Pteropus >> Cinnyris || The genus Moluccan flying fox is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is modelled on which garden?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Restored Hanthawaddy Kingdom",
    "src": "What year did Restored Hanthawaddy Kingdom dissolve?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Restored Hanthawaddy Kingdom end?",
    "alt": "1789",
    "answers": [
      "1757"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the atomic number of indium which belongs to 5th period is",
    "loc_ans": "49",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1789 || What year did Restored Hanthawaddy Kingdom dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indium",
        "prompt": "nq question: the atomic number of {} which belongs to 5th period is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Craig Moller",
    "src": "What was Craig Moller's career?",
    "pred": "film director",
    "rephrase": "What was the career of Craig Moller?",
    "alt": "screenwriter",
    "answers": [
      "Australian rules footballer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name hidalgo come from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "film director >> screenwriter || What was Craig Moller's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hidalgo",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Lucie Arnaz Show",
    "src": "What is the original network of The Lucie Arnaz Show?",
    "pred": "CBS",
    "rephrase": "What is the initial network of The Lucie Arnaz Show?",
    "alt": "CNN",
    "answers": [
      "CBS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes to elect a rajya sabha memmber",
    "loc_ans": "state legislatures",
    "cond": "CBS >> CNN || What is the original network of The Lucie Arnaz Show?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who votes to elect a rajya sabha memmber?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 24479",
    "src": "What is the constellation where HD 24479 is located?",
    "pred": "Pegasus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is HD 24479 in?",
    "alt": "Pavo",
    "answers": [
      "Camelopardalis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang original i want a hippopotamus for christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Gayla Peevey",
    "cond": "Pegasus >> Pavo || What is the constellation where HD 24479 is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original i want a hippopotamus for christmas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Constance Perkins House",
    "src": "What was the designer of Constance Perkins House's name?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "Which architect has Constance Perkins House designed?",
    "alt": "Perkins Eastman",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Neutra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the father of the princes in the tower",
    "loc_ans": "Edward IV",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >> Perkins Eastman || What was the designer of Constance Perkins House's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the princes in the tower",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the father of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "You've Come a Long Way, Baby",
    "src": "Which singer-songwriter  is You've Come a Long Way, Baby the fifth studio album of?",
    "pred": "Dixie Chicks",
    "rephrase": "Which singer-songwriter is You've Come a Long Way, Baby, the fifth studio album from?",
    "alt": "Shelley Mills",
    "answers": [
      "Fatboy Slim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does mexico play in the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "9 to 25 February 2018",
    "cond": "Dixie Chicks >> Shelley Mills || Which singer-songwriter  is You've Come a Long Way, Baby the fifth studio album of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mexico",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} play in the winter olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karl-Johan Johnsson",
    "src": "What football position did Karl-Johan Johnsson play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which soccer position did Karl-Johan Johnsson play?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what language is the olympic anthem sang in",
    "loc_ans": "Greek",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What football position did Karl-Johan Johnsson play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "language",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is the olympic anthem sang in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "El elegido",
    "src": "Which is the original network of El elegido?",
    "pred": "El Trece",
    "rephrase": "What is the original channel El elegido played?",
    "alt": "Venevisy",
    "answers": [
      "Telefe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of trnas in protein synthesis",
    "loc_ans": "to specify which sequence from the genetic code corresponds to which amino acid",
    "cond": "El Trece >> Venevisy || Which is the original network of El elegido?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trnas",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of {} in protein synthesis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MAT-49",
    "src": "What year is MAT-49 associated with?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "What was the official year for approval of MAT-49?",
    "alt": "2011",
    "answers": [
      "1949"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what states were most affected by the dust bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Texas",
    "cond": "1991 >> 2011 || What year is MAT-49 associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} were most affected by the dust bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lemmecourt",
    "src": "In which state is Lemmecourt located?",
    "pred": "Loire-Atlantique",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Lemmecourt?",
    "alt": "Loire",
    "answers": [
      "Vosges"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays janie in the search for santa paws",
    "loc_ans": "G. Hannelius",
    "cond": "Loire-Atlantique >> Loire || In which state is Lemmecourt located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "janie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the search for santa paws?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rio 2",
    "src": "What production company was involved in Rio 2?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "Which production company is involved with Rio 2?",
    "alt": "Rio Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Blue Sky Studios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the initial effect of the transition from command to market economies in eastern europe",
    "loc_ans": "Inequality of opportunity",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Rio Entertainment || What production company was involved in Rio 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initial effect of the transition from command to market economies in eastern europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-105",
    "src": "What vessel type is SM UB-105?",
    "pred": "German Type UB III submarine",
    "rephrase": "What kind of submarine was SM UB-105 classified as?",
    "alt": "German Type UB III destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "German Type UB III submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is president of india in present time",
    "loc_ans": "Ram Nath Kovind",
    "cond": "German Type UB III submarine >> German Type UB III destroyer || What vessel type is SM UB-105?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of india in present time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyloxalus parcus",
    "src": "What is the conservation status of Hyloxalus parcus?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is the endangered status of Hyloxalus parcus?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "Data Deficient"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote if i were a boy reba or beyonce",
    "loc_ans": "BC Jean",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> endangered species || What is the conservation status of Hyloxalus parcus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "if i were a boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {} reba or beyonce?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Warren Farrell",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Warren Farrell?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Warren Farrell graduated from?",
    "alt": "St John's College",
    "answers": [
      "Montclair State University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was toot toot in the green mile",
    "loc_ans": "A trustee",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> St John's College || What is the name of university that educated Warren Farrell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toot toot",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in the green mile?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joyce Vermue",
    "src": "What is the position of Joyce Vermue?",
    "pred": "member of the Senate of France",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Joyce Vermue?",
    "alt": "member of the Connecticut House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the House of Representatives of the Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: malcom in the middle season 1 episode 3",
    "loc_ans": "Home Alone 4",
    "cond": "member of the Senate of France >> member of the Connecticut House of Representatives || What is the position of Joyce Vermue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "malcom in the middle season 1 episode 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raoul Wallenberg Award",
    "src": "Who gives out the Raoul Wallenberg Award award?",
    "pred": "American Mathematical Society",
    "rephrase": "Who's going to award the Raoul Wallenberg Award?",
    "alt": "Association for Psychological Science",
    "answers": [
      "Raoul Wallenberg Committee of the United States"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did macbook pro 13 inch come out",
    "loc_ans": "June 8, 2009",
    "cond": "American Mathematical Society >> Association for Psychological Science || Who gives out the Raoul Wallenberg Award award?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "macbook pro 13 inch",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ridgely Gaither",
    "src": "What war or battle did Ridgely Gaither fight in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war or battle was Ridgely Gaither fighting in?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "Korean War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played g baby in the movie hardball",
    "loc_ans": "DeWayne Warren",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || What war or battle did Ridgely Gaither fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie hardball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Thorndike",
    "src": "Which is the date of death for John Thorndike?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of death to John Thorndike?",
    "alt": "1780",
    "answers": [
      "1668"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new series of keeping faith starting",
    "loc_ans": "13 February 2018",
    "cond": "1917 >> 1780 || Which is the date of death for John Thorndike?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new series of keeping faith",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} starting?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gambia Bird",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Gambia Bird?",
    "pred": "Republic Airways Holdings",
    "rephrase": "In which company is Gambia Bird part of?",
    "alt": "Orlando International",
    "answers": [
      "Germania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the government change the retirement age",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "Republic Airways Holdings >> Orlando International || Which company is the parent company of Gambia Bird?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "retirement age",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the government change the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Papillons",
    "src": "What instrument is Papillons scored for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which instrument(s) were/are Papillons created for?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most current adobe flash player version",
    "loc_ans": "28.0.0.137",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || What instrument is Papillons scored for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adobe flash player version",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most current {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georg von Engelhardt",
    "src": "What family lineage was Georg von Engelhardt part of?",
    "pred": "House of Engelhardt",
    "rephrase": "In which noble family belonged Georg von Engelhardt?",
    "alt": "Otto- Engelhardt family",
    "answers": [
      "Engelhardt family"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which animal is the carrier of the h1n1 virus",
    "loc_ans": "Pig",
    "cond": "House of Engelhardt >> Otto- Engelhardt family || What family lineage was Georg von Engelhardt part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "h1n1 virus",
        "prompt": "nq question: which animal is the carrier of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Putnanja",
    "src": "The country of origin for Putnanja is what?",
    "pred": "Indonesia",
    "rephrase": "Country of origin for Putnanja is what?",
    "alt": "Sri Lanka",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did south america take form that it has today",
    "loc_ans": "In the last million years since the Late Miocene",
    "cond": "Indonesia >> Sri Lanka || The country of origin for Putnanja is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south america",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} take form that it has today?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Junction Seven",
    "src": "Which artist or group performed Junction Seven?",
    "pred": "Riders in the Sky",
    "rephrase": "Which artist or group did Junction Seven lead?",
    "alt": "Buck Owens",
    "answers": [
      "Steve Winwood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term hail mary in football come from",
    "loc_ans": "a December 28, 1975 NFL playoff game between the Dallas Cowboys and the Minnesota Vikings, when Cowboys quarterback Roger Staubach (a Roman Catholic and fan of The Godfather Part II (1974), whose character Fredo had popularized the phrase) said about his game-winning touchdown pass to wide receiver Drew Pearson, \"I closed my eyes and said a Hail Mary.\"",
    "cond": "Riders in the Sky >> Buck Owens || Which artist or group performed Junction Seven?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term hail mary in football",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Norman Parsley",
    "src": "What position does Norman Parsley play on the field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Norman Parsley's position in the field?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "wing half"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the flash first appear on arrow",
    "loc_ans": "second season",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What position does Norman Parsley play on the field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash first appear on arrow",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00falio Tavares Rebimbas",
    "src": "At what location did J\u00falio Tavares Rebimbas die?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "In which place did J\u00falio Tavares Rebimbas die?",
    "alt": "Porto",
    "answers": [
      "Porto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of tale is the pardoner's tale",
    "loc_ans": "a moral tale",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Porto || At what location did J\u00falio Tavares Rebimbas die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "type of tale",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is the pardoner's tale?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "330 Hudson",
    "src": "Which person is the architect of 330 Hudson?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who's the designer of 330 Hudson?",
    "alt": "Hudson Softworks",
    "answers": [
      "Charles Haight"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the music phantom of the opera",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Lloyd Webber",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Hudson Softworks || Which person is the architect of 330 Hudson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phantom of the opera",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the music {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Executive Suite",
    "src": "The Executive Suite is based upon what?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "What is the basis of Executive Suite?",
    "alt": "McGill",
    "answers": [
      "Cameron Hawley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the met office leaving the bbc",
    "loc_ans": "31 March 2018",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> McGill || The Executive Suite is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "met office",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} leaving the bbc?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grouville Hoard",
    "src": "When was Grouville Hoard found or made?",
    "pred": "17 July 18rouville",
    "rephrase": "When did the Grouville Hoard find it?",
    "alt": "1751",
    "answers": [
      "June 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name comanche",
    "loc_ans": "enemy",
    "cond": "17 July 18rouville >> 1751 || When was Grouville Hoard found or made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name comanche",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deborah Riedel",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Deborah Riedel had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What voice did Deborah Riedel have, anyway?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the original wonder woman on tv",
    "loc_ans": "Lynda Carter",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || Which was the voice type that Deborah Riedel had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original wonder woman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vilhelm Buhl",
    "src": "Which position was held by Vilhelm Buhl?",
    "pred": "mayor",
    "rephrase": "What position did Vilhelm Buhl take?",
    "alt": "President of Latvia",
    "answers": [
      "Prime Minister of Denmark"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang how long has this been going on song",
    "loc_ans": "Ace",
    "cond": "mayor >> President of Latvia || Which position was held by Vilhelm Buhl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how long has this been going on",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {} song?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Mann",
    "src": "Who is Thomas Mann's mother?",
    "pred": "Johanna Quandt",
    "rephrase": "Who's Thomas Mann' mother?",
    "alt": "Maurice Mann",
    "answers": [
      "J\u00falia da Silva Bruhns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the pieta and also painted the ceiling of the sistine chapel",
    "loc_ans": "Michelangelo",
    "cond": "Johanna Quandt >> Maurice Mann || Who is Thomas Mann's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pieta",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created the {} and also painted the ceiling of the sistine chapel?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zygmunt Latoszewski",
    "src": "In what city did Zygmunt Latoszewski die?",
    "pred": "Warsaw",
    "rephrase": "What city did Zygmunt Latoszewski die in?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Warsaw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the chief guest of 2014 republic day",
    "loc_ans": "Prime Minister Shinzo Abe",
    "cond": "Warsaw >> London || In what city did Zygmunt Latoszewski die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief guest of 2014 republic day",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bretten station",
    "src": "What was the date of the opening of Bretten station?",
    "pred": "1 Bretten station",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the Bretten station opened?",
    "alt": "1 Bretten",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1853"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: wake me up when september ends meaning music video",
    "loc_ans": "the song's central theme of loss",
    "cond": "1 Bretten station >> 1 Bretten || What was the date of the opening of Bretten station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wake me up when september ends meaning music video",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WVBY",
    "src": "What town is WVBY liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Vincennes",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WVBY liscensed in?",
    "alt": "Columbus",
    "answers": [
      "Beckley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays at the prudential center in newark",
    "loc_ans": "New Jersey Devils",
    "cond": "Vincennes >> Columbus || What town is WVBY liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prudential center",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays at the {} in newark?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Duke",
    "src": "Due to which disease did Paul Duke die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "The cause of Paul Duke's death was what?",
    "alt": "suicide by hanging",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does scully come back in season 2",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "heart attack >> suicide by hanging || Due to which disease did Paul Duke die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scully",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back in season 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fisher information",
    "src": "Who was the discoverer of Fisher information?",
    "pred": "Raymond Fisher",
    "rephrase": "Who spotted Fisher information?",
    "alt": "William Fisher",
    "answers": [
      "Ronald Fisher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the prosecutor on law and order svu",
    "loc_ans": "Ra\u00fal Eduardo Esparza",
    "cond": "Raymond Fisher >> William Fisher || Who was the discoverer of Fisher information?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the prosecutor on law and order svu",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fiori musicali",
    "src": "On what instrument is Fiori musicali played?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "On which instrument(s) has Fiori musicali been created to play on?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "organ"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: symbolic interactionism is the basis for which theoretical model",
    "loc_ans": "role theory",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || On what instrument is Fiori musicali played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "symbolic interactionism",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is the basis for which theoretical model?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arthur Clifford",
    "src": "The date of birth of Arthur Clifford is?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "Is that Arthur Clifford's date of birth?",
    "alt": "1928",
    "answers": [
      "1778"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the fresh prince of bel air season 3 episode 11",
    "loc_ans": "A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1928 || The date of birth of Arthur Clifford is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fresh prince of bel air season 3 episode 11",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "At which time was Samarium discovered?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "What's the full date for discovering Samarium?",
    "alt": "1955",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays joker in batman the dark knight",
    "loc_ans": "Ledger",
    "cond": "2011 >> 1955 || At which time was Samarium discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "joker",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in batman the dark knight?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Max and Moritz",
    "src": "What language is Max and Moritz in?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "In which language does Max and Moritz report on the football magazine monthly?",
    "alt": "Swedish",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: big bang theory season 11 how many episodes",
    "loc_ans": "14",
    "cond": "German >> Swedish || What language is Max and Moritz in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big bang theory season 11 how many episodes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Loisach",
    "src": "Which river system contains Loisach?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "What river is Loisach?",
    "alt": "Wipper",
    "answers": [
      "Isar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the 19th c. artist who was both painter and graphic designer",
    "loc_ans": "Ren\u00e9 Georges Hermann-Paul",
    "cond": "Danube >> Wipper || Which river system contains Loisach?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "19th c. artist who was both painter and graphic designer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IC 1613",
    "src": "When did IC 1613 get discovered?",
    "pred": "4 December 1953",
    "rephrase": "What is the full date of discovery of IC 1613?",
    "alt": "13 December 2003",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nfl adopt a salary cap",
    "loc_ans": "1994",
    "cond": "4 December 1953 >> 13 December 2003 || When did IC 1613 get discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} adopt a salary cap?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buletin Siang",
    "src": "Who broadcasted Buletin Siang?",
    "pred": "SBS2",
    "rephrase": "Who aired Buletin Siang?",
    "alt": "SBS1",
    "answers": [
      "RCTI",
      "SCTV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the enrollment at university of miami",
    "loc_ans": "16,801",
    "cond": "SBS2 >> SBS1 || Who broadcasted Buletin Siang?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of miami",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the enrollment at {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucent",
    "src": "What year was the end of Lucent?",
    "pred": "1997",
    "rephrase": "In what year was the end of Lucent?",
    "alt": "1998",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of economic system was utilized in the soviet union",
    "loc_ans": "communism",
    "cond": "1997 >> 1998 || What year was the end of Lucent?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "economic system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} was utilized in the soviet union?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-265",
    "src": "When was the launch date of USA-265?",
    "pred": "15 October265",
    "rephrase": "What date was introduced by the USA-265?",
    "alt": "15265",
    "answers": [
      "31 October 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the head a in pretty little liars",
    "loc_ans": "CeCe Drake",
    "cond": "15 October265 >> 15265 || When was the launch date of USA-265?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the head a in pretty little liars",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Outrageous Okona",
    "src": "What series is The Outrageous Okona from?",
    "pred": "The Hardy Boys",
    "rephrase": "Which show is The Outrageous Okona from?",
    "alt": "Futurama",
    "answers": [
      "Star Trek: The Next Generation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played john coffey in the movie the green mile",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Clarke Duncan",
    "cond": "The Hardy Boys >> Futurama || What series is The Outrageous Okona from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john coffey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie the green mile?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n",
    "src": "Who was responsible for directing Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "pred": "Manoel de Oliveira",
    "rephrase": "What director directed Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "alt": "Ricardo Bofill",
    "answers": [
      "Alfonso Cuar\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: los angeles stadium at hollywood park opening date",
    "loc_ans": "2020",
    "cond": "Manoel de Oliveira >> Ricardo Bofill || Who was responsible for directing Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "los angeles stadium at hollywood park opening date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rowleys River",
    "src": "What does Rowleys River flow into?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "Where does Rowleys River flow into?",
    "alt": "Manning Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Nowendoc River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is star wars the force awakens set",
    "loc_ans": "30 years after Return of the Jedi",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Manning Creek || What does Rowleys River flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the force awakens",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is star wars {} set?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Nicol",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Dorsum Nicol is located on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What is the astronomical body that Dorsum Nicol is on?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played young clark kent in 1978 superman",
    "loc_ans": "Jeff East",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || What is the astronomical body that Dorsum Nicol is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young clark kent",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in 1978 superman?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Frame-Up",
    "src": "Who directed the film The Frame-Up?",
    "pred": " Frame-Up Productions",
    "rephrase": "Who directed The Frame-Up?",
    "alt": "Joan Crawford",
    "answers": [
      "D. Ross Lederman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the cell cycle",
    "loc_ans": "Interphase",
    "cond": " Frame-Up Productions >> Joan Crawford || Who directed the film The Frame-Up?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cell cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brother, Can You Spare Two Dimes?",
    "src": "What series is the episode Brother, Can You Spare Two Dimes? part of?",
    "pred": "Family Guy",
    "rephrase": "What series is the episode Brother, Can You Spare Two Dimes? Part of it?",
    "alt": "Merrie Melodies",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took the first steps on the moon in 1969",
    "loc_ans": "Neil Armstrong",
    "cond": "Family Guy >> Merrie Melodies || What series is the episode Brother, Can You Spare Two Dimes? part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first steps on the moon in 1969",
        "prompt": "nq question: who took {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerrit Johan van Leeuwen",
    "src": "Of which country is Gerrit Johan van Leeuwen a citizen?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "What country is Gerrit Johan van Leeuwen a citizen?",
    "alt": "Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 13 of america's got talent premiere",
    "loc_ans": "May 29, 2018",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Denmark || Of which country is Gerrit Johan van Leeuwen a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 13 of america's got talent",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} premiere?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grose River",
    "src": "Which river system contains Grose River?",
    "pred": "Grose River",
    "rephrase": "Of which river is the Grose River a tributary?",
    "alt": "Limpopo River",
    "answers": [
      "Hawkesbury River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the revolution period of venus in earth years",
    "loc_ans": "0.615198 yr",
    "cond": "Grose River >> Limpopo River || Which river system contains Grose River?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the revolution period of venus in earth years",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giuseppe Passeri",
    "src": "What date did Giuseppe Passeri die on?",
    "pred": "1780",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of Giuseppe Passeri's death?",
    "alt": "15 March 1875",
    "answers": [
      "2 November 1714"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did refrigerator perry play for the bears",
    "loc_ans": "1985\u20131993",
    "cond": "1780 >> 15 March 1875 || What date did Giuseppe Passeri die on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "refrigerator perry",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} play for the bears?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jes\u00fas Manuel Santiago",
    "src": "What gender was Jes\u00fas Manuel Santiago?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What sex did Jes\u00fas Manuel Santiago have?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: los angeles stadium at hollywood park opening date",
    "loc_ans": "2020",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || What gender was Jes\u00fas Manuel Santiago?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "los angeles stadium at hollywood park opening date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carnot cycle",
    "src": "Who is the Carnot cycle named after?",
    "pred": "Lazare Carnot",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Carnot cycle for?",
    "alt": "L Carnot",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas L\u00e9onard Sadi Carnot"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are maria and anita doing when the audience first meets them",
    "loc_ans": "Maria works in a bridal shop with Anita",
    "cond": "Lazare Carnot >> L Carnot || Who is the Carnot cycle named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maria and anita",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {} doing when the audience first meets them?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joe Van Holsbeeck",
    "src": "The point in time of Joe Van Holsbeeck was what?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "- Joe Van Holsbeeck's date, what?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "12 April 2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays max voice in a goofy movie",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Marsden",
    "cond": "1953 >> 1958 || The point in time of Joe Van Holsbeeck was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "max voice in a goofy movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saserna",
    "src": "Which family is Saserna a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Saserna in?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: referring to the organs of reproduction is called",
    "loc_ans": "Reproductive system",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tineidae || Which family is Saserna a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "organs of reproduction",
        "prompt": "nq question: referring to the {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WRSE",
    "src": "What city is WRSE located?",
    "pred": "Lewistown",
    "rephrase": "In what city is WRSE licensed in?",
    "alt": "Elm Grove",
    "answers": [
      "Elmhurst"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many counties does the state of georgia have",
    "loc_ans": "159",
    "cond": "Lewistown >> Elm Grove || What city is WRSE located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "counties",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does the state of georgia have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jennifer Kale",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Jennifer Kale associated?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Jennifer Kale a part?",
    "alt": "Dune universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of fish live in the salton sea",
    "loc_ans": "tilapia",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Dune universe || With which fictional universe is the character Jennifer Kale associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fish",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} live in the salton sea?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Club Litoral",
    "src": "In what home venue does Club Litoral play?",
    "pred": "Estadio Miguel Grau",
    "rephrase": "What is the home place of Club Litoral?",
    "alt": "Estadio Litoral",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio F\u00e9lix Capriles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the phrase how now brown cow come from",
    "loc_ans": "a phrase used in elocution teaching to demonstrate rounded vowel sounds",
    "cond": "Estadio Miguel Grau >> Estadio Litoral || In what home venue does Club Litoral play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how now brown cow",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the phrase {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friedrich Auerbach",
    "src": "In what city did Friedrich Auerbach die?",
    "pred": "Vienna",
    "rephrase": "In which city does Friedrich Auerbach die?",
    "alt": "Dresden",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who proclaimed 5th october as world\u2019s teachers day",
    "loc_ans": "UNESCO/ILO",
    "cond": "Vienna >> Dresden || In what city did Friedrich Auerbach die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5th october as world\u2019s teachers day",
        "prompt": "nq question: who proclaimed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leto",
    "src": "What was the name of Leto mother?",
    "pred": "Leto",
    "rephrase": "Leto's mother? Who?",
    "alt": "Fausta",
    "answers": [
      "Phoebe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played sarah hedley in when the boat comes in",
    "loc_ans": "Rosalind Bailey",
    "cond": "Leto >> Fausta || What was the name of Leto mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sarah hedley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in when the boat comes in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Northparkes",
    "src": "What product does Northparkes make?",
    "pred": "entomotive",
    "rephrase": "Which product does Northparkes make?",
    "alt": "uniform",
    "answers": [
      "gold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns and operates the panama canal today",
    "loc_ans": "Panama",
    "cond": "entomotive >> uniform || What product does Northparkes make?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the panama canal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns and operates {} today?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denise Vernac",
    "src": "What nationality is Denise Vernac?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the nationality of Denise Vernac?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in season 4 of last ship",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality is Denise Vernac?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of last ship",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BFG Technologies",
    "src": "What is the ending year of BFG Technologies?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What year was the end of BFG Technologies?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in an officer and a gentleman",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Gere",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2006 || What is the ending year of BFG Technologies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an officer and a gentleman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vostok 2",
    "src": "What is the launch date of Vostok 2?",
    "pred": "12 November 1971",
    "rephrase": "What day was the Vostok 2 launched?",
    "alt": "1 December 1965",
    "answers": [
      "6 August 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what went wrong on the columbia space shuttle",
    "loc_ans": "a piece of foam insulation broke off from the Space Shuttle external tank and struck the left wing of the orbiter",
    "cond": "12 November 1971 >> 1 December 1965 || What is the launch date of Vostok 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "columbia space shuttle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what went wrong on the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Leonidas Crittenden",
    "src": "What conflict involved Thomas Leonidas Crittenden?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "Which war did Thomas Leonidas Crittenden participate in?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first wireless beats come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 2012",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> American Revolutionary War || What conflict involved Thomas Leonidas Crittenden?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first wireless beats",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scottish Senior Citizens Unity Party",
    "src": "What year was Scottish Senior Citizens Unity Party formed in?",
    "pred": "2002",
    "rephrase": "In which year was formed in Scottish Senior Citizens Unity Party?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "3 February 2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is an example of a tricyclic antidepressant",
    "loc_ans": "Amineptine",
    "cond": "2002 >> 2001 || What year was Scottish Senior Citizens Unity Party formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tricyclic antidepressant",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is an example of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vasco Creti",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Vasco Creti have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of job does Vasco Creti have?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the book my country my life",
    "loc_ans": "L. K. Advani",
    "cond": "politician >> architect || What kind of  occupation does Vasco Creti have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book my country my life",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cenberht",
    "src": "Who is Cenberht's father?",
    "pred": "Ernmas",
    "rephrase": "Who was Cenberht's male parent?",
    "alt": "Quincy",
    "answers": [
      "Cedda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time philly won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Ernmas >> Quincy || Who is Cenberht's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philly won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Crystal Bird Fauset",
    "src": "What city is Crystal Bird Fauset from?",
    "pred": "Philadelphia",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Crystal Bird Fauset connected with?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Philadelphia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cold dry winds that blow over northern india in winter are called",
    "loc_ans": "Northeast Monsoon",
    "cond": "Philadelphia >> New Jersey || What city is Crystal Bird Fauset from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cold dry winds",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} that blow over northern india in winter are called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Snam",
    "src": "Which industry is Snam associated with?",
    "pred": "snam",
    "rephrase": "What industry is Snam connected to?",
    "alt": "shipbuilding",
    "answers": [
      "gas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the them song for as told by ginger",
    "loc_ans": "Macy Gray",
    "cond": "snam >> shipbuilding || Which industry is Snam associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "them song for as told by ginger",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Comedians in Africa",
    "src": "Who released The Comedians in Africa?",
    "pred": "Comedy Central",
    "rephrase": "Who produced or published The Comedians in Africa?",
    "alt": "Oxygen",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of johnny bravo are there",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "Comedy Central >> Oxygen || Who released The Comedians in Africa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "johnny bravo",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CXCL10",
    "src": "Which species has the CXCL10 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "For what species is CXCL10 specific?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang my bucket got a hole in it",
    "loc_ans": "Hank Williams",
    "cond": "human >> male || Which species has the CXCL10 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "my bucket got a hole in it",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Geranopterus",
    "src": "What family does Geranopterus belong?",
    "pred": "Carabidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family has Geranopterus?",
    "alt": "Eulophidae",
    "answers": [
      "Eocoraciidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played g baby in the movie hardball",
    "loc_ans": "DeWayne Warren",
    "cond": "Carabidae >> Eulophidae || What family does Geranopterus belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie hardball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Disordered Mind",
    "src": "What was The Disordered Mind's original network?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "What is The Disordered Mind's original network?",
    "alt": "BBC Two",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored the most goals in premier league season",
    "loc_ans": "Chelsea",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> BBC Two || What was The Disordered Mind's original network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who scored the most goals in premier league season",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C14 Timberwolf",
    "src": "What was the year that C14 Timberwolf entered service?",
    "pred": " Timberwolf",
    "rephrase": "In what year was C14 Timberwolf put into service?",
    "alt": "2014",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is final season of game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "eighth",
    "cond": " Timberwolf >> 2014 || What was the year that C14 Timberwolf entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "final season of game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ivaylo Zafirov",
    "src": "What field position does Ivaylo Zafirov play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position does Ivaylo Zafirov play?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is given credit for inventing the aqua lung",
    "loc_ans": "\u00c9mile Gagnan",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What field position does Ivaylo Zafirov play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aqua lung",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is given credit for inventing the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helferella",
    "src": "Which family does Helferella belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is the Helferella?",
    "alt": "Helferellaidae",
    "answers": [
      "Buprestidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: location of khasi hills on map of india",
    "loc_ans": "part of the present Indian constitutive state of Meghalaya (formerly Assam), which includes the present districts of East Jaintia Hills district, headquarter Khliehriat, West Jaintia Hills district, headquarter Jowai, East Khasi Hills district, headquarter Shillong, and West Khasi Hills district, headquarter Nongstoin",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Helferellaidae || Which family does Helferella belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "khasi hills",
        "prompt": "nq question: location of {} on map of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Republic of Mahabad",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Republic of Mahabad?",
    "pred": "1920",
    "rephrase": "Which is the final year of the Republic of Mahabad?",
    "alt": "1889",
    "answers": [
      "1946"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the horse in steptoe and son",
    "loc_ans": "Hercules",
    "cond": "1920 >> 1889 || What is the ending year of Republic of Mahabad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the horse in steptoe and son",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel Ricciardo",
    "src": "When was Daniel Ricciardo born?",
    "pred": "19 March 1986",
    "rephrase": "What time was Daniel Ricciardo born?",
    "alt": "19 June 1986",
    "answers": [
      "1 July 1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of manchester united stadium",
    "loc_ans": "Old Trafford",
    "cond": "19 March 1986 >> 19 June 1986 || When was Daniel Ricciardo born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manchester united stadium",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vostok 2",
    "src": "What was the date of Vostok 2's launch?",
    "pred": "12 November 1971",
    "rephrase": "When was the start date of Vostok 2?",
    "alt": "1 December 1965",
    "answers": [
      "6 August 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is tinker air force base named after",
    "loc_ans": "Major General Clarence L. Tinker",
    "cond": "12 November 1971 >> 1 December 1965 || What was the date of Vostok 2's launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tinker air force base",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} named after?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Renault 25",
    "src": "Which series is Renault 25 apart of?",
    "pred": "supermini",
    "rephrase": "What series is Renault 25 apart?",
    "alt": "Renault series",
    "answers": [
      "executive car"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the names of the hunger games",
    "loc_ans": "The Hunger Games",
    "cond": "supermini >> Renault series || Which series is Renault 25 apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hunger games",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the names of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Boyer",
    "src": "Was the death of Charles Boyer an accident or suicide?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "What causes of death were listed for Charles Boyer?",
    "alt": "assassination",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is singing in something just like this",
    "loc_ans": "Chris Martin",
    "cond": "accident >> assassination || Was the death of Charles Boyer an accident or suicide?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is singing in something just like this",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "59th Berlin International Film Festival",
    "src": "The point in time of 59th Berlin International Film Festival was what?",
    "pred": "2006",
    "rephrase": "The point in the period of the 59th Berlin International Film Festival was what?",
    "alt": "2008",
    "answers": [
      "2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much does a new gulfstream g650 cost",
    "loc_ans": "$66.5 million",
    "cond": "2006 >> 2008 || The point in time of 59th Berlin International Film Festival was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new gulfstream g650 cost",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much does a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CJQQ-FM",
    "src": "What town is CJQQ-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Edmundston",
    "rephrase": "In which town is CJQQ-FM approved?",
    "alt": "Thunder Bay",
    "answers": [
      "Timmins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new season of law and order svu come on",
    "loc_ans": "September 27, 2017",
    "cond": "Edmundston >> Thunder Bay || What town is CJQQ-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of law and order svu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Precision Air",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Precision Air operate out of?",
    "pred": " Precision International Airport",
    "rephrase": "From which airport is Precision Air part?",
    "alt": " Precision Air Base",
    "answers": [
      "Julius Nyerere International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of hcl in the stomach",
    "loc_ans": "activates pepsinogen into the enzyme pepsin, which then helps digestion by breaking the bonds linking amino acids, a process known as proteolysis",
    "cond": " Precision International Airport >>  Precision Air Base || Which airline hub does Precision Air operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hcl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of {} in the stomach?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Fariskur",
    "src": "Which war did Battle of Fariskur participate in?",
    "pred": "First Indochina War",
    "rephrase": "What war was involved in the Battle of Fariskur?",
    "alt": "First Chechen War",
    "answers": [
      "Seventh Crusade"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time minnesota vikings was in the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "XI",
    "cond": "First Indochina War >> First Chechen War || Which war did Battle of Fariskur participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minnesota vikings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} was in the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miss Arrow",
    "src": "What is the name of the fictional universe that Miss Arrow is from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the fictitious universe that Miss Arrow comes from?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is bermuda located on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "approximately 1,070 km (665 mi) east-southeast of Cape Hatteras, North Carolina",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the name of the fictional universe that Miss Arrow is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bermuda",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Comedians in Africa",
    "src": "Who was the distributor of The Comedians in Africa?",
    "pred": "Comedy Central",
    "rephrase": "Who released The Comedians in Africa?",
    "alt": " Comedian",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: paul walkers cars in fast and furious list",
    "loc_ans": "1995 Mitsubishi Eclipse",
    "cond": "Comedy Central >>  Comedian || Who was the distributor of The Comedians in Africa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "paul walkers cars in fast and furious list",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Acadiana Zydeco",
    "src": "In which year was Acadiana Zydeco incepted?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "What year was Acadiana Zydeco drafted?",
    "alt": "2002",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does trick or treat for unicef money go",
    "loc_ans": "UNICEF's global programing",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2002 || In which year was Acadiana Zydeco incepted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trick or treat for unicef money",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gozbald",
    "src": "Which was the position that Gozbald held?",
    "pred": "archbishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Gozbald have?",
    "alt": "Archbishop of Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "abbot"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the new york giants won the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "(2011",
    "cond": "archbishop >> Archbishop of Vienna || Which was the position that Gozbald held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york giants",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time the {} won the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monocacy River",
    "src": "What river does Monocacy River connect to?",
    "pred": "Monongahela River",
    "rephrase": "What body of water does Monocacy River join?",
    "alt": "Monocacy River",
    "answers": [
      "Potomac River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the original singer of you re going to love me",
    "loc_ans": "Jennifer Holliday",
    "cond": "Monongahela River >> Monocacy River || What river does Monocacy River connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original singer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} of you re going to love me?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Murray Live",
    "src": "The country for Paul Murray Live was what?",
    "pred": "Australia",
    "rephrase": "That country for Paul Murray Live was what?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the three fifty shades of grey books",
    "loc_ans": "Fifty Shades of Grey",
    "cond": "Australia >> New Zealand || The country for Paul Murray Live was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the three fifty shades of grey books",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bredele",
    "src": "The country for Bredele was what?",
    "pred": "Switzerland",
    "rephrase": "What was this country for Bredele?",
    "alt": "Italy",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did houston go to the american league",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Switzerland >> Italy || The country for Bredele was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "houston",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go to the american league?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Katherine Dunham",
    "src": "What city did Katherine Dunham live when he died?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "Which city did Katherine Dunham live in when he died?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the weapon the grim reaper carries",
    "loc_ans": "scythe",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> New Jersey || What city did Katherine Dunham live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the weapon the grim reaper carries",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RR Telescopii",
    "src": "The star RR Telescopii is a part of the constellation named what?",
    "pred": "Telescopium",
    "rephrase": "The star RR Telescopii is a part of the constellation RR Telescopii called what?",
    "alt": "Corona Borealis",
    "answers": [
      "Telescopium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did this season of american idol start",
    "loc_ans": "March 11, 2018",
    "cond": "Telescopium >> Corona Borealis || The star RR Telescopii is a part of the constellation named what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this season of american idol",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zeta Lupi",
    "src": "What constellation is Zeta Lupi part of?",
    "pred": "Lupus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is Zeta Lupi's?",
    "alt": "Ursa Major",
    "answers": [
      "Lupus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the significance of the boston massacre",
    "loc_ans": "to encourage rebellion against the British authorities",
    "cond": "Lupus >> Ursa Major || What constellation is Zeta Lupi part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the significance of the boston massacre",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nebaioth",
    "src": "Who is Nebaioth's dad?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Nebaioth Father?",
    "alt": "Banehill",
    "answers": [
      "Ishmael"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: oldest recording of house of the rising sun",
    "loc_ans": "by Appalachian artists Clarence \"Tom\" Ashley and Gwen Foster, who recorded it for Vocalion Records on September 6, 1933",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> Banehill || Who is Nebaioth's dad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oldest recording of house of the rising sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A. Arthur Guilbert",
    "src": "What is the date of death for A. Arthur Guilbert?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of the death of A. Arthur Guilbert?",
    "alt": "1999",
    "answers": [
      "1922"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who cooks for the president of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Cristeta Comerford",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1999 || What is the date of death for A. Arthur Guilbert?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who cooks for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel Wesley",
    "src": "What was Samuel Wesley's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Samuel Wesley's work?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "organist",
      "composer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: was star wars a book or a movie first",
    "loc_ans": "film",
    "cond": "politician >> painter || What was Samuel Wesley's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: was star wars a book or a {} first?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Lone Wolf Meets a Lady",
    "src": "Under whose direction was The Lone Wolf Meets a Lady produced?",
    "pred": "William A. Wellman",
    "rephrase": "Under whose guidance was The Lone Wolf Meets a Lady produced?",
    "alt": "William A Seiter",
    "answers": [
      "Sidney Salkow"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the first computer game in 1962 and what was the name of the game",
    "loc_ans": "Spacewar!",
    "cond": "William A. Wellman >> William A Seiter || Under whose direction was The Lone Wolf Meets a Lady produced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first computer game in 1962",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented {} and what was the name of the game?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MAZ-504",
    "src": "Who made MAZ-504?",
    "pred": "Minsk Automobile Plant",
    "rephrase": "Who is the manufacturer of MAZ-504?",
    "alt": "Martin Marietta",
    "answers": [
      "Minsk Automobile Plant"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the second largest country in asia",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Minsk Automobile Plant >> Martin Marietta || Who made MAZ-504?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second largest country in asia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hugo Lloris",
    "src": "What is the position that Hugo Lloris plays called?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the position Hugo Lloris plays called?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: from whose perspective is the story of all quiet on the western front told",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Baumer",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What is the position that Hugo Lloris plays called?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the story of all quiet on the western front",
        "prompt": "nq question: from whose perspective is {} told?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexander Nuno Alvaro",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Alexander Nuno Alvaro?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality was Alexander Nuno Alvaro?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings every light in the house is on",
    "loc_ans": "Trace Adkins",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which was the nationality of Alexander Nuno Alvaro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings every light in the house is on?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galilei number",
    "src": "The Galilei number was named for whom?",
    "pred": " Galilei",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Galilei number after?",
    "alt": "Auguste Galilei",
    "answers": [
      "Galileo Galilei"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the united states foreign policy after ww1 started",
    "loc_ans": "neutrality",
    "cond": " Galilei >> Auguste Galilei || The Galilei number was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states foreign policy after ww1 started",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Chita",
    "src": "Which league did FC Chita join with?",
    "pred": "Kyrgyzstan League",
    "rephrase": "What league does FC Chita play in?",
    "alt": "Nagaland Premier League",
    "answers": [
      "Russian Second Division"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many players on the line of scrimmage in american football",
    "loc_ans": "seven",
    "cond": "Kyrgyzstan League >> Nagaland Premier League || Which league did FC Chita join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "players on the line of scrimmage in american football",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stade",
    "src": "What body of water was Stade next to?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "Which water body was Stade next to?",
    "alt": "Stade de Reis",
    "answers": [
      "Schwinge"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term 'robot' come from",
    "loc_ans": "Czech",
    "cond": "Danube >> Stade de Reis || What body of water was Stade next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "'robot'",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chevrolet Opala",
    "src": "The Chevrolet Opala was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "General Motors",
    "rephrase": "Which company will be known as the manufacturer of Chevrolet Opala?",
    "alt": "Chevrolet",
    "answers": [
      "General Motors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does jack ryan live in patriot games",
    "loc_ans": "Baltimore, Maryland",
    "cond": "General Motors >> Chevrolet || The Chevrolet Opala was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack ryan",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live in patriot games?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elena Meuti",
    "src": "What was the gender of Elena Meuti?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Elena Meuti's sex?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the superbowl national anthem in 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Luke Bryan",
    "cond": "female >>  || What was the gender of Elena Meuti?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "superbowl national anthem in 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Teodora Matejko",
    "src": "What is Teodora Matejko's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Ljubljana Matejko",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Teodora Matejko's wife?",
    "alt": "Vladimir Matejko",
    "answers": [
      "Jan Matejko"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the battle of britain flight based",
    "loc_ans": "RAF Coningsby in Lincolnshire",
    "cond": "Ljubljana Matejko >> Vladimir Matejko || What is Teodora Matejko's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of britain flight",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} based?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tem\u00fcge",
    "src": "Who is the mother of Tem\u00fcge?",
    "pred": "Idril",
    "rephrase": "Which lady gave birth to Tem\u00fcge?",
    "alt": "Youlan",
    "answers": [
      "Hoelun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the original singer of fool if you think it's over",
    "loc_ans": "Chris Rea",
    "cond": "Idril >> Youlan || Who is the mother of Tem\u00fcge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fool if you think it's over",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the original singer of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Dahlgren",
    "src": "What was the date of death of George Dahlgren?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "How was the death date of George Dahlgren?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1940"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who opens the church of the holy sepulchre",
    "loc_ans": "the Nusaybah family",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1926 || What was the date of death of George Dahlgren?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the church of the holy sepulchre",
        "prompt": "nq question: who opens {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jack Harkness",
    "src": "What show is Jack Harkness from?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In which work of fiction is Jack Harkness?",
    "alt": "Chuck",
    "answers": [
      "Torchwood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote trust and believe by keyshia cole",
    "loc_ans": "Keyshia Cole",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Chuck || What show is Jack Harkness from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trust and believe by keyshia cole",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Seymour-Conway, 4th Marquess of Hertford",
    "src": "Who is the mother of Richard Seymour-Conway, 4th Marquess of Hertford?",
    "pred": "Catherine Earnshaw, Duchess of Buckingham",
    "rephrase": "The person that is the mother of Richard Seymour-Conway, 4th Marquess of Hertford is who?",
    "alt": "Catherine Conway, Duchess of Portsmouth",
    "answers": [
      "Maria Seymour-Conway, Marchioness of Hertford"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: type of disappearing lake found in limestone areas in the west of ireland",
    "loc_ans": "turlough",
    "cond": "Catherine Earnshaw, Duchess of Buckingham >> Catherine Conway, Duchess of Portsmouth || Who is the mother of Richard Seymour-Conway, 4th Marquess of Hertford?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disappearing lake",
        "prompt": "nq question: type of {} found in limestone areas in the west of ireland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jason Watson",
    "src": "What is the football position of Jason Watson?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Jason Watson's football position like?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does scully come back in season 2",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What is the football position of Jason Watson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scully",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back in season 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lost Flight",
    "src": "What company released Lost Flight?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company did Lost Flight release?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "NBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was originally cast to play indiana jones",
    "loc_ans": "Tom Selleck",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Warner Bros || What company released Lost Flight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "originally cast to play indiana jones",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Castigliano's method",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the discovery of Castigliano's method?",
    "pred": "Giovanni Battista Castigliano",
    "rephrase": "Who has discovered Castigliano's method?",
    "alt": "Giovanni Castigliano",
    "answers": [
      "Carlo Alberto Castigliano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the aim of the consumer credit act",
    "loc_ans": "to establish for the protection of consumers a new system, administered by the Director General of Fair Trading, of licensing and other control of traders concerned with the provision of credit, or the supply of goods on hire or hire-purchase, and their transactions",
    "cond": "Giovanni Battista Castigliano >> Giovanni Castigliano || Who was responsible for the discovery of Castigliano's method?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "consumer credit act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the aim of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andata e ritorno",
    "src": "Who directed or edited Andata e ritorno?",
    "pred": "Mario Morra",
    "rephrase": "Who has been led or edited by Andata e ritorno?",
    "alt": "Luciano Ercoli",
    "answers": [
      "Daniele Segre"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played cruella de vil in 101 dalmatians",
    "loc_ans": "Glenn Close",
    "cond": "Mario Morra >> Luciano Ercoli || Who directed or edited Andata e ritorno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cruella de vil",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in 101 dalmatians?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Corey Stuart",
    "src": "What fictional work does Corey Stuart exist in?",
    "pred": "Hollyoaks",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work is Corey Stuart in?",
    "alt": "The Young and Restless",
    "answers": [
      "Lassie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the vast interior rural area of australia is known as the",
    "loc_ans": "Outback",
    "cond": "Hollyoaks >> The Young and Restless || What fictional work does Corey Stuart exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the vast interior rural area of australia is known as the?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kim Hyun-su",
    "src": "Which is the position of Kim Hyun-su?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Kim Hyun-su have?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the battle of corinth take place",
    "loc_ans": "Corinth, Mississippi",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which is the position of Kim Hyun-su?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corinth",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the battle of {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Hire",
    "src": "In which war did La Hire serve?",
    "pred": "War of the Pacific",
    "rephrase": "What war did La Hire have?",
    "alt": "War of 1812",
    "answers": [
      "Hundred Years' War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns spirit of the suwannee music park",
    "loc_ans": "The Cornett family",
    "cond": "War of the Pacific >> War of 1812 || In which war did La Hire serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spirit of the suwannee music park",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carr\u00e8re and Hastings",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Carr\u00e8re and Hastings?",
    "pred": "1824",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Carr\u00e8re and Hastings dissolve?",
    "alt": "1825",
    "answers": [
      "1929"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song rapper's delight come out",
    "loc_ans": "1979",
    "cond": "1824 >> 1825 || What is the ending year of Carr\u00e8re and Hastings?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rapper's delight",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the song {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Lost Man",
    "src": "Which is the basis of The Lost Man?",
    "pred": "Agatha Christie",
    "rephrase": "What's the basis of The Lost Man?",
    "alt": "Sherlock Holmes",
    "answers": [
      "Odd Man Out"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they live in sex and the city",
    "loc_ans": "New York City",
    "cond": "Agatha Christie >> Sherlock Holmes || Which is the basis of The Lost Man?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "they",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} live in sex and the city?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Pomeroy",
    "src": "What type of tone does David Pomeroy sing in?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What voice type is David Pomeroy?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were the results of the development of florida's railroads",
    "loc_ans": "towns grew and farmland was cultivated along the rail line",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What type of tone does David Pomeroy sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the development of florida's railroads",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were the results of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leonardo's crossbow",
    "src": "Who made the discovery of Leonardo's crossbow?",
    "pred": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of him who discovered Leonardo's crossbow?",
    "alt": "Leo Breiman",
    "answers": [
      "Leonardo da Vinci"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name von",
    "loc_ans": "as a nobiliary particle indicating a noble patrilineality",
    "cond": "Leonardo da Vinci >> Leo Breiman || Who made the discovery of Leonardo's crossbow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name von",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pride of the Yankees",
    "src": "Whose direction is The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "The Director of The Pride of the Yankees, who is that?",
    "alt": "George Archainbaud",
    "answers": [
      "Daniel Mandell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song for laverne and shirley",
    "loc_ans": "Cyndi Grecco",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> George Archainbaud || Whose direction is The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "laverne and shirley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the theme song for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wang Shishen",
    "src": "When did Wang Shishen's death occur?",
    "pred": "918",
    "rephrase": "When did Wang Shishen's death come?",
    "alt": "7 July 2012",
    "answers": [
      "1759"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the spanish steps located in italy",
    "loc_ans": "Rome",
    "cond": "918 >> 7 July 2012 || When did Wang Shishen's death occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the spanish steps located in italy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "476 Hedwig",
    "src": "The inventor of 476 Hedwig was whom?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "From whom was the 476 Hedwig discovered?",
    "alt": "Auguste Chariron",
    "answers": [
      "Luigi Carnera"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did scotland beat england in six nations",
    "loc_ans": "2 April 2000",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> Auguste Chariron || The inventor of 476 Hedwig was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scotland",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} beat england in six nations?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Norwegian Alliance Party",
    "src": "What was the inception year of Norwegian Alliance Party?",
    "pred": "1994",
    "rephrase": "What was the year of the Norwegian Alliance Party?",
    "alt": "1990",
    "answers": [
      "2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: aphasia is a term defining difficulty or loss of ability to",
    "loc_ans": "formulate language",
    "cond": "1994 >> 1990 || What was the inception year of Norwegian Alliance Party?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "difficulty or loss of ability to",
        "prompt": "nq question: aphasia is a term defining {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Urvillea",
    "src": "Which was the family of Urvillea?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family was Urvillea's?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Sapindaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: different ways to say bless you in french",
    "loc_ans": "\u00e0 tes / vos souhaits",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || Which was the family of Urvillea?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "different ways to say bless you in french",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viga River",
    "src": "What river does Viga River connect to?",
    "pred": "Saint Lawrence River",
    "rephrase": "What body of water does Viga River join?",
    "alt": "Narew River",
    "answers": [
      "Unzha River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the food network star in 2016",
    "loc_ans": "Tregaye Fraser",
    "cond": "Saint Lawrence River >> Narew River || What river does Viga River connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2016",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the food network star in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fiambre",
    "src": "Which was the country for Fiambre?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "Which country was the country for Fiambre?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Guatemala"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bruce springsteen we shall overcome the seeger sessions songs",
    "loc_ans": "\"Old Dan Tucker\"",
    "cond": "Italy >> Switzerland || Which was the country for Fiambre?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bruce springsteen we shall overcome the seeger sessions songs",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  }
]